（song）
（歌曲）
hello？
你好？
Yeah, I saw.
是的，我看到了。
I saw when I switched over.
我换的时候看到了
Hey, I didn't think. I didn't say anything.
嘿，我没想到。 我什么也没说。
It's OK. It's OK. It's OK.
没关系。 没关系。 没关系。
It's early.
还早呢。
It's like 7 a.m..
好像是早上七点...
I am.
我是。
I am sleepy.
我困了。
I just woke up like not too long ago.
我刚刚醒来，就像不久前一样。
I'm getting grief already. It's.
我已经开始悲伤了。 它的。
It happens.
它发生了。
It happens, guys.
它发生了，伙计们。
Oh, God.
天啊。
OK, well, good morning, everybody.
好的，好的，大家早上好。
what's up*3
怎么了*3
as a gallon of yard.
作为一加仑的院子。
Hopefully everybody enjoyed their all their time last night. I.
希望每个人都喜欢他们昨晚的所有时间。 一世。
I was.
我曾是。
I had a great time of all the all the funny videos you guys submitted, and
你们提交的所有有趣的视频让我玩得很开心，而且
it was.
它是。
I still can't stop thinking about the fucking kayak.com.
我仍然无法停止思考该死的 kayak.com。
They are obviously everyone's having a great
他们显然是每个人都过得很愉快，或者每个人都已经度过了一个愉快的周末。
And you're excited for this fucking collab.
你对这次他妈的合作感到兴奋。
Wow. Now, I didn't even start, and.
哇。 现在，我什至没有开始，而且。
Holy shit,
天啦噜，
Yeah,
是啊，这游戏还没开始，我就已经输了。
Not. Not too much, but just a tad bit.
不是。 不是太多，只是一点点。
Okay.
好的。
Like it's ever so slightly
就像它是如此轻微地到达我想要的地步，就像，用我的手指环绕着他的脖子
and just squeeze the life out of him slowly and slowly and slowly.
慢慢地，慢慢地，慢慢地把他的生命挤出来。
And give him maybe give him a kiss on the cheek, and that's it.
给他也许在他的脸颊上亲一下，就是这样。
Yeah, well, it.
是的，嗯，它。
You know, it's to be expected when you are I feel like anytime anytime I collab for
你知道，当你是我的感觉时，这是可以预料的，我随时合作
EN niji boy, I end up losing my shit at some point in time.
EN niji 男孩，我最终会在某个时间点失去我的狗屎。
Right. They just were fond of this.
对。 他们只是喜欢这个。
It's. It's does not take too long.
它的。 它不需要太长时间。
It really doesn't take that long, guys.
伙计们，这真的不需要那么长时间。
Poor mysta, though.
不过，可怜的米斯塔。
What do you mean, poor mysta?
你是什​​么意思，可怜的米斯塔？
What about poor me?
可怜的我呢？
Huh? Well, what are you talking about?
嗯？ 好吧，你在说什么？
Poor mysta.
可怜的米斯塔。
what the fuck are you talking about?
你他妈在说什么？
Poor shoto, though, dude.
不过，可怜的shoto，伙计。
Oh, come on, dear. Shoto.
哦，来吧，亲爱的。 肖托。
Today is my.
今天是我的。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
Where all this bullshit bothers you?
所有这些废话在哪里困扰你？
Oh, do you say? OK.
哦，你说？ 好的。
Sorry I didn't get to say it.
抱歉我没来得及说。
Could you say happy birthday up.
你能不能说生日快乐。
Happy birthday.
生日快乐。
Hope  you having a great day?
希望你有一个美好的一天？
I feel like at this point, every stream will, like, encounter somebody's birthday
我觉得在这一点上，每一个流都会，就像，遇到某人的生日
and are opting for the donation.
并选择捐赠。
And just thank you for the tiny gifts of suppositories.
并感谢您提供栓剂的小礼物。
Good morning, dudes.
早安，伙计们。
I'm probably going to have alerts off the screen
我可能会在屏幕上显示警报，只是因为，你知道，出于对
what's it disrespect for the the collab and just make sure, like,
什么是对合作的不尊重，只是确保在我们玩的时候没有任何东西被打断。
But I will read through the donations when I do have time, though,
但是，当我有时间的时候，我会仔细阅读捐款，所以不要担心。
My dear children and guild members.
我亲爱的孩子们和公会成员。
It is OK
没关系
Happy birthday.
生日快乐。
Happy birthday, bro.
生日快乐，兄弟。
Happy birthday Audi ok.
祝奥迪生日快乐。
But I'm really excited for this game.
但我对这场比赛真的很兴奋。
I don't have any idea what it's I.
我不知道我是什么。
I just know like we had to break out of prison of each other and
我只知道我们必须越狱
I don't know if you saw last time
不知道你上次有没有看到
we had that kind of collaboration, it's kind of
我们有那种合作，它是那种
it was kind of scuffed.
它有点磨损。
OK, I'm going to turn off the lights right now, actually.
好的，我现在要关灯，事实上。
Yeah, it was a really fucking scuffed because Bunnymen
是的，这真的很他妈的磨损，因为兔人
I've never like, I've never sweated that much.
我从来没有喜欢过，我从来没有出过那么多汗。
I've never yelled out much.
我从来没有大喊大叫。
I've never lost my mind that much silencer in the fucking dog years.
在该死的狗年里，我从来没有失去过这么多的消音器。
Oh, my. God.
天啊。 上帝。
Why do you do. This, guys?
你为什么这样做。 这，伙计们？
Why the fuck do you do this? I'm
你他妈为什么要这么做？ 我是
you know, one know they're going to go
你知道，一个人知道他们会去
fuck you.
去你的。
OK? But yeah, so
好的？ 但是，是的，上帝，我失去了你。
What the fuck was I saying? What the hell was I even saying, dude?
我他妈在说什么？ 我到底在说什么，伙计？
Yeah.
是的。
So last time we had a collaboration,
所以上次我们进行了合作，有一次我说它还不错。
A little cave, man, we fucked around, like, quite a bit,
一个小山洞，伙计，我们到处乱搞，就像，相当多，
and I may or may not have lost my mind by the end of it.
到最后我可能会也可能不会失去理智。
So much so we started stress eating, dude.
如此之多，以至于我们开始强调饮食，伙计。
We we had to, like.
我们不得不，喜欢。
There was.
有。
Like, 2 hours in.
比如，2小时。
He was in a bag of chips, and I was eating jerky, and he never eats on stream
他在一袋薯条里，我在吃肉干，他从不在直播中吃东西
unless, like, you know, he gets, he gets to a point like that.
除非，比如，你知道，他得到了，他达到了那样的地步。
Pushed him to a point.
把他逼到了一个点。
I push off points, you OK.
我推开分，你行。
I think I'm ready, though, so give us a break.
不过，我想我已经准备好了，所以让我们休息一下。
No, I will not.
不我不会。
I'm not do that.
我不是那样做的。
That's earned those boxer
这是赚来的，那些拳击手不能随便索取，就像我要免费给你一样
right now.
现在。
There's no free barks in this household sometimes.
这个家里有时没有免费的树皮。
Also, thank you for the hygiene, guys.
另外，谢谢你们的卫生，伙计们。
I didn't get to say thank you for that.
我没来得及说谢谢。
Sorry, but ba ba ba ba
对不起，但是 ba ba ba 与
with the AC. I think that it's on our end.
AC。 我认为这是我们的目标。
Ah, thank you for all the resources, guys.
啊，谢谢你们提供的所有资源，伙计们。
Appreciate it. Welcome back.
欣赏它。 欢迎回来。
OK, I think he's ready now.
好的，我想他现在已经准备好了。
So I'm going to switch over to the game.
所以我要切换到游戏。
All right?
好的？
Yeah. hold on
是的。 坚持，稍等
where am I?
我在哪里？
Well, there I am.
嗯，我来了。
The actor
演员
Da Vinci.
达芬奇。
Yes, I know. Da Vinci.
是的，我知道。 达芬奇。
I know him.
我认识他。
The one from the Titanic.
泰坦尼克号上的那个。
Da Vinci.
达芬奇。
Oh, he taught we.
哦，他教我们的。
Oh, yeah, we. Talked about that. We talked about this last time.
哦，是的，我们。 谈到了那个。 我们上次谈过这个。
You know this very.
你很清楚这一点。
We talked about this last time ,mysta.
我们上次讨论过这个，mysta。
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
We literally talked.
我们从字面上谈了起来。
Did we not talk about this?
我们没谈过这个吗？
I swear to God, it.
我向上帝发誓，它。
We did. Yeah, we did. We did.
我们做到了。 是的，我们做到了。 我们做到了。
So I just like gaslighting you.
所以我只是喜欢给你点煤气灯。
I was talking about in my chat just now.
我刚才在聊天中谈到。
Well, OK. Well, good morning.
好吧，好吧。 嗯，早上好。
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿嘿嘿。
My blood pressure is high already.
我的血压已经很高了。
That's fucking great, man. Let's go.
这他妈的太棒了，伙计。 我们走吧。
I'll be ready to break out of jail today.
我今天将准备出狱。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
OK. Sorry.
好的。 对不起。
So what will. Happen?
那会怎样。 发生？
What you do?
你做什么？
I want to make sure my got a picture of my face on the screen, like.
我想确保我在屏幕上有一张我的脸，比如。
Zoomed in really fucking close.
放大得真他妈的近。
Oops.
哎呀。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I think that's not valid. I show them your beautiful face.
我认为这是无效的。 我向他们展示你美丽的脸庞。
I know. Right?
我知道。 对？
I was getting a sense already because apparently any sense of this game, we.
我已经有了一种感觉，因为显然我们对这款游戏有任何感觉。
Have to censor this. Game.
必须审查这一点。 游戏。
Apparently, there's like a scene where you have to censor.
显然，这就像一个你必须审查的场景。
I don't know when, though.
不过，我不知道什么时候。
Ah. Oh, shit.
啊。 妈的。
Well, I didn't know that, hon.
嗯，我不知道，亲爱的。
What?
什么？
You had to censor this fucking game?
你必须审查这该死的游戏？
Are you kidding?
你在开玩笑吗？
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Let me get a censor image to. I don't know if you're a yes.
让我得到一个审查图像。 我不知道你是否是。
Are you sure you're not? Yes. I mean. Then you're being for realising I.
你确定不是吗？ 是的。 我是说。 那你就是为了认识我。
My chat said so.
我的聊天是这样说的。
OK, so my chat would never lie to me.
好的，所以我的聊天永远不会骗我。
That's fucking Calvin, you know, as fucking calves.
那是他妈的卡尔文，你知道，作为他妈的小牛。
Shut the hell up, OK?
闭嘴，好吗？
We find a good image.
我们找到了一个好的图像。
Can you give me a good image?
你能给我一个好的形象吗？
A good image?
好形象？
When I used image, I'm using.
当我使用图像时，我正在使用。
What Never mind.
什么没关系。
I'll end up.
我会结束的。
I'll just use this. In this case.
我会用这个。 在这种情况下。
Yeah, I'll put it in the middle of the screen.
是的，我会把它放在屏幕中间。
OK, I'm ready now.
好的，我现在准备好了。
What did you get arrested for?
你是因为什么被捕的？
I got arrested for being too fucking funny.
我因为太他妈的搞笑而被捕了。
Too funny, too attractive ,too sexy, too top.
太有趣了，太有吸引力了，太性感了，太顶级了。
Too top? was it in your title right now.
太顶了？ 现在在你的标题里吗？
Can you read out your title?
你能读出你的标题吗？
My title? Yeah. Your streams.
我的头衔？ 是的。 你的流。
I tell ya, some.
我告诉你，一些。
That's some contradictory.
这就有些矛盾了。
So you could you play a way out with Shoto? OK.
所以你能和Shoto一起玩出路吗？ 好的。
Oh, you are a motherfucker.
哦，你是个混蛋。
You're such a whore.
你真是个婊子。
You know what happened?
你知道发生了什么吗？
You must like I was about I was Larry about to start stream.
你一定像我一样，我是拉里即将开始直播。
Right?
对？
You're like, oh, here's the new link.
你就像，哦，这是新的链接。
Must be out of it.
一定是脱离了。
And I was I was like, oh, shit.
我当时就像，哦，狗屎。
I had to readjust.
我不得不重新调整。
Everything now because the original he died this asshole.
现在的一切都是因为原来他死了这个混蛋。
That's not my fault.
那不是我的错。
I, I don't, I don't usually do this shit man.
我，我不，我通常不做这个狗屎的人。
I don't collab with people.
我不与人合作。
The fuck are you calling me?
你他妈在叫我？
Special oh, you don't want.
特别哦，你不要。
No. I'm just saying I don't collab with people.
不，我只是说我不与人合作。
But the fact that you're collabing with me means, like,
但是你和我合作的事实意味着，比如，
and you don't collab with people often means that you like me or you like(muah, muah,muah)
而且你不与人合作通常意味着你喜欢我或你喜欢（muah，muah，muah）
your breath smells.
你的呼吸有味道。
It stinks. It stinks.
它很臭。 它很臭。
Get the fuck away.
滚开
Brush your teeth.
刷牙。
Mysta. OK.
米斯塔。 好的。
Did OK, Mysta.
没问题，米斯塔。
Wong. Hold on, hold on. Don't do it.
黄。 等一下，等一下。 不要做。
Don't be that way. Don't be that way.
不要那样。 不要那样。
I can. OK, you're not haunted.
我可以。 好吧，你没有闹鬼。
I'll do something.
我会做点什么。
I'll do something a little sweet for you, OK?(muah)
我给你做点甜蜜的事好吗？(muah)
Non. You didn't see it on your side, but people saw it on my side.
非。 你没有在你身边看到它，但人们在我身边看到了它。
But on any side, just my moderator's I it's get rid of you.
但在任何方面，只是我的版主的我是摆脱你。
Get rid of me, get rid of me now don't take it away, please.
摆脱我，现在摆脱我，请不要把它带走。
No, what the fuck?
不，他妈的是什么？
All that's that's like that's like bottom of the barrel type of disrespect.
所有这一切就像是桶底部的不尊重。
Come on, honey.
来吧，亲爱的。
Come on, man.
来吧，伙计。
You know what?
你知道吗？
Your breath smells beautiful.
你的呼吸闻起来很美。
It smells great. Delicious.
它闻起来很棒。 美味的。
I would.
我会。
I would put it in their perfume bottle and spread all over myself every single day.
我会把它放在他们的香水瓶里，每天都涂在自己身上。
That's just how much I love your breath.
这就是我多么爱你的呼吸。
That's how much I love how much you smell.
这就是我有多爱你的气味。
You smell good.
你的味道很好。
I love the way your feet smell at night.
我喜欢你的脚在晚上闻起来的味道。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Anyways, I'm going to get start over again.
不管怎样，我要重新开始。
I'm going to get started again.
我要重新开始了。
I'm going to click start right now, OK?
我现在要点击开始，好吗？
And just see what happens oh.
看看会发生什么哦。
Connected with. Shoto.
与。 肖托。
What's your plan after this? Like some love and shit.
这之后你有什么打算？ 就像一些爱和狗屎。
I don't know,
我不知道，
but I thought about it.
但我想了想。
You haven't thought about it?
你没有想过吗？
Though. Must be he.
尽管。 一定是他。
Talking about the universe. No.
谈论宇宙。 不。
Vastly different.
大不相同。
Nothing. Nothing. Thinks I'm being smart.
没有。 没有。 认为我很聪明。
Leo, are you implying that I'm not smart?
狮子座，你是在暗示我不聪明吗？
Or words? I'm smart.
还是文字？ 我很聪明。
Hey, I might not be smart in your book, but I do get shit done.
嘿，我可能在你的书中并不聪明，但我确实完成了一些事情。
Exactly.
确切地。
I like that.
我喜欢。
Are you with that? Bam!
你同意吗？ 砰！
We got the right characters for each other.
我们为彼此找到了合适的角色。
Oh, no. We get to. Choose. Hold on. Wait.
不好了。 我们到了。 选择。 坚持，稍等。 等待。
We could be. Someone. You can be Leo Caruso.
我们可能是。 某人。 你可以成为里奥·卡鲁索。
Crime, armed robbery.
犯罪，持械抢劫。
Wait a second. Personality.
等一下。 性格。
Yeah.
是的。
Let's just don't discipline reserved, confident, short tempered joker.
让我们不要管教矜持、自信、脾气暴躁的小丑。
Sweetheart, this person is
甜心，这个人在获得金融大学学位并与他的高中甜心结婚后，
Vince installed in the job in banking.
文斯在银行工作。
What the hell
我勒个去
embezzlement, murder and fraud.
贪污、谋杀和欺诈。
Y'all, let's go.
你们，我们走吧。
What the fuck. Shoto, murder.
什么鬼。 肖托，谋杀。
Murder is a murder is something it's murder is OK.
谋杀是谋杀是谋杀是可以的。
Sentence.
句子。
Oh, what. Did you do? 14 years.
啊什么。 你做了吗？  14年。
I live six months.
我活了六个月。
Grand theft. Oh, wait there.
大盗。 哦，在那儿等着。
Well, I I.
嗯，我我。
Could actually see you committing grand theft auto.
实际上可以看到你犯了侠盗猎车手。
OK? Is that when you steal a car?
好的？ 那是你偷车的时候吗？
Yeah, I think that's when you steal a car, right?
是的，我想那是你偷车的时候，对吧？
Yeah, that's when you steal a car. One I think so.
是的，那是你偷车的时候。 一个我觉得。
OK, you know, I'm joking.
好吧，你知道，我在开玩笑。
How have these options
怎么有这些选项
yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
Let's get all of this
让我们得到这一切
dude.
老兄。
I fucking forgot my name.
我他妈的忘记了我的名字。
shoto. shoto? No.
肖托。 射击？ 不。
You dip.
你浸。
I'm obviously I'm so glad I did. Yeah. Fuck.
我显然很高兴我做到了。 是的。 他妈的。
Shut the fuck up. Don't call me a debt.
他妈的闭嘴。 不要称我为债务。
What is that?
那是什么？
I've never had anyone could be a dip before.
我以前从未有过任何人可以浸入水中。
What does that even mean?
那有什么意思？
When you wouldn't, you lost your mouth.
如果你不这样做，你就失去了你的嘴。
Wouldn't you like to know a dip?
你不想了解一下吗？
These balls.
这些球。
I wish.
我希望。
I wish I had my heart rate monitor on right now.
我希望我现在有我的心率监测器。
You could see it probably just spiked up, like.
你可以看到它可能刚刚飙升，就像。
Oh, am I making you flustered?
哦，我让你心慌了吗？
No, you're not.
不，你不是。
Make me.
让我。
Feel.
感觉。
OK. Like we haven't even started playing the game.
好的。 就像我们还没有开始玩游戏一样。
Let's control ourselves.
让我们控制自己。
How about we be civilised for maybe 10 seconds, OK?
我们文明 10 秒钟怎么样，好吗？
And and why are we going into prison?
我们为什么要进监狱？
Yeah, you're going to prison, babe.
是的，你要进监狱了，宝贝。
Isn't this romantic?
这不是很浪漫吗？
And it's fucking romantic, right? Date.
这他妈的很浪漫，对吧？ 日期。
Can we go in the shower together?
我们可以一起去洗澡吗？
I think we can, actually.
我认为我们可以，事实上。
Oh, I mean, you offered, so you can't.
哦，我的意思是，你提供了，所以你不能。
You can't just pull out or you want to pull out.
你不能只是拉出来，或者你想拉出来。
You're not going to pull out on me.
你不会拉我的。
Yeah, you know, I've never pulled out in my life.
是的，你知道，我这辈子从来没有退出过。
All right?
好的？
That's what I like to hear.
这就是我喜欢听到的。
Is you.
是你。
Yeah. You ain't got no drifted.
是的。 你没有迷路。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Are you talking about.
你在说吗。
Look at my dress shirt.
看看我的礼服衬衫。
Not shit has the patterns.
不是狗屎有模式。
You saying I have no drip dribble.
你说我没有滴滴运球。
No drip.  way to see me?
没有滴水。 怎么见我？
OK, ok. OK.
好的好的。 好的。
I just look at you like you're looks so fucking stupid.
我只是看着你，就像你看起来很愚蠢一样。
I have floral. What the hell do you have?
我有花。 你到底有什么？
You're going to have a plain white dress shirt. No.
你将有一件纯白色的衬衫。 不。
Wait forever.
永远等待。
You're probably already here.
你可能已经在这里了。
Yeah, I'm going to be right here. Right now.
是的，我会在这里。 现在。
Ask me on the bench. Look at that. Yep.
在板凳上问我。 看那个。 是的。
That's me.
那是我。
You think that's drip? Do you have a white shirt?
你以为是滴滴？ 你有白衬衫吗？
You have a white shirt.
你有一件白衬衫。
You just have a single white t shirt.
你只有一件白色T恤。
Oh, look at me.
哦，看着我。
Shirt.
衬衫。
Fuck off.
滚蛋。
Fuck off, darling.
滚蛋，亲爱的。
OK, well, on.
好的，好的，开。
I don't know. How I jog.
我不知道。 我怎么慢跑。
Ooh. Hold on.
哦。 坚持，稍等。
Wait a minute. Just I'm going to introduce myself real quick.
等一下。 只是我要快速介绍一下自己。
I'm a little bit smaller, even smaller till now.
我小了一点，甚至小到现在。
They see the game, OK?
他们看比赛，好吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I guess I just was outside.
我想我只是在外面。
Yeah, I. That's enough. It's OK.
是的，我。这就够了。 没关系。
What do you think? Chat.
你怎么看？ 聊天。
Should I make, like, small or not? Get off.
我应该做小还是不做？ 下车。
This. Hmm.
这。 唔。
I think this is good enough for me.
我认为这对我来说已经足够好了。
OK, what do you think? Shot?
好的，你怎么看？ 射击？
Yes, of fucking al. Bravo. All right.
是的，他妈的人。 太棒了。 好的。
We don't have all day.
我们没有一整天。
All right.
好的。
Only get smaller. A little smaller, ok?
只会变小。 小一点，好吗？
Everyone wants it to be a little bit smaller.
每个人都希望它小一点。
I'll do that then. Oh.
那时我会这样做。 哦。
He go. Look, I'm small, dude.
他去。 看，我很小，伙计。
Your ear is your fucking.
你的耳朵是你他妈的。
Was it a fox series or, like, taking up, like, 70%.
是狐狸系列还是占据了 70%。
Thing, you know, all of these stupid dog.
事情，你知道，所有这些愚蠢的狗。
Fine. Look, sign that. That's a thing.
美好的。 看，签那个。 那是一回事。
Put it back on, put it back on and there's certain there's certain like,
戴上它，再戴上它，肯定有一定的，你知道的，它在上面的魅力点。
Yeah. Yeah, I like that. OK, I'm small now.
是的。 是的，我喜欢这样。 好吧，我现在还小。
You're also small.
你还小。
Small p you always small there.
小p你总是小在那里。
All right.
好的。
I'll just put you up on me here.
我会把你放在我这里。
Yeah I'm a big that's right now I've been I'm very excited
是的，我现在是一个大人物，在过去的
for this for the past 24 hours.
24 小时里，我一直对此感到非常兴奋。
To play with me.
陪我玩。
Get inside don't fight it, OK?
进去别打了，好吗？
Maybe, maybe I didn't see that.
也许，也许我没有看到。
But you do want to you want to out what else.
但是你确实想你想出什么别的。
That's a just everybody right now right here.
那就是现在这里的每个人。
Are you go punch those people. Oh, no, that's not you.
你去打那些人。 哦，不，那不是你。
Know, that's not me. I'm just watching someone fight.
知道，那不是我。 我只是在看一个人打架。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Please.
请。
OK, what do you want. About some prison.
好的，你想要什么。 关于某个监狱。
What do you want? Hmm?
你想要什么？ 唔？
I'll just be walking around. Stay strong.
我只会四处走走。 坚强点。
You think I'm weak?
你觉得我弱吗？
You think I'm a pussy, huh?
你以为我是猫，对吧？
I did not say that.
我没那么说过。
I see.
我懂了。
I fuck people up I fuck up. Really?
我操别人我操。 真的吗？
Yeah. I guess I'll just walk around this way.
是的。 我想我会这样走。
Yeah, I'm sure you do.
是的，我相信你会的。
I know.
我知道。
So in that fight out there, it was brutal.
所以在那场战斗中，这是残酷的。
It was your bones crack.
那是你的骨头裂开。
Yeah. I didn't do shit, though.
是的。 不过，我没有做坏事。
Oh, my God, man, this place is bad. It's.
哦，天哪，伙计，这个地方很糟糕。 它的。
It's really going to fight.
真的要打了。
I don't know. I'm not.
我不知道。 我不是。
I can't survive in here.
我不能在这里生存。
I don't belong in here, man.
我不属于这里，伙计。
We're having, like, two different conversation.
我们正在进行两次不同的对话。
We're having two conversations lot.
我们正在进行两次对话。
We'll wait for yours to finish.
我们会等你的完成。
I'll just stop talking to this guy.
我会停止和这个人说话。
This guys. I don't even know. What this dude said.
这家伙。 我根本不知道。 这哥们说的。
Yeah, this guy. Gotcha.
是的，这个人。 明白了。
What do you know? He'll be fine.
你知道什么？ 他会没事的。
What is this?
这是什么？
What is it you know about this?
你对此有什么了解？
Be it's bad news, man.
不管是坏消息，伙计。
Bad fucking news. Really? You serious?
坏消息。 真的吗？ 你是认真的？
Worst mistake of my Lalo's chucked in here.
我拉罗的最糟糕的错误被扔在这里了。
The worst mistake.
最严重的错误。
Ok, stop.
好的，停下来。
No inmates behind this point.
这一点背后没有囚犯。
Can I go potty?
我可以上厕所吗？
Get in there.
进到那里去。
Oh, yeah. Pop me down, baby.
哦耶。 让我下来，宝贝。
No, he
不，他
he touched somewhere.
他摸到了某个地方。
Edition of what the hell.
版什么鬼。
Did you read?
你读了吗？
He really.
他真的。
I didn't get to see him.
我没来得及见他。
Oh, you can you can do it yourself.
哦，你可以，你可以自己做。
Yeah, I'm probably got pads on eventually. Oh.
是的，我可能最终得到了垫子。 哦。
That's all right.
没关系。
Let me in.
让我进去。
I can't believe you just.
我简直不敢相信你。
Said love and. Such. You are. So
说爱和。 这样的。 你是。 所以
what does that cause?
那是什么原因？
I think that that caught me off guard.
我想这让我措手不及。
I can't stop thinking about it like you really threw a curveball. OK,
我不能停止思考它，就像你真的扔了一个曲线球一样。 好的，
where am I going?
我要去哪里？
Oh, he pushed me.
哦，他推我。
No Internet duty fucking pushed me.
没有互联网职责他妈的推动我。
You got punched. Oh, shit.
你被打了 妈的。
Hey, are we good?
嘿，我们好吗？
Are you guys good?
你们好吗？
I think so.
我认同。
For some reason, my chat just a oh, god.
出于某种原因，我的聊天只是一个哦，上帝。
I think we get
我想我们得到
privileges now.
现在的特权。
OK, cool. Yeah, it's just a bit of lag.
嗯不错。 是的，只是有点滞后。
Yeah, but a lag I think YouTube's being a bit funky.
是的，但我认为 YouTube 有点过时了。
Get undressed. Wait.
脱衣服。 等待。
They want me to undress, right?
他们要我脱衣服，对吧？
Do I have the sense of you?
我对你有感觉吗？
I think you're going to be naked.
我想你会赤身裸体。
I think they're not going to show an EP.
我认为他们不会展示 EP。
I'm pretty sure it's OK. Like, Oh, my God.
我很确定没问题。 就像，哦，我的上帝。
You two break it up now.
你们两个现在分手吧。
It heals this guy.
它治愈了这个人。
Harvey. Sensitive guys. Fuck you.
哈维。 敏感的家伙。 去你的。
Censor what?
审查什么？
Really? Censor
真的吗？ 审查
no, it's OK. This is. Fine.
不，没关系。 这是。 美好的。
There's a look at my ass.
看看我的屁股。
This is fine.
这可以。
See, this is why I am.
看，这就是我的原因。
I'm glad I drove this OK?
我很高兴我开车这样好吗？
My head censoring it.
我的头审查它。
Oh, my God. I think I'm fine. I think I'm fine.
我的天啊。 我觉得我很好。 我觉得我很好。
Are we good?
我们好吗？
I think I'm ok.
我觉得我还可以。
I think. I'm ok. Oh,
我认为。 我很好。 哦，
dude.
老兄。
Oh, ok.
哦好的。
I'm. I'm trying. I'm trying.
我是。 我在尝试。 我在尝试。
I'm trying to shut up.
我试着闭嘴。
I was trying to cover. OK.
我试图掩饰。 好的。
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
There's a full on cock. I didn't see a cock.
有一个完整的公鸡。 我没有看到公鸡。
Did you was a cowboy.
你是牛仔吗？
Was there really a cock up the coffee one?
咖啡里真的有一只公鸡吗？
What the hell?
我勒个去？
All my stop gaslighting me.
我所有的停止给我加油。
There's no way I didn't see one.
我不可能没有看到一个。
You are a.
你是一个。
Bitch. You are a horny
婊子。 你是一个角质同性恋。 看
hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持。
Where is it? Where is it? OK, ok. I have it on my screen now.
它在哪里？ 它在哪里？ 好的好的。 我现在在我的屏幕上。
Why is the screen size changing?
为什么屏幕尺寸会发生变化？
It's changing, dude. I don't.
它正在改变，伙计。 我不。
I can't tell you.
我不能告诉你。
All right.
好的。
Well, and this is my present.
嗯，这是我的礼物。
This isn't going to work.
这是行不通的。
Yeah.
是的。
When are we allowed in here?
我们什么时候可以进来？
Uh, well, I'll just chill here.
呃，好吧，我就在这里冷静一下。
I guess
我猜
oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
Oh, my. God. Guys.
天啊。 上帝。 伙计们。
Just imagine a bunch of naked guys right now, OK?
想象一下现在有一群赤身裸体的人，好吗？
It's censored.
它受到审查。
We're fine.
我们都很好。
We're fine. They censored it for us.
我们都很好。 他们为我们审查了它。
You all walk around.
你们都走来走去。
Interesting picture.
有趣的图片。
Wow. Go, go, go. Nice.
哇。 去！去！去。 好的。
I love pictures. Dude.
我喜欢图片。 老兄。
There's a lot of butts already. Picture.
已经有很多屁股了。 图片。
Yeah, there's a lot of nudity on the screen right now.
是的，现在屏幕上有很多裸体。
Hey, what is this?
嘿，这是什么？
Oh, let me wash my hands before I jackoff.
哦，让我在开学前先洗手。
OK, nice. Hey, look at my plate.
好的，不错。 嘿，看看我的盘子。
I see my butt.
我看到我的屁股。
Come on, get up. You wish us. Is that nice?
来吧，起来吧。 你希望我们。 那很好吗？
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
I see.
我懂了。
What do you mean? It looks better.
你什么意思？ 它看起来更好。
You guys say
你们说
this dude has this dude.
这个家伙有这个家伙。
Has 40 -year-old man butt.
拥有40岁男人的屁股。
Do you think about that and why?
你有没有想过这个，为什么？
Why is it offensive, dad?
爸爸，为什么会冒犯？
How much is it like the fucking said
像他妈说的多少钱
what the hell
搞什么鬼
I hear you
我听说你在我身上看到了狙击手，但我什么也没做。
Why are you getting mad at me?
你为什么生我的气？
I was just walking up the stairs, huh?
我刚上楼梯，嗯？
Yeah, that was you, Dad.
是的，就是你，爸爸。
I literally was.
我真的是。
You fucking this guy.
你他妈的这家伙。
Obviously, it's going to be me.
显然，这将是我。
I do not.
我不。
Understand the concept of a split screen multiplayer.
了解分屏多人游戏的概念。
You did.
你做到了。
I swear to God, you did. There is.
我向上帝发誓，你做到了。 有。
I see you in that. Oh, my God. You see me.
我在那里看到你。 我的天啊。 你看我。
So you
所以你是灵魂伴侣或喜欢，卖兄弟或卖邻居。
Some fucking God. No, I refuse.
某个该死的神。 不，我拒绝。
No, you know what?
不，你知道吗？
You know, I'm not putting any clothes on.
你知道，我没有穿任何衣服。
I'm not seeing any clothes on.
我没有看到任何衣服。
You can stare at my bare ass.
你可以盯着我光着屁股看。
Fuck you, mysta. Holy shit.
去你妈的，米斯塔。 天啊。
No, no. Just embrace embrace it.
不，不。 只是拥抱拥抱它。
Whatever, dude.
随你怎样，伙计。
I'm just going to sit down then.
那我就坐下吧。
Basically embrace it.
基本上拥抱它。
I don't, I don't want to look your. ass now keep.
我没有，我不想看你的。 屁股现在保持。
I'm not looking people looking.
我不是在看人在看。
Trust is everywhere.
信任无处不在。
Zoom in on this hold on.
放大这个保持。
There's a there has to be a way to manipulate the angle
必须有一种方法来操纵角度，这样我才能得到完整的屁股覆盖。
Right, right.
是的是的。
I'm not looking.
我不是在看。
This. You're I'm not looking. As you are.
这。 你是我不找。 就像你一样。
Don't don't lie.
不要不要说谎。
I'ma.
我是一个。
Fuck you all
去你妈的
yeah. 49.
是的。  49.
Suit.
套装。
I fucking
我他妈的
I'm so happy enough.
我很高兴。
Damn.
该死。
Even he wants me put on clothes ? why?
连他都要我穿衣服？ 为什么？
Why did it pan like that?
为什么会变成这样？
Why it's so good the ass was over your head boy, did you know why.
为什么它这么好，屁股在你的头上，你知道为什么吗？
Yeah. Hello.
是的。 你好。
Well, that's a a party.
嗯，那是一个聚会。
That's me. Yeah, that's you.
那是我。 是的，就是你。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I like your beard out, not your beard.
我喜欢你的胡子，不是你的胡子。
Your sideburns.
你的鬓角。
Thank you. I grew them myself.
谢谢你。 我自己种的。
I came out my room with these shit.
我带着这些狗屎走出了我的房间。
Yeah.
是的。
All right. So I want to talk of you.
好的。 所以我想谈谈你。
Oh, is it you? Oh, is it me?
哦，是你吗？ 哦，是我吗？
Where are you?
你在哪里？
I don't think so. It wants me to get up.
我不这么认为。 它要我起来。
See points of interest and care about these people.
查看兴趣点并关心这些人。
Yeah, I don't care about them.
是的，我不在乎他们。
I'm like, you need to work out. Just be me. Do this.
我想，你需要锻炼。 就当我吧。 做这个。
He's telling me.
他在告诉我。
I need to work.
我需要工作。
Out, but oh.
出来了，但是哦。
Oh, OK, fine.
哦，好的，好的。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I'll. I'll do it to you like a week.
患病的。 我会像一周一样对你做。
Did you got, you know, look at me, look at me.
你有没有，你知道，看着我，看着我。
Look at me, look at me on the couch. I'm going to catch up.
看看我，看看沙发上的我。 我要赶上。
Doughnut.
甜甜圈。
I mean, I at eight. Nine.
我是说，我八岁。 九。
Oh, gosh.
哦，天哪。
Ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔噢
Filled way up.
充满了向上。
It's not so much
不是那么多
God's way.
天道。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
This is something.
这是东西。
Stop it.
停下来。
Just stop typing.
只是停止打字。
Let me catch up to you.
让我追上你。
What?
什么？
One more, one more. Oh, my God.
再来一张，再来一张。 我的天啊。
Why does it have so much?
为什么它有这么多？
My arm ow, ow, ow.
我的胳膊啊啊啊啊啊啊
Dude, you have.
伙计，你有。
You have a deaf age. Deaf. Oh.
你已经聋哑了。 聋。 哦。
Oh, my God. That's not fair. Oh,
我的天啊。 这不公平。 哦，
I'm still typing
我还在打字
I'm still typing by still passing is out there. So bad, so bad, you are so bad.
我仍在打字，但仍然在外面。 太糟糕了，太糟糕了，你太糟糕了。
I'm like, 43 years old.
我就像，43岁。
Did look at.
看过了。
So fucking bad. Dude
太他妈坏了 老兄
I is still typing, Help.
我还在打字，求助。
Oh, yes, I did it. Oh.
哦，是的，我做到了。 哦。
Dude, my arm hurts.
哥们，我的胳膊疼。
Oh, let me go, let me go.
哦，放开我，放开我。
You are like, oh, my God, Slack.
你就像，哦，天哪，Slack。
It's time to hurry.
是时候快点了。
Oh, oh, do I have.
哦，哦，我有。
To help you up?
帮你起来？
It's not about one hour.
这不是大约一小时。
Help me to help me about what?
帮我帮我一下什么？
Harvey wants that piece.
哈维想要那块。
He should be happy he's on the outside.
他应该很高兴他在外面。
Oh, he might be on the outside.
哦，他可能在外面。
He just got to watch me.
他只得看着我。
Yeah, I guess I can't get inside.
是的，我想我进不去。
It's just going to get the content on screen.
它只是将内容显示在屏幕上。
What the fuck did.
他妈的做了什么。
Yeah, I'm recording this for this for my YouTube.
是的，我正在为我的 YouTube 录制这个。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Could you walk you, please?
请你带你走好吗？
As soon as I get stronger during that new phase, all they told me in.
一旦我在那个新阶段变得更强壮，他们告诉我的一切。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Hey, what's up, bitch?
嘿，怎么了，婊子？
If you really want to, I keep you informed.
如果你真的想，我会随时通知你。
Consent
同意
Oh, shit. Huh?
妈的。 嗯？
Oh, my God. Oh, oh.
我的天啊。 哦，哦。
Oh, my God. You're going in.
我的天啊。 你要进去了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I can't fight
我无法战斗
oh, my God, dude, I'm fucking in love.
哦，天哪，伙计，我他妈的恋爱了。
What are you doing? You're getting beat up myself.
你在做什么？ 你自己被揍了。
I came to beat up my black bag, faggot.
我来打我的黑包，基佬。
Oh, well, of course.
哦，当然。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow. Jim.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔」 吉姆。
Oh, my God. You got the money.
我的天啊。 你拿到钱了。
I just want the nut crusher oh.
我只想要坚果粉碎机哦。
That wasn't my box. Track my nuts right now.
那不是我的盒子。 立即追踪我的坚果。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔」
Holy shit. You're so dreads
天啊。 你太害怕了，他们中的一些人哇。
My moves. Are so play.
我的动作。 都这么玩。
I'm not just.
我不只是。
I'm a seasoned veteran.
我是一个经验丰富的老手。
You killed someone. That makes sense.
你杀了人。 这就说得通了。
Yeah. Oh.
是的。 哦。
Oh, right.
啊对。
Shot the left jab oh.
射左刺哦。
I mean, it's all for Theft Auto.
我的意思是，这一切都是为了盗窃汽车。
Oh. Yeah.
哦。 是的。
All right, just imagine the muscle car.
好吧，想象一下肌肉车。
Of the car.
车的。
Bomb, bomb?
炸弹，炸弹？
I fucking hate cars. Fuck you. Fuck you.
我他妈的讨厌汽车。 去你的。 去你的。
What blow it.
吹什么。
Just imagine as a car because you commit.
想象成一辆车，因为你承诺。
Grand Theft Auto.
侠盗猎车手。
Yeah.
是的。
Last stop.
终点站。
Order.
命令。
Break it up before I put you all in solitary.
在我把你们都单独关起来之前分手吧。
Oh, God, please. No, that's actually fake.
哦，上帝，请。 不，这实际上是假的。
Celebrate your back.
庆祝你的背部。
It's when they put you in those rooms and restrained you so you can't move.
就是当他们把你放在那些房间里并限制你让你不能移动的时候。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
With me. OK.
与我一起。 好的。
That's kind of kinky.
这有点古怪。
Stop that.
停下。
It's like sensory deprivation.
这就像感官剥夺。
OK, maybe you would like that.
好吧，也许你会喜欢。
I feel like I'm, like, bondage.
我觉得我，就像，束缚。
I mean, you're not wrong, Mysta.
我的意思是，你没有错，Mysta。
But.
但。
I don't.
我不。
I don't think anybody's going to be, like,
我不认为任何人会在整个过程中像挠你的蛋蛋或者像挤压你的乳头一样。
You're just going to be. Oh, no.
你将成为。 不好了。
Going to happen when I get what I.
当我得到我想要的东西时就会发生。
Got all day.
得了一整天。
All right, you're saying that, like, it happens often.
好吧，你是说，就像，它经常发生。
Next.
下一个。
Where are you, huh?
你在哪里，嗯？
Wow. You're in the cafeteria.
哇。 你在自助餐厅。
Yeah. Hey, there I am.
是的。 嘿，我来了。
Are you going to sit with me?
你要和我坐在一起吗？
Yeah. Yeah. Tell me I am friends.
是的。 是的。 告诉我我是朋友。
You're bitch.
你是婊子。
You're my friends. You go find a place of your own.
你们是我的朋友。 你去找一个属于自己的地方。
What the fuck do you mean you have friends?
你他妈有朋友是什么意思？
We have. Friends.
我们有。 朋友们。
I mean, OK, look. Look over here. Look over here.
我的意思是，好吧，看。 看这里。 看这里。
Callaway free.
卡拉威免费。
Free seat.
免费座位。
I want to eat.
我想吃。
Hey, is someone talking?
嘿，有人在说话吗？
No. Oh, my fucking God. Here.
不，哦，我的天哪。 这里。
Anyone? Get out the way, man.
任何人？ 滚开，伙计。
Me neither.
我也不。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Show them force.
向他们展示力量。
Don't fuck with me when I'm hungry, OK?
我饿的时候别跟我操，好吗？
We got a tough guy over here.
我们这里有个硬汉。
I'm just eating and drinking it.
我只是吃喝而已。
All right, what are you going to do about it?
好吧，你打算怎么办？
Know what?
知道什么？
San Jose. Oh, my God. Oh, shit, man.
圣荷西。 我的天啊。 哦，该死的，伙计。
Relax, OK?
放松，好吗？
Go fuck.
去他妈的。
Eat this is some good beans.
吃这个是一些好豆子。
That's my fault, motherfucker.
那是我的错，混蛋。
He's sick.
他病了。
So sorry. It's not talking to me.
非常抱歉。 它不是在跟我说话。
Why am I walking like this?
我为什么要这样走路？
What the fuck is going on?
到底是怎么回事？
Yeah, I think. I think. All right.
是的，我想。 我认为。 好的。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Just off. For that.
刚下。 为了那个原因。
OK, got it. Yeah.
好的，我知道了。 是的。
Get lost.
迷路。
You think this is get lost, right?
你认为这是迷路，对吧？
Hey, you hear that call?
嘿，你听到那个电话了吗？
Oh, my fucking God. Really? Dave, ready?
哦，我的他妈的上帝。 真的吗？ 戴夫，准备好了吗？
To wait. A second.
等待。 一秒。
Wait a second.
等一下。
No, this ain't cool. Oh.
不，这不酷。 哦。
Oh, my fucking God.
哦，我的他妈的上帝。
It was. Shot.
它是。 射击。
I got involved.
我参与了。
All these made me fucking jump.
这一切都让我他妈的跳了起来。
Oh, my God. Slade.
我的天啊。 斯莱德。
You killed him.
你杀了他。
Oh, no, no.
哦，不，不。
I got to step down. I just killed that guy. What the fuck?
我得下台。 我刚刚杀了那个人。 什么鬼？
Oh, he's alive.
哦，他还活着。
No. Oh, no.
不，哦，不。
Fuck her.
操她。
I'll kill you.
我会杀了你。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
See, that's our lives.
看，这就是我们的生活。
That your car? You OK?
那是你的车？ 你还好吗？
Come on, scumbag. OK,
来吧，渣男。 好的，
we're just going to.
我们只是要去。
Throw shit at some fucking hell. What?
把屎扔到他妈的地狱里。 什么？
He literally was times-I was.
他确实是时代——我是。
That was like a metal get sort of mean.
这就像金属变得有点意思。
That's what all fuck it is is so we don't know what she did.
他妈的就是这样，所以我们不知道她做了什么。
Oh, I just use my special technique.
哦，我只是使用我的特殊技术。
From both.
从两者。
Sides.
双方。
But, you know, that's gonna
但是，你知道，那会
oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
No, you better not say.
不，你最好不要说。
Oh, my God, I'm so scared. Christ.
哦，天哪，我好害怕。 基督。
Russ, that wasn't
拉斯，那不是一个很热，很有趣的流氓。 嘿。
Don't kill me.
不要杀我。
I'm sorry
对不起
I didn't see the next chapter.
没看到下一章
Please.
请。
Oh, God. Yeah. Come on. God.
天啊。 是的。 来吧。 上帝。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔噢
Oh, my God. He actually killed him.
我的天啊。 他真的杀了他。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, yes. Oh.
哦是的。 哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
That could have been you.
那可能是你。
Yeah, I thought you.
是的，我以为你。
I thought I'm strong. Mm.
我以为我很坚强。
E Well.
E 嗯。
You've been built to deal worse.
你生来就是为了应对更糟的事情。
He's not a car.
他不是汽车。
Oh. And now I get the hotness.
哦。 现在我得到了热度。
Shit. Easy.
拉屎。 简单的。
I hate those things.
我讨厌那些东西。
80, baby.
80，宝贝。
Worse things to worry about in here.
更糟糕的事情要担心在这里。
See this?
看到这个了吗？
You don't get this.
你没有得到这个。
What? You're getting injected.
什么？ 你被注射了。
I'll get injected. Oh.
我会被注射。 哦。
No. I get touched by a hot nurse.
不，我被一个热辣的护士感动了。
All right, just lay down and rest for a while.
好吧，躺下休息一会儿。
Mm. Well, yeah. Nice
嗯。 嗯，是的。 好的
oh, look, I'm checking out.
哦，看，我正在检查。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I think you you're oh.
我觉得你是哦。
Screwdrivers. Oh.
螺丝刀。 哦。
I was on my way.
我正在路上。
I got is. You.
我得到的是。 你。
It's him. I got fucked. Up. I'm Leah.
是他。 我被操了。 向上。 我是利亚。
Vincent.
文森特。
Listen, thanks vincent.
听着，谢谢文森特。
I'm Vincent.
我是文森特。
You're Vincent, and I'm Leo.
你是文森特，我是里奥。
I mean it, man.
我的意思是，伙计。
What's your beef with that guy anyway?
反正你和那个人有什么关系？
Let's just say it's a long story, but don't worry, OK?
说来话长，但别担心，好吗？
He's out of the picture now. All I a.
他现在已经不在了。 所有我一个。
He was engaged.
他订婚了。
Pansies. I need what's that exactly?
三色紫罗兰。 我需要那到底是什么？
You're very reserved right now.
你现在很保守。
You got a cover all over you.
你全身都被遮盖了。
I just need you to watch my back. Well, I get it.
我只需要你看着我的背影。 嗯，我明白了。
That's all.
就这些。
Your poses is very
你的姿势很
provocative thing.
挑衅的事情。
I'm not interested.
我没兴趣。
OK, I'll do it myself. Well, all right.
好的，我会自己做。 好吧，好吧。
Well, you can't just walk out of here.
好吧，你不能就这么离开这里。
Of course I can.
当然，我可以。
We're going to both end up in the hall.
我们都将在大厅结束。
Well, I don't have a choice.
好吧，我别无选择。
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
You know, we finally get to play with each.
你知道，我们终于可以和每个人一起玩了。
Other in court.
其他在法庭上。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
OK, teamwork. Keep your eye sharp.
好的，团队合作。 保持眼睛敏锐。
Yeah. All right, you better fuck this up.
是的。 好吧，你最好把它搞砸。
I don't know what I have to say. What are you going to.
我不知道我要说什么。 你要干什么。
You better not fuck it up.
你最好别搞砸了。
I have never fucked up anything in my life.
我这辈子从来没有搞砸过任何事情。
Assist skill.
辅助技能。
Hold on. Wait.
坚持，稍等。 等待。
Wait a second.
等一下。
That's impressive. G
这令人印象深刻。  G
what are you doing?
你在做什么？
We have an inmate on the run, Mysta.
我们有一个犯人在逃，米斯塔。
Mysta. You ladies walked out
米斯塔。 女士们走在大家面前
all i god.
我的上帝。
All right, hold on. Wait, g.
好吧，等一下。 等等，g。
I'll distract a nurse. Just watch.
我会分散护士的注意力。 只是看。
I'll distract the nurse. How?
我会分散护士的注意力。 如何？
Get back in bed.
回到床上。
Get back in j. OK, I'm gonna call her.
回到j。 好的，我去给她打电话。
I'll call for her right
我会呼吁她的权利
and then I think you can walk away.
然后我认为你可以走开。
Uh huh.
嗯。
So now I get the nurse.
所以现在我找护士。
Fuck you.
去你的。
Oh, damn you.
哦，该死的你。
You're going for it.
你会去的。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Can I have some water?
我可以要些水吗？
Yeah, sore throat.
是的，喉咙痛。
Can I have some water.
我可以要些水吗。
Ways.
方法。
Next move. Ooh.
下一步行动。 哦。
What the fuck are you doing?
你他妈在做什么？
All right.
好的。
Where do I go?
我要去哪？
I don't know. That's up to you, buddy.
我不知道。 这取决于你，伙计。
I'm here. I'm doing my job. You do your job.
我在这里。 我在做我的工作。 你做你的工作。
There's a guy here.
这里有一个人。
He's got
他得到了
I hope I'm not bothering you.
我希望我没有打扰你。
Cisco. It's my job.
思科。 这是我的工作。
Do, do, do.
做，做，做。
Do it, do it, do it. Dude, this is all you.
做，做，做。 伙计，这就是你的全部。
This is literally all you right now.
这就是你现在的全部。
Oh, my God. Oh, shit.
我的天啊。 妈的。
I thought you fucked up, OK?
我以为你搞砸了，好吗？
What do I do?
我该怎么办？
I think it is a decent.
我认为这是一个体面的。
Thing that you end up working in a prison.
你最终在监狱里工作的事情。
Can you do anything, like bang on a window or something?
你能做任何事吗，比如敲窗户什么的？
I don't know how to bang on the window. Oh, wait, hold on.
我不知道怎么敲窗户。 哦，等等，等等。
Oh, you're right. E
哦，你是对的。 乙
it's, like, right behind you.
它就在你身后。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
I dropped the bomb. No.
我扔了炸弹。 不。
You look a bit pale.
你看起来有点苍白。
Something wrong?
有问题？
Well, I'll knock on it after, ok? OK.
好吧，我会在之后敲它，好吗？ 好的。
After she looks away, because you can't be looking at me, I think.
在她移开视线之后，我想，因为你不能看着我。
Oh, all right.
哦那好吧。
I'll just sit here.
我就坐在这里。
Ok? Go, go, go, go, go, go.
好的？ 走，走，走，走，走，走。
Let me go. Let me go.
让我走。 让我走。
Oh, oh, oh, oh, ooh.
噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God. You are so lucky.
我的天啊。 你太幸运了。
You are so lucky. What was that?
你太幸运了。 那是什么？
What was that timing?
那是什么时间？
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Oh, where's he going?
哦，他要去哪里？
Oh, something else.
哦，别的东西。
That is fine right now.
现在很好。
I just got to be fast.
我只得快点。
Yeah, I am really hungry.
是的，我真的很饿。
Hurry back. Hurry back. Go.
快回来。 快回来。 去。
Guys.
伙计们。
In the way
在路上
how does she not see me?
她怎么看不到我？
I don't know. Oh, she's still around. Please
我不知道。 哦，她还在。 请
you were just served.
你刚刚被送达。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Give me more. Food.
给我多一点。 食物。
That was disgusting.
那太恶心了。
That was a tiny portion e
那是一小部分，加油。 我该怎么办？
Get ready to go. To bed.
准备出发。 睡觉。
That was a. Snack.
那是一个。 小吃。
Sorry. That's awfully nice.
对不起。 这真是太好了。
Let's go. See this. This is fun.
我们走吧。 看到这个。 这很好玩。
We did. She's gone.
我们做到了。 她走了。
It's gone.
它不见了。
She's a ghost.
她是个鬼。
She's not even real dead.
她甚至还没有真正死去。
That was only the first collaboration
那只是第一次合作，你直接走到项链前面。
I couldn't believe what I saw.
我简直不敢相信我所看到的。
Hey, what are you up to? Nothing.
嘿，你在干什么？ 没有。
Nothing. Bitch.
没有。 婊子。
You know, why are the windows open? Oh.
你知道，为什么窗户是开着的？ 哦。
Oh, they can run away anyways.
哦，反正他们可以逃跑。
But they could jump out.
但他们可以跳出来。
They could, but then everything's fenced up around the prison.
他们可以，但是监狱周围的一切都被围起来了。
Oh, yeah?
哦耶？
Why do we need that for?
为什么我们需要它？
It's like a. To like is.
它就像一个。 喜欢就是。
A chisel. Yeah, it's a chisel.
一个凿子。 是的，它是一把凿子。
Basketball
篮球
OK. Sitting on a bench.
好的。 坐在长凳上。
Yeah.
是的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
My note loser for the nerd symbiotically nerds.
我对于书呆子共生书呆子的笔记失败者。
Oh, look who's here.
哦，看看谁在这里。
Look at the other night. He's lonely.
看看另一个晚上。 他很孤独。
I'm Val. I'm here to keep you company.
我是瓦尔。 我是来陪你的。
I felt so bad for you out of the kindness of my heart.
出于我内心的善良，我为你感到难过。
I'm coming here to give you companionship.
我来这里是为了给你陪伴。
Uh, huh, uh huh.
嗯嗯嗯嗯。
Because you're fucking lonely. I'm lonely.
因为你他妈太寂寞了。 我很寂寞。
I don't need. You.
我不需要。 你。
I was fine. Being on my own. You surprised me.
我很好。 独自一人。 你让我吃惊。
See my.
见我的。
Beard? Look at my beard.
胡须？ 看我的胡子。
Come on. Your beard. Is ugly.
来吧。 你的胡子。 很丑。
Oh, you see, that knows about you.
哦，你看，那知道你。
You know.
你知道。
You know what? I'm going to make me a kiss your.
你知道吗？ 我要让我吻你。
Face sitting on that little sitting on big noses.
脸坐在那个小鼻子上。
You know why? Why? You fucking. Know why.
你知道为什么？ 为什么？ 你他妈 知道为什么。
Look,
看，
I appreciate what you did back there, but you need to back off.
我很感激你在那里所做的，但你需要退后。
I need to back off. I'm trying to be nice.
我需要退后。 我正在努力表现得很好。
I'm sure a way for. Me to bust out of here.
我肯定有办法。 我要离开这里。
But I need to get out of here, too.
但我也需要离开这里。
How about I bust on your face?
我打你的脸怎么样？
Not my problem.
不是我的问题。
Just offering my help here.
只是在这里提供我的帮助。
You know what? I don't need your help. I can handle myself.
你知道吗？ 我不需要你的帮助。 我可以自己处理。
Yeah, Dan, like you did in the infirmary back there.
是的，丹，就像你在后面的医务室做的那样。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
I'm not.
我不是。
Listen, I'm pretty much in on this.
听着，我对此非常感兴趣。
Just trying to make you understand that you could really use my help
只是想让你明白你真的可以使用我的帮助
i like my man. I can handle myself.
我喜欢我的男人。 我可以自己处理。
Oh, yeah. That's very cute.
哦耶。 那很可爱。
Yeah. What about harvey? That.
是的。 哈维呢？ 那。
Oh, Harvey,
哦，哈维，
the fuck do you know about Harvey?
你他妈的知道哈维吗？
Who you been talking to?
你跟谁说话？
The walls are standing here.
墙壁就在这里。
Let's supposed to believe that.
让我们相信这一点。
Let's just.
让我们只是。
You and me have something in common.
你和我有共同点。
We both want him dead.
我们都希望他死。
So you like me being pitting you against
所以你喜欢我让你靠在电锯指节上吗？ 有点像
How about me, man? Do that again.
我呢，伙计？ 再做一次。
Maybe not but I want to.
也许不是，但我想。
Do you want, like, coffee dog?
你想要，比如，咖啡狗吗？
I've always wanted to be done something with that software.
我一直想用那个软件做点什么。
I'm going after.
我要追。
If you covered on me, can I like to call you on this?
如果你覆盖我，我可以打电话给你吗？
Damn sure.
该死的确定。
Chaz.
查兹。
Oh, good.
哦，很好。
So fucking snarky.
太他妈刻薄了。
Why oh.
为什么哦。
My goodness.
我的天啊。
I can't keep my eyes off you, babe.
我不能让我的眼睛从你身上移开，宝贝。
OK, maybe you can do that if you put one finger in the, you know.
好吧，如果你把一根手指放进去，也许你可以做到这一点，你知道的。
Ass? All right.
屁股？ 好的。
Yeah, right. Do you have a deal?
是的，对。 你有交易吗？
One finger in the ass, ok?
一根手指插在屁股上，好吗？
Yeah.
是的。
You can use the other ones for the for your special technique.
您可以将其他的用于您的特殊技术。
Can I promise you. Your ninja tsu.
我能答应你吗。 你的忍者tsu。
Ahh. Alone in my room?
啊。 一个人在我的房间里？
I'm in the other one right now.
我现在在另一个。
Are you?
你是？
Oh, hey.
噢！嗨。
I hear someone jerking .
我听到有人在抽搐。
You want to jerk with me?
你想和我混蛋吗？
Yeah, you're finished.
是的，你已经完成了。
Let's jerk together, bro.
让我们一起混蛋，兄弟。
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
是啊是啊。 是的。
It's my plan.
这是我的计划。
And I decide.
我决定。
Oh, and you're being you want to be you. I take Tom.
哦，你正在成为你想成为的你。 我带汤姆。
I want to be in control.
我想掌控一切。
Whatever you say.
不管你说什么。
I mean it, man. Follow the story.
我的意思是，伙计。 跟随故事。
To the beat. Well, Sam.
到节拍。 嗯，山姆。
You didn't know were taking jerky.
你不知道吃肉干。
Not seriously.
不认真。
You know, sure enough.
你知道，果然。
Oh, all right.
哦那好吧。
Oh, we did.
哦，我们做到了。
Do we beat the game?
我们赢了比赛吗？
Oh, my God. Joe.
我的天啊。 乔。
Thanks for joining.
感谢您的加入。
Everyone is back on by.
每个人都回来了。
I'll see you guys tomorrow for the next stream.
明天下一场直播见。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Oh, look at that.
哦，看那个。
See, we're in the helicopter.
看，我们在直升机上。
You didn't really have an escape plan, did you?
你真的没有逃跑计划，是吗？
Spoilers.
剧透。
Of course I did.
我当然做了。
You had an idea. I'll give you that.
你有个主意。 我会给你那个。
I got you out today.
我今天让你出去了。
What do you mean, you got all this?
你什么意思，你得到了这一切？
We got spoilers.
我们有剧透。
Yeah, well, yeah, yeah, sure.
是的，是的，是的，是的，当然。
But if it wasn't for me, you'd still be in there.
但如果不是因为我，你还会在那里。
Don't forget, I saved your ass.
别忘了，我救了你的屁股。
Twice.
两次。
I don't know about that.
我不知道。
Saving my ass part, but I'll give you this.
保存我的屁股，但我会给你这个。
It did help out
它确实有帮助
a little bit.
一点点。
And I saw us twice.
我见过我们两次。
That's fine.
没事儿。
Now. Whistles
现在。 口哨
now this.
现在这个。
Is you.
是你。
Ever, like, watch what comes out of your mouth?
曾经，比如，看看你嘴里说了什么？
Sometimes
有时
think you're.
认为你是。
What does that mean?
这意味着什么？
Is that saying, guys, is this a British thing?
那是说，伙计们，这是英国的事情吗？
Nah, I saw.
呐，我看到了。
I mean, you know, you see stretched out.
我的意思是，你知道，你看到了伸展。
Gapping. So I'm going, OK, I'm
差距。 所以我要去，好吧，我在
in. I didn't need that visual.
我不需要那种视觉效果。
I really didn't need that fucking visual.
我真的不需要那种该死的视觉效果。
You did
你做了
OK, get sub is this day.
好的，今天得到子。
Mysta. Mysta.
米斯塔。 米斯塔。
Yes, yes, yes, yes. That's me.
是的，是的，是的，是的。 那是我。
Fred. Sup?
弗雷德。 苏？
Oh, good. Fred, what do you want?
哦，很好。 弗雷德，你想要什么？
It's Fred.
是弗雷德。
You know, I was thinking of the exact same. Do
你知道，我的想法完全一样。 做
sir we could figure something out, right?
先生，我们可以想办法，对吧？
Because you're a fucking Kramer. A Muslim.
因为你是一个他妈的克莱默。 一个穆斯林。
What are you talking.
你在说什么。
You're older than me.
你比我大。
Probably doesn't make you one.
可能不会让你成为一个。
But that's not true.
但事实并非如此。
Yo, hurry up.
哟，快点。
We don't have all day.
我们没有一整天。
I am totally 18. Hey.
我完全 18 岁。嘿。
All right. They're orderly. Yeah.
好的。 他们井然有序。 是的。
I know. All right.
我知道。 好的。
What are we doing now? We got. We got to sweep.
我们现在在做什么？ 我们有。 我们要扫地。
We got to get the chisel. Gets chisel.
我们必须得到凿子。 得到凿子。
Well, the chisel was up there, so you
好吧，凿子在上面，所以你
probably just, like.
可能只是，喜欢。
Just grab it. Can we just grab it?
抓住它。 我们可以抓住它吗？
What the l.
什么l。
You're the guy who knows how to get things around here.
你是知道如何在这里解决问题的人。
Uh, can I just climb.
呃，我可以爬吗？
You a way out of.
你有出路。
Here? Oh, you know,
这里？ 哦，你知道的，回到你那个有趣的家伙，巴基。
We've got to get rid of him eventually. Yeah, he did.
我们最终必须摆脱他。 是的，他做到了。
He pushed you.
他推你。
Let me put you on.
让我给你戴上。
you know what's up?
你知道怎么了？
you better get used to this fucking bitch, because there's no way out, Powell.
你最好习惯这个该死的婊子，因为没有出路，鲍威尔。
At least not alive.
至少没有活着。
He's mean. OK?
他很卑鄙。 好的？
You know, my chat keeps calling me 81.
你知道，我的聊天一直叫我 81。
I'm a mad Madge slob.
我是一个疯狂的Madge slob。
This is why I have. To do slob on me.
这就是为什么我有。 对我做邋遢。
Now break
现在休息
oh. Oh, my God.
哦。 我的天啊。
You broke in my room. Just broke.
你闯进了我的房间。 刚刚破了。
Oh, don't just stand there. Get a new one.
哦，不要只是站在那里。 换一个新的。
All right, smart.
好吧，聪明。
Oh, is he going to be suspicious of you if you break yours or not?
哦，如果你打破你的，他会怀疑你吗？
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I don't think I can be. Can I totters?
我不认为我可以。 我可以踉踉跄跄吗？
I'm just mopping. Around.
我只是在拖地。 大约。
It looks like you missed a spot. I got stuff.
看起来你错过了一个地方。 我有东西。
Yeah.
是的。
Seems like I had one else. We got here.
好像我还有一个。 我们去那里。
I was looking out and I, like.
我正在向外看，我喜欢。
Open going up here.
打开这里。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
It's my first time.
这是我的第一次。
I'm not sure if I'm liking it, but I've done worse.
我不确定我是否喜欢它，但我做得更糟。
Are you kidding me?
你在跟我开玩笑吗？
This is the best job you get.
这是你得到的最好的工作。
The view, the smell from the tar smell.
从焦油味的看法，气味。
Oh, it's perfect.
哦，它是完美的。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Interruptive coming to that
打扰了
yeah. I don't want that.
是的。 我不要那个。
I don't think talking to these guys is going to get me anything.
我不认为与这些人交谈会给我带来任何好处。
OK, I got to go get a new broom. Did you break your broom? Yeah.
好吧，我得去买一把新扫帚了。 你把扫帚弄坏了吗？ 是的。
How about you go break your body and join me?
你去打破你的身体并加入我怎么样？
I can't break mine.
我不能打破我的。
You can't break it? my bro.
你不能打破它吗？ 哥们。
Look, stay here, all right? Ow!
听着，待在这里，好吗？ 哦！
Oh! Oh!
哦！ 哦！
Come here, come here, come here.
过来，过来，过来。
Get over here to drag this over here.
过来把这个拖过来。
Here's what's going to have to stay here.
这就是必须留在这里的东西。
Yes, I'm going to start out.
是的，我要开始了。
I've got to go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
我必须走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走。
Oh, you go. Oh, I go.
哦，你去。 哦，我去。
What's I go?
我去干什么？
I think that's a waitress.
我认为那是一个女服务员。
You go. OK, yeah, that makes more sense.
你去。 好的，是的，这更有意义。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
Again, I'm going to come back in here.
再次，我将回到这里。
I'm going to be here.
我会在这里。
Like, oh, holy shit.
就像，哦，天哪。
Looking around, dude, you took so long to come here.
环顾四周，伙计，你花了这么长时间才来到这里。
Keep it up, boys.
坚持下去，孩子们。
We don't have all day now. Get back to work.
我们现在没有一整天。 回去工作。
Yeah, I'm going up.
是的，我要上去。
I'm going. Oh, yeah, yeah.
我要去。 哦，是的，是的。
Easy peasy, lemon squeezy.
简单的豌豆，柠檬汁。
Give me the chisel.
把凿子给我。
The how the fuck are you gonna get back down.
你他妈的要怎么回去。
By walking in here?
走进这里？
Well, if I break my broom again, can't see that
好吧，如果我再次打破我的扫帚，看不到那个
all right, hold on, hold on.
好吧，等一下，等一下。
Give me a second.
你稍等一会儿。
Fuck you, bitch.
去你妈的，婊子。
Don't look at him. He's going to notice you heard.
不要看他。 他会注意到你听到的。
Not alone.
不是一个人。
You're going to distract them.
你会分散他们的注意力。
And distract him.
并分散他的注意力。
I got a distraction.
我分心了。
What do you want me to do?
你想要我做什么？
Something nice. Touch him.
不错的东西。 抚摸他。
Touch him.
抚摸他。
Where is this guy? Oh, this guy. Yeah, this guy.
这个人在哪里？ 哦，这家伙。 是的，这个人。
Oh, e e e.
哦，e e e。
Hey, can I ask you something?
嘿，我能问你一件事吗？
What's up?
怎么了？
Being a prison guard, almost like being in prison.
作为一名狱警，几乎就像在监狱里一样。
I mean, you're in here all the time with us.
我的意思是，你一直和我们在一起。
Are you being a smartass?
你是个聪明人吗？
I mean. Am I being a smartass?
我是说。 我是个聪明人吗？
What's with the attitude?
态度如何？
Just making conversation, man.
只是聊天，伙计。
I'm just trying to. Go in, and I'm going in here.
我只是想。 进去，我就进去。
And you said I wanted one. Oh, I'm inside.
你说我想要一个。 哦，我在里面。
Leave you alone. Bring Chisel to Fred.
让你一个人呆着。 把凿子带给弗雷德。
Whose pride is locked.
谁的骄傲被锁住了。
Oh, that guy's right. Table, hon.
哦，那家伙是对的。 表，亲爱的。
Vincent, help you.
文森特，帮你。
Where's the door?
门在哪里？
Where's your door?
你的门在哪里？
Yeah. Where is that? It's that one.
是的。 哪里是？ 就是那个。
The one on the right.
右边那个。
Of course, it's.
当然，是的。
Where are you, an idiot?
你在哪里，白痴？
No, not me.
不，不是我。
I'm literally.
我是字面上的。
I'm legitimately confused.
我有理由感到困惑。
Where's the door? Go back this one.
门在哪里？ 回去这个。
Back, back, back, back, back.
回来，回来，回来，回来，回来。
Out my.
出我的。
There. There's a door right there.
那里。 那里有一扇门。
The door on the right where
右边的门在哪里
there's no door mister, what are you talking about?
没有门先生，你在说什么？
I don't see a fucking door.
我没有看到他妈的门。
Oh, my God. Shit.
我的天啊。 拉屎。
Shoto, I'm going to fucking kill you.
肖战，我他妈要杀了你。
You can't.
你不能。
You can't say this.
你不能这么说。
I don't know where the doors there's a door right here.
我不知道门在哪里，这里有一扇门。
Let me check the door. Here's locked.
让我看看门。 这里被锁定了。
Mop, mop. Mop. Go back to the mop.
拖把，拖把。 拖把。 回到拖把上。
Just looking around.
只是随便看看。
Along, we get back to work.
一路走来，我们回去工作。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Holy shit. OK, see the door?
天啊。 好的，看到门了吗？
You see you through the window.
你透过窗户看到你。
Look where this one.
看看这个在哪里。
Yeah, you're not in there.
是的，你不在里面。
Look, you're not there.
看，你不在。
You must stop right there you are.
你必须停在那里。
Holy. So oh, wow.
圣。 所以哦，哇。
There's a door right here.
这里有一扇门。
Right away.
马上。
I looked over to your screen.
我看着你的屏幕。
I saw my big fucking face on the window.
我在窗户上看到了我他妈的大脸。
I know where you right.
我知道你在哪里。
Oh, my God, you're right. There is the door.
哦，我的上帝，你是对的。 有门。
We didn't see the door there.
我们没有看到那里的门。
I'm so sorry. Jesus Christ.
我很抱歉。 耶稣基督。
You OK?
你还好吗？
So, Don, sorry.
所以，唐，对不起。
Get rid of the fuck out of here.
把他妈的从这里赶出去。
I got to give Fred.
我必须给弗雷德。
Oh, tragic.
哦，悲剧。
Have this oh,
有这个哦，
my God.
我的上帝。
Do you see it?
你看到了吗？
It blended in with the fucking walls.
它与他妈的墙壁融为一体。
Thought I'm.
以为我是
Going to not telling your tail on.
不会告诉你的尾巴。
Oh, man. Wouldn't you like to do that?
天啊。 你不想那样做吗？
I know it's a fucking flop plug.
我知道这是一个他妈的翻牌插头。
It's not a plug.
它不是插头。
You can't touch.
你不能碰。
This.
这。
It's a motorised bump flow.
这是一个机动的颠簸流。
That's why he's breathing. A little.
这就是他呼吸的原因。 一点。
Green.
绿。
Or maybe. Maybe it is. Maybe it is.
或许。 也许是的。 也许是的。
And I connect to it like, you.
我像你一样连接到它。
Know, you can't.
知道，你不能。
Connect to.
连接至。
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
Where's your tail, huh?
你的尾巴在哪里，嗯？
My tail?
我的尾巴？
Yeah. Where's your tail?
是的。 你的尾巴在哪里？
I don't have it in
我没有
little bitch.
小婊子。
I didn't even pay attention to what the fuck is going on now.
我什至没有注意他妈的现在发生了什么。
You were. I knocked.
你之前是。 我敲了敲。
You knocked.
你敲门了。
That got to knock back.
那必须击退。
I can look left.
我可以向左看。
And right.
没错。
Hi, babe.
嗨，宝贝。
Oh, hey there,
哦，嘿那里，
Katie.
凯蒂。
Nothing much.
没什么。
Just chillin.
只是冷静。
Why are you looking at me?
你为什么看着我？
I see. Shining his light in your face. Shiny.
我懂了。 将他的光芒照在你的脸上。 闪亮的。
Oh, I'm distracting. Distracting from what?
哦，我分心了。 分心什么？
You have a book is tomorrow visiting.
你有一本书明天要拜访。
They can't wait for sheets.
他们等不及要床单了。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Freezing could I have some extra sheets?
冷冻 我可以多加几张床单吗？
Oh, no, it's not going to happen.
哦，不，这不会发生。
I yeah.
我是的。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Shut that right now.
立即关闭它。
You are so. Bad.
你太。 坏的。
What do you mean? I'm so bad.
你什么意思？ 我是如此糟糕。
I didn't know what to ask.
我不知道该问什么。
There you are. So interesting.
你在这。 很有趣。
She literally just
她实际上只是从字面上要求额外的床单，他不想给我。
He's an asshole. Hurry up. Just hurry up.
他是个混蛋。 赶快。 快点吧。
You guys do your. Thing like I'm doing.
你们做你的。 像我正在做的事情。
I'm doing. Don't do that.
我在做。 不要那样做。
Fuck. Would I ask him?
他妈的。 我会问他吗？
What do I ask him?
我问他什么？
What's
什么是
what? Excuse me.
什么？ 打扰一下。
What? What are you doing?
什么？ 你在做什么？
What? Visiting day.
什么？ 参观日。
Do you have a book on visiting this tomorrow?
你有关于明天参观这里的书吗？
Visiting day?
参观日？
No. You sure?
不，你确定？
Yeah. Go to sleep.
是的。 去睡觉。
Catholic has all kinds of cancelled.
天主教有各种取消。
I can't get in touch. Ed.
我联系不上。 埃德。
Oh, hello.
哦你好。
Nothing sexy going on here.
这里没有什么性感的。
It's nothing.
这没什么。
Man. I'm not doing. This to busting my balls.
男人。 我没有做。 这是为了破坏我的蛋蛋。
I shut those job. All right,
我关闭了那些工作。 好的，
go back.
回去。
OK? Yeah, yeah, yeah. You do your thing. Do your thing.
好的？ 耶耶耶。 你做你的事。 做你的事。
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, come back.
快点，快点，快点，回来。
Somebody's got to come back.
总得有人回来。
But no, he left you another guard.
但是不，他给你留了另一个守卫。
Come down here. OK?
下来这里。 好的？
Not the coast is clear.
不是海岸是清楚的。
Ooh. What are you doing over there?
哦。 你在那边做什么？
Lead doing step. Right.
领导做一步。 对。
What are you doing? Step-bro.
你在做什么？ 继兄弟。
I'm coming.
我来了。
He's got leg.
他有腿。
He's coming out.
他要出来了。
Come down this way to it.
沿着这条路下来。
OK, I'll distract him.
好的，我会分散他的注意力。
I'll be.
我将要。
Has a go in. So.
进去了。所以。
When I look at my ass.
当我看着我的屁股。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I'll do a special dance just for you.
我会为你跳一段特别的舞蹈。
He's not interested. You lost his attention, fucker.
他不感兴趣。 你失去了他的注意力，混蛋。
Good OK, I'll go talk to him.
好的好的，我去和他谈谈。
But I stopped him now. OK, go to sleep.
但我现在阻止了他。 好了，去睡觉吧。
All right.
好的。
All right. All down. Hello.
好的。 都下来了。 你好。
I think something going on hit.
我认为发生了什么事。
Pull on stop.
拉停。
Talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk.
说话，说话，说话，说话，说话，说话，说话。
OK, ok, ok. OK.
好好好。 好的。
I'll just distract him whole. My God.
我只会分散他的注意力。 我的上帝。
I can't sleep with him. They cold.
我不能和他睡觉。 他们冷。
They can't sleep cold.
他们睡不着冷。
No notes.
没有注释。
Hello. Nice.
你好。 好的。
Yeah, I'm just against cool. Nothing going on here.
是的，我只是反对酷。 这里什么都没有。
Yeah, yeah, yeah. She time.
耶耶耶。 她时间。
I do not even thank.
我什至不感谢。
You, fucking asshole.
你个混蛋
You are such a some. Somebody is literally coming right now.
你就是这样一个人。 现在有人真的要来了。
He's coming on your ass.
他正在攻击你。
He's coming in your eyes.
他正在进入你的眼中。
Oh, hey, baby.
哦，嘿，宝贝。
Give him a. Different dance this time.
给他一个。 这次不一样的舞蹈。
Look, I'll show you my armpits.
看，我会告诉你我的腋窝。
I don't chase.
我不追。
Can I see.
我可以看吗。
OK? No.
好的？ 不。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Just wages, wages.
只是工资，工资。
Wages on my way.
工资在路上。
Just doing my head first.
只是先做我的头。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Yeah. Now's your chance. Not a chance to.
是的。 现在是你的机会。 没有机会。
Go and do it. And do it.
去做吧。 并去做。
I'll distract this guy. I'll distract him.
我会分散这家伙的注意力。 我会分散他的注意力。
OK? OK. I got it.
好的？ 好的。 我得到了它。
I got it.
我得到了它。
I actually got it this time.
这次我真的明白了。
Oh, it's open.
哦，它是开放的。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh. Ah, I'm cold.
哦。 啊，我冷。
You need to do it.
你需要这样做。
Could I have some extra sheets?
我可以要一些额外的床单吗？
No, no, no, no, no. You guys
不，不，不，不，不，不。 你们没关系。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I want sleep.
我想睡觉。
Right in front of the guard.
就在守卫面前。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
Give it to me. Give it to me now. Give it to me now.
把它给我。 现在把它给我。 现在把它给我。
No one's looking.
没有人在看。
No one's looking. Oh.
没有人在看。 哦。
Ok. OK.
行。 好的。
Now it's your turn.
现在轮到你了。
Not your it's here, ok?
不是你的，它在这里，好吗？
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh, hold on.
哦，等一下。
Give me sanctions or
给我制裁或任何人来。
By coming in.
通过进来。
I want one guys.
我想要一个人。
Walking over
走过
you might want to stop.
你可能想停下来。
Now. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Because it
现在。 停，停，停，停，停，停。 因为它
oh, my God. Hey.
我的天啊。 嘿。
Hey there. Huh?
嘿。 嗯？
You want on?
你要上吗？
You want to you want to sniff my butt?
你想你想闻我的屁股吗？
Well, hello, interest.
嗯，你好，兴趣。
He's not interested.
他不感兴趣。
How is.
怎么。
Anyone? I don't. Ho, ho, ho.
任何人？ 我不。 哈哈哈。
OK. I think.
好的。 我认为。
I think you two can distract this guy, though, right?
不过，我认为你们两个可以分散这个家伙的注意力，对吧？
I think so.
我认同。
You. Yeah, yeah.
你。 是啊是啊。
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. I'm
走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走。 我是
my bed is broke.
我的床坏了。
What do you want me to do about it?
你想让我怎么做？
I want you to fix it. Not my problem.
我要你修理它。 不是我的问题。
Go to sleep.
去睡觉。
All right?
好的？
OK. OK, we're clean. Holy shit.
好的。 好的，我们很干净。 天啊。
Right now.
现在。
I got guys, you know?
我有伙计，你知道吗？
I want it to work. I'm not tired.
我想让它工作。 我不累。
I can't go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
我不能走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走。
Go, go. I'm doing it. I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
走，走。 我正在做。 我在做，我在做。
You're safe. You're safe, you're safe. This is a safe day.
你是安全的。 你是安全的，你是安全的。 这是安全的一天。
You can come inside. It's good, good, good.
你可以进来。 很好，很好，很好。
He's walking away to safety.
他正在走向安全。
Yeah. Come on. It's my lucky day. Then
是的。 来吧。 这是我的幸运日。 然后
I die.
我死。
Slice. Oh, that was easy.
片。 哦，那很容易。
Anita. Oh, no.
安妮塔。 不好了。
I do need to chisel it
我确实需要凿它
you OK? Good, good.
你还好吗？ 好好。
You're good.
你很好。
OK, one guy's walking up.
好的，一个人走上来了。
I think you're fine. Still a fine.
我觉得你很好。 还是罚款。
A fine. You're fine.
罚款。 你很好。
You're fine. I'm going to risk it.
你很好。 我要去冒险。
I'm going to risk it.
我要去冒险。 我要去冒险。
I'll.
患病的。
I'll distract this guy. Huh?
我会分散这家伙的注意力。 嗯？
Hello?
你好？
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
I decided to talk to
我决定和他谈谈
I will say.
我会说。
What did you say? Nothing.
你说什么？ 没有。
You sure?
你确定？
Yeah. Now go back to bed. Oh, my God.
是的。 现在回去睡觉。 我的天啊。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
Just in time.
恰逢其时。
At least. He's very.
至少。 他很。
Clean. Oh, so clean.
干净的。 哦，好干净。
Let's wait until the lights glow.
让我们等到灯光亮起。
You know, he got me worried.
你知道，他让我很担心。
There.
那里。
There I was talking to him.
我在那里和他说话。
And you, like, extended. That's all.
而你，就像，扩展。 就这些。
All. Now we're both going to escape.
全部。 现在我们俩都要逃跑了。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
It's Night-Time. The lights are out.
现在是夜间。 灯灭了。
You come over to my cell.
你到我的牢房来。
I could actually Ready?
我真的可以准备好了吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, I'm ready.
是的，我准备好了。
We were all right.
我们没事。
We were just going to leave. Yeah, I think so.
我们正要离开。 是的，我想是的。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
A step, bro.
一步，兄弟。
I'm stuck.
我被困住了。
Oh. I'm not stuck, actually. Down
哦。 实际上，我并没有被困住。 向下
look at us.
看着我们。
Damn, this smell. Hey. Yeah, this smell.
妈的，这味道。 嘿。 对，就是这个味道。
My eyes.
我的眼睛。
Yeah. So you're acting like fucking now.
是的。 所以你现在表现得像他妈的。
Get back here.
回到这里。
Ewwww.
呜呜呜。
And for me, in that position, I didn't have a choice for the game.
对我来说，在那个位置上，我对比赛没有选择。
Wanted me to do
要我做
part of them. They came on to me.
其中一部分。 他们来找我。
Yeah. Yeah. I can't get no you're.
是的。 是的。 我不明白你是。
You're actually two. We
你实际上是两个。 我们
you can.
你可以。
You can. You can.
你可以。 你可以。
Can you? I can't. You like.
你可以吗？ 我不能。 你喜欢。
Are you
你是否试图推进你在做什么。
Oh, you want a golfer?
哦，你想要一个高尔夫球手？
So you only golfers know if. Back down here.
所以只有高尔夫球手知道。 回到这里。
Get the fuck back down here.
让他妈的回到这里。
OK, I thought you could block me for a second.
好吧，我以为你可以阻止我一秒钟。
I wanted to.
我想。
Oh, did we get free here?
哦，我们在这里得到自由了吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
You go through there, it's gonna kill you if you walk through
你穿过那里，如果你穿过它会杀了你
it's balance.
这是平衡。
How would that kill you? What do you mean? It's.
怎么会杀了你？ 你什么意思？ 它的。
It will cut your. Oh, we know you're right.
它会削减你的。 哦，我们知道你是对的。
No, it could. It's. This is it.
不，它可以。 它的。 就是这个。
Look sharp.
看起来很犀利。
Oh, that's enough.
哦，这就够了。
No, no. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up.
不，不。 他妈的闭嘴。 他妈的闭嘴。
Give me a second. Oh, my God. What are you doing?
你稍等一会儿。 我的天啊。 你在做什么？
I swear to God, I'm going to fuck this.
我向上帝发誓，我要去他妈的。
Is that what this. Is a part of that you want to explore?
是这样的吗。 您想探索其中的一部分吗？
Where's your sports?
你的运动在哪里？
Are your instincts, huh?
你的直觉是吧？
Where are your where's your curiosity?
你的好奇心在哪里？
Come here.
过来。
No, no, no, no, no. Help. Here.
不，不，不，不，不，不。 帮助。 这里。
Pull it.
拉它。
All right.
好的。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, my. God.
天啊。 上帝。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Fine. OK.
美好的。 好的。
Something just stopped it bad with.
有什么东西阻止了它。
All this for the fan.
这一切都是为了粉丝。
And now we stick it in yeah.
现在我们坚持下去是的。
Look at this. Easy.
看这个。 简单的。
Quickly go inside
赶紧进去
go inside.
进去。
What you doing? Go inside.
你在干什么？ 进去。
Hello, Mysta..
你好，米斯塔..
Oh, yeah. Mysta.
哦耶。 米斯塔。
Dolan.
多兰。
God, I
天啊我
Hahhh.
哈哈。
I thought I was going to chop. Your legs off.
我以为我要砍了。 你的腿断了。
I wanted to see that down.
我想看看。
It was no get again.
这是没有得到再次。
No way.
没门。
No, no, no. I want to grab it.
不不不。 我想抓住它。
Come over here now.
现在过来。
Fuck you.
去你的。
Like you want to grab it, huh?
就像你想抓住它，对吧？
Huh? Should be able to see.
嗯？ 应该可以看到。
Want to snap my legs again? And I'm serious.
又想折断我的腿？ 我是认真的。
Don't don't do it to me, OK?
不要不要这样对我好不好？
You promise?
你保证？
You promise you won't do that. You promise you won't do that?
你保证不会那样做。 你保证不会那样做？
Hey. I tell forever, OK?
嘿。 我永远告诉你，好吗？
Don't let it go.
不要放过它。
Mister. Just get it. Just kidding.
先生。 只要得到它。 只是在开玩笑。
I'm kidding.
我在开玩笑。
OK. Come on.
好的。 来吧。
Help me.
帮我。
Hey, man, find a way just like come.
嘿，伙计，想办法来吧。
I can't get through.
我过不去
Maybe you can hold the other end.
也许你可以抓住另一端。
No, I can't hold that. You're not going to give it to me.
不，我受不了了。 你不会把它给我的。
Hold on. Maybe I got to find a way.
坚持，稍等。 也许我得想办法。
I say there.
我说那里。
Stay there and look pretty.
呆在那里，看起来很漂亮。
OK, practise your your squats.
好的，练习你的深蹲。
I don't know
我不知道
how easy.
多么容易。
All right, so now this stuff.
好的，所以现在这个东西。
Because electric power stuff.
因为电力的东西。
Yeah, it's it's the the the the the the the thermodynamics.
是的，它是热力学。
The other the the the integrals, the.
其他的积分，。
Sorry, calculus.
对不起，微积分。
I didn't hear what you just said because I was looking at my five us.
我没有听到你刚才说的话，因为我正在看着我的五个我们。
We'll get.
我们会得到的。
All right, look in your ass. Look at my ass.
好吧，看看你的屁股。 看看我的屁股。
Oh, no, look at your ass asss.
哦，不，看看你的屁股屁股。
Funky, ugly.
时髦，丑陋。
Class. He's working your way.
班级。 他正在按照你的方式工作。
You mean you saw me naked?
你的意思是你看到我赤身裸体？
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, I did need something. All right.
是的，我确实需要一些东西。 好的。
OK, Leo does have a nice ass.
好吧，Leo确实有一个不错的屁股。
No. What the fuck.
不，他妈的。
Are you looking
你是不是在寻找
what?
什么？
I know you look and let me look.
我知道你看，让我看。
And you were looking. You're looking while I was away to.
而你正在寻找。 我不在的时候你在找。
What the fuck is you?
你他妈是什么鬼？
Can't get enough of it.
受够了。
Prison does nobody say I'm lonely. And.
监狱里没有人说我孤独。 和。
It's all me.
都是我。
Fantasy days.
幻想的日子。
I'm here,
我在这里，
OK? You you got a ten year service.
好的？ 你得到了十年的服务。
Once we. Do the sentence, you.
一旦我们。 做这句话，你。
Have like six months or something, right?
有六个月左右的时间，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Foul problem because I murdered somebody.
犯规问题，因为我谋杀了某人。
That's why they're.
这就是他们的原因。
I don't know what's worse, murdering someone on Grand Theft Auto,
我不知道更糟糕的是，在侠盗猎车手中谋杀某人，
but, like, sentences, laundry card.
但是，例如句子，洗衣卡。
Once we have that, you.
一旦我们有了，你。
Don't know which one's worse.
不知道哪个更差。
To hide. In it. Yeah.
隐藏。 在里面。 是的。
That one.
那个。
OK, think about.
好的，考虑一下。
The suspected and then bring it to the boat.
怀疑然后把它带到船上。
Let's say.
比方说。
Let's say somebody murders murders me, OK?
假设有人谋杀了我，好吗？
I converses like somebody steals your car.
我说话就像有人偷了你的车一样。
Which is worse to you?
哪个对你更糟？
Well, if you're dead, you're dead.
好吧，如果你死了，你就死了。
But if you're alive, you just lost a shit ton of money because your car's gone,
但如果你还活着，你会因为你的车不见了而损失了一大笔钱，
and you're probably gonna be put in debt,
你很可能会负债累累，你的保险会飞涨，你会活下去。
Very sad.
很伤心。
So that's what I'm saying.
这就是我要说的。
You have to think. About these things.
你必须思考。 关于这些事情。
Did you have the pain?
你痛过吗？
I don't think you're thinking.
我不认为你在想。
I I don't care.
我不在乎。
I don't think so. I don't know, sir.
我不这么认为。 我不知道，先生。
What am I doing?
我在做什么？
What is happening? I wasn't paying attention to my life.
怎么了？ 我没有注意我的生活。
I was thinking about money.
我在想钱。
OK? I push you and you get stuck.
好的？ 我推你，你就卡住了。
No, you go inside.
不，你进去。
Oh, fuck.
哦，操。
What am I supposed to be the dad here? What?
我在这里应该是什么爸爸？ 什么？
Smiley daddy?
笑脸爸爸？
You're supposed to call him Daddy free. Petrified. Right?
你应该叫他爸爸自由。 石化。 对？
That's great. I would never call you daddy.
这太棒了。 我永远不会叫你爸爸。
Since you did it last time during the collab.
因为你上次在合作期间这样做了。
No. Yes, you did.
不，是的，你做到了。
There's there's little evidence.
几乎没有证据。
Oh, no, no.
哦，不，不。
I have your number. Please.
我有你的号码。 请。
See the rules and regulations.
请参阅规则和规定。
Not just my number.
不只是我的号码。
It's the card, man.
这是卡，伙计。
I need your name and number
我需要你的名字和电话号码
convince him.
说服他。
Hold on, Vince.
等等，文斯。
What do you think? You're.
你怎么看？ 你是。
What's your name again?
你又叫什么名字？
Little closer.
更近一点。
It's not here. Ow!
它不在这里。 哦！
Ow! Ow!
哦！ 哦！
Ow! Ow! Get over here, you idiot.
哦！ 哦！ 到这里来，你这个白痴。
I convinced him.
我说服了他。
Oh, my God. You. You're amazing.
我的天啊。 你。 你太棒了。
Holy shit. Oh.
天啊。 哦。
Okay.
好的。
I guess I'm going to.
我想我会的。
I'll see you down there. Oh, my God.
我会在下面见到你。 我的天啊。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Here.
这里。
Court We go this way and those other moves shh.
法庭我们走这条路，其他的动作嘘。
Stop talking. Nope. We're going to get suspicious.
别说话了。 没有。 我们会产生怀疑。
Amongst us. Amongst
在我们中间。
us, amongst us, amongst us, amongst us, amongst us, amongst us, amongst us.
在我们中间，在我们中间，在我们中间，在我们中间，在我们中间，在我们中间，在我们中间。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Are you trying to shake me around?
你是想动摇我吗？
What are you, fucking dick
你是什​​么，他妈的鸡巴
this is not a shop.
这不是一家商店。
It's like, you know.
就像，你知道的。
It's like we're going on a grocery market ride.
这就像我们要去杂货市场一样。
I'm in the I'm the shopping cart.
我在我是购物车。
It's like back when I was five years old.
就像回到我五岁的时候。
Oh, I got in the shopping cart before, and then it fell on me.
哦，我之前进过购物车，然后就掉到了我的身上。
It fell on you.
它落在你身上。
Holy shit.
天啊。
It flipped upside down. But I did it.
它颠倒过来了。 但我做到了。
Yeah. Where are we going?
是的。 我们去哪？
Oh. This is how we get past today's laundry. Hi.
哦。 这就是我们如何通过今天的洗衣。 你好。
What if they check in? What? They check it.
如果他们签到怎么办？ 什么？ 他们检查它。
Gain access to the back room.
进入后面的房间。
It's the back room.
是后室。
The back rooms.
后面的房间。
You never watch the bathrooms?
你从不看浴室？
No, I haven't
不，我没有
Hello.
你好。
Hey, guard, can I ask you something?
嘿，警卫，我能问你一件事吗？
Time for. You.
的时间。 你。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
You got rejected immediately.
你马上就被拒绝了。
Sucks the suck.
糟透了。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇。
What are you doing, inmate?
你在做什么，犯人？
Get away from there. Go to my office.
远离那里。 去我的办公室。
He pushed me into.
他把我推了进去。
The push you into me. Wow.
把你推向我。 哇。
OK, I think you have to go where the guards.
好吧，我想你必须去守卫的地方。
All right? Unless he doesn't let you.
好的？ 除非他不让你。
He doesn't let me go in there unless it does.
他不让我进去，除非它允许。
And I'm just stupid.
而我只是愚蠢。
Never mind.
没关系。
Oh, no. He's gone. Look, he's going to look. He's going to look.
不好了。 他已经去了。 看，他会看的。 他要去看看。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, man. What are you doing?
天啊。 你在做什么？
Come here. Get these guys. I don't know. I'm.
过来。 得到这些家伙。 我不知道。 我是。
I've put them in the hole.
我把它们放进了洞里。
I mean, what did I.
我的意思是，我做了什么。
What did we think was going to happen?
我们认为会发生什么？
We need to put the sheets in.
我们需要把床单放进去。
You put in the washing machine.
你放进洗衣机。
To get sheets on top. Of me. All of they're right here.
把床单放在上面。 我的。 他们都在这里。
Oh, on fire
哦，着火了
on. Yeah.
在。 是的。
OK, bring it over.
好的，把它拿过来。
Oh, I think got beat up that dude again.
哦，我想又被那个家伙打败了。
I think. No, no, no.
我认为。 不不不。
It's open.
它是开放的。
Oh, it's open. Open.
哦，它是开放的。 打开。
Oh, he's. Still stuck in there. OK.
哦，他是。 还卡在那里。 好的。
I think I can just put sheets in now. Hmm.
我想我现在可以把床单放进去。 唔。
How much do we have to put inside like I should some.
我们必须像我应该的那样在里面放多少。
No, I. Don't know
不，我不知道
why you get inside it and I'll put a sheet on top of you. Ok?
你为什么要进去，我会在你身上放一张床单。 好的？
Oh, it just disappeared.
哦，它刚刚消失了。
There's no sheets anymore.
已经没有床单了。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
You got to put it on me then. OK,
那你得给我戴上。 好的，
cover me.
掩护我。
I'll be.
我将要。
Back. OK, we're all set.
后退。 好的，我们都准备好了。
Cover yourself.
盖住自己。
Oh, you can hide. Ha!
哦，你可以隐藏。 哈！
All right.
好的。
See, now.
看，现在。
I don't know how. Me.
我不知道怎么。 我。
It's impossible. It's impossible.
是不可能的。 是不可能的。
Fuck this up .Your purity.
去他妈的。你的纯洁。
Right now literally looks like amongst us.
现在看起来就像在我们中间。
I know, right?
我知道，对吧？
You're being real.
你是真实的。
Sussy.
苏西。
Well, yes.Sussy.
嗯，是的。苏西。
Sassy guide.
时髦的指南。
No. Hi, Fi, you fucking idiot.
不，嗨，Fi，你这该死的白痴。
You OK.
你还好吗。
See what we have here?
看看我们这里有什么？
I'm all right. Looks good.
我没事。 看起来挺好的。
Get out of the way.
走开。
Oh, he's pushing you.
哦，他在逼你。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, no way.
哦，没办法。
Where am I. Going?
我去哪儿了？
To get rid of that guard.
摆脱那个守卫。
Oh, do I have to convince this God as well?
哦，我也必须说服这个上帝吗？
Uh, hey.
呃，嘿。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
I can get to distract him.
我可以分散他的注意力。
Maybe
也许
there's going to be a fight.
会有一场战斗。
I don't know why. There's always fights and prison.
我不知道为什么。 总是有打架和牢狱之灾。
She's broken, but there's a problem with that washing machine.
她坏了，但那台洗衣机有问题。
Oh, yeah? What's the problem?
哦耶？ 问题是什么？
I don't know. It's broken.
我不知道。 它被打破。
I'll do.
我会做。
Where the fuck am I going? Doesn't look broken.
我他妈要去哪里？ 看起来没破。
Stop lying.
停止说谎。
Get back towards
往回走
you're wearing me.
你穿着我。
Let me talk to you again. There going to be a fight?
让我再和你谈谈。 会打架吗？
I think those two. What are you doing?
我觉得那两个 你在做什么？
I don't know.
我不知道。
This help.
这个帮助。
Over there like that grab. She.
那边就是那个抓。 她。
Can't you not see, dude?
难道你看不到吗，伙计？
How does he not see me?
他怎么看不到我？
Get back to work?
回去工作？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, shit. OK.
妈的。 好的。
Ok. What the fuck do I do then?
行。 那我他妈怎么办？
Hey, come one of you to do something.
嘿，来你们中的一个做点什么。
You seem to be having a great day.
你似乎度过了愉快的一天。
You got that shit, right?
你有那个狗屎，对吧？
You're looking at a free. Man, ok? Shit.
你正在看一个免费的。 伙计，好吗？ 拉屎。
Yep. Next week is my last.
是的。 下周是我的最后一周。
Oh, I need you in here to help
哦，我需要你在这里帮忙
have fun.
玩得开心。
Oh, I will.
哦，我会的。
I need to get in the back room, but I need someone to focus on that.
我需要进入后面的房间，但我需要有人专注于此。
Ah the guard's gone.
啊，守卫走了。
First, I'll go to a strip club.
首先，我会去脱衣舞俱乐部。
Why are you talking to this guy?
你为什么要和这个人说话？
I need to get someone to do something or the best strip club.
我需要找人做某事或最好的脱衣舞俱乐部。
And maybe I can sabotage all.
也许我可以破坏一切。
Oh, no, he's.
哦，不，他是。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. He's really right there.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。 他真的就在那里。
He's literally right there.
他真的就在那里。
Yes, that's sabotage.
是的，这就是破坏。
I'll put this. Inside. Of that.
我会放这个。 里面。 其中。
You fuck what?
你他妈的什么？
Put it inside it.
把它放在里面。
I want to put it inside.
我想把它放在里面。
Put it inside. Put inside. OK.
把它放在里面。 放进去。 好的。
Oh, my God. Deal. With this.
我的天啊。 交易。 有了这个。
And put. It down. Oh, shit.
并放。 它下来。 妈的。
I could just put it down. What have you done before?
我只能放下它。 你以前做过什么？
And then turn it on. Oh, wait.
然后打开它。 等一下。
I can open the door.
我可以开门。
I can open this door, but.
我可以打开这扇门，但是。
Ah. Oh, yeah. He has to get the shot.
啊。 哦耶。 他必须投篮。
Yeah, I'm ready. I'm ready.
是的，我准备好了。 我已经准备好了。
Yeah, I'll put this last one in.
是的，我会把最后一个放进去。
OK, I can't put this last one in
好的，我不能把这最后一个放在放下。
What do I do then?
那我该怎么办？
I'll turn on.
我会打开。
Go. I'm doing it. I'm doing it now.
去。 我正在做。 我现在正在做。
It's a way for him to leave as always for me live.
这是他离开的一种方式，一如既往地为我活着。
OK, ok. OK.
好的好的。 好的。
And I run through it all broken again.
我又一次经历了这一切。
Yeah, it's broken.
是的，它坏了。
Go with that man. OK, come on. Come on. Doors open, doors open.
和那个人一起去。 好的，来吧。 来吧。 门开了，门开了。
Oh, let's go.
哦，我们走吧。
Like in the fucking warrior.
就像在他妈的战士。
Oh. Oh, my god.
哦。 我的天啊。
Oh, oh. Oh.
哦，哦。 哦。
All right. There's an event.
好的。 有一个事件。
All right, now we need to put the seats.
好的，现在我们需要放置座位。
Oh, now you're going to beSussy.
哦，现在你要成为苏西了。
That's going to events, man.
那是要发生的事情，伙计。
Get my hands.
抓住我的手。
Get my hands. Up
抓住我的手。 起来和Mysta。
Fine. You want me. To go in the vents?
美好的。 你需要我。 进入通风口？
No, just trying to check you out. I mean, go again.
不，只是想看看你。 我的意思是，再去一次。
You little bitch.
你这个小婊子。
Get up here.
起来这里。
I just started.
我刚开始。
But now.
但现在。
Oh, sure.
行，可以。
You're right.
你说的对。
No, hey.
不，嘿。
Who wants Shake?
谁要奶昔？
Shake a little bit more?
再摇一摇？
All right, I got to give you sheets.
好吧，我得给你床单。
I need sheets for
我需要床单
where you doing up there?
你在那里做什么？
Beside
旁
what is that OK,
什么好，
here, take the fucking.
来，去他妈的。
Sheet, bitch.
床单，婊子。
And what was that one?
那是什么？
Bring me some sheets on it.
给我一些床单。
Grabbed my hand, babe.
抓住我的手，宝贝。
Dude, what do you need some money sheets for?
哥们，你要几张钞票干什么？
I'm like Spiderman.
我就像蜘蛛侠。
All I have. You can you.
我所拥有的一切。 你可以的。
Shoot? Can shoot.
射击？ 能拍。
What's it called?
这叫什么？
You're you're sticky stuff am.
你是你是粘性的东西。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I'm not.
我不是。
Is open there.
在那里开着。
Oh, you shouldn't eat that
哦，你真的不应该吃那个。 你可以吗？
Not ever has ever eaten spider spider silk web.
从来没有吃过蜘蛛蜘蛛丝网。
Whatever it is isn't.
不管是什么都不是。
Spider webs like made out of that off
蜘蛛网就像是由它制成的
it's all very sanitary, isn't it?
这一切都很卫生，不是吗？
I mean, yeah, it's probably not, but I don't think that's what it's made out of.
我的意思是，是的，它可能不是，但我不认为这就是它的组成部分。
I'm pretty sure it comes from the ass.
我很确定它来自屁股。
Did no it doesn't.
没有它没有。
Spider webs does.
蜘蛛网可以。
It does. Isn't there like another blast.
确实如此。 是不是又一次爆发了。
There's another hole.
还有一个洞。
Isn't there another hole for it?
不是还有个坑吗？
You're thinking of vaginas.
你在想阴道。
No, I'm not the. Why are you.
不，我不是。 你为什么。
That's the hole. No, there's no. Do it.
那就是那个洞。 不，没有。 去做吧。
Oh, my God, no.
哦，我的上帝，没有。
There's another hole.
还有一个洞。
Isn't there another hole? I'm like.
不是还有个坑吗？ 我长得像。
I don't yeah.
我没有呀。
There's one you open and then there's the other one in.
你打开一个，然后另一个进去。
No, really.
不完全是。
I'll be out of OK.
我会没事的。
Oh, yeah. I've had enough. I've had enough.
哦耶。 我已经受够了。 我已经受够了。
I've had enough kind of there on that hey.
我已经受够了，嘿。
Oh, that I can hold out for you.
哦，我可以为你坚持。
Maybe I can pull here like this is.
也许我可以像这样拉到这里。
This is your job? Yeah. You like that?
这是你的工作？ 是的。 你喜欢？
OK, yeah.
好的，是的。
You can keep it down.
你可以保持下去。
Can you, like, lower?
能不能低一点？
A little bit lower.
低一点。
Lower down. Yeah, you'll get
低下。 是的，你会让你在我的头上得到更多。 或者。 不。
No. Fuck.
不，操。
I'm sorry, babe.
对不起，宝贝。
Oh, maybe, maybe put on. Oh, oh, oh.
哦，也许，也许穿上。 哦哦哦。
There you go. There you go.
你去吧。 你去吧。
I know
我知道
why we have the guard here.
为什么我们这里有警卫。
US the guard.
美国守卫。
The fucking guard.
该死的守卫。
He walked. By. I don't know.
他走了。 经过。 我不知道。
Look, pull this together.
看，把这个放在一起。
Oh, what's.
哦，什么。
This big.
这么大。
Thing here? US
东西在这里？ 我们
they won't hear us, huh?
他们不会听到我们的，对吧？
Slowly.
慢慢地。
Mm hmm. See
嗯嗯。 看
and now one of us has to jump.
现在我们中的一个人必须跳下去。
Where do you get down near me?
你在我附近哪里下车？
It's pitch black.
一片漆黑。
I got to go down. There, right?
我得下去。 在那里，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Fuck it. I'll go first.
去他妈的。 我会先去。
OK, go
好的，去你好吗？
OK. This, you know.
好的。 这个，你知道的。
You know shit.
你知道狗屎。
Dumb ass. Yeah.
笨蛋。 是的。
It's fine. I'm not afraid of the dark.
没事。 我不怕黑。
Find a flashlight. Here
找一个手电筒。 这里
is the flashlight I just got you.
是我刚给你的手电筒。
Just go over here.
就到这里吧。
You all guess.
你们都猜。
All I hold the fuck on Jesus.
我对耶稣的一切都是他妈的。
Calm your tits. I'm coming.
平静你的乳房。 我来了。
Hey, sunset hope in the dark.
嘿，黑暗中的日落希望。
I'm your hope in the dark.
我是你黑暗中的希望。
You all know what's going on here.
你们都知道这里发生了什么。
No, I'm wet.
不，我湿了。
How the hell did you end up there?
你到底是怎么到那里去的？
Almost close to help you left. What?
差一点就帮你离开了。 什么？
It was all dark. Yeah. I can't see.
天黑了。 是的。 我看不见。
I needed some light.
我需要一些光。
I can do something.
我可以做点什么。
Very light, you dumb fuck.
很轻，你这个笨蛋。
You think right now? Shut up, smart.
你现在想？ 闭嘴，聪明。
Shut up. OK, fine. I'm not.
住口。 好的。 我不是。
You don't get like that.
你不会那样。
Fuck you. Fuck you. No, no, I'm leaving. I'm leaving.
去你的。 去你的。 不，不，我要走了。 我走了。
Oh, fuck you.
哦，去你妈的。
Fuck you. I got to go.
去你的。 我要走了。
Get you anyway. I can fucking do this. I can see in the dark.
无论如何都要得到你。 我他妈的可以做到这一点。 我可以在黑暗中看到。
You figure I need.
你认为我需要。
You want me to beg?
你要我乞求吗？
Oh, I need you beg for me beg for me.
哦，我需要你为我求求我。
Why you fucking wish
为什么你他妈的希望你他妈的希望。
We had you get over there Fuck you.
我们让你到那里去你妈的。
Man with my legs.
有我腿的人。
Another valve over here Leo.
莱奥这边的另一个阀门。
Fucker.
笨蛋。
I'm helping you help me out.
我正在帮助你帮助我。
Oh, you're wet too.
哦，你也湿了。
They were both wet. Im always wet.
他们都湿了。 我总是湿的。
Looks like that. One. Stop the water.
看起来是这样的。 一。 停止水。
Stop looking at me.
别看我了。
Stop looking at you what I want to look at What if I want to look at you,
别看你我想看什么如果我想看你怎么办，
creep if I want.
如果我愿意，蠕动。
To Absolute creep. Creep
绝对蠕变。 蠕变
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Why did you just leave?
你为什么刚刚离开？
Give flashlight?
送手电筒？
No, he's mine.
不，他是我的。
Give me the flashlight. No.
给我手电筒。 不。
It's my flashlight.
这是我的手电筒。
Flashlight. Flashlight is my flash.
手电筒。 手电筒是我的闪光灯。
Hand me the flashlight.
把手电筒递给我。
Vincent, hand me the flashlight.
文森特，把手电筒递给我。
I can get my flashlight.
我可以得到我的手电筒。
But you see my face.
但你看到我的脸。
I'm looking.
我在看。
Look at his face.
看他的脸。
Look at this stone dark.
看这石暗。
Vincent.
文森特。
Hello. Is your brain OK?
你好。 你的大脑还好吗？
I Vincent.
我文森特。
Vincent, hand me the flashlight.
文森特，把手电筒递给我。
Here's a flashlight, son.
这是手电筒，儿子。
Get the fuck out of here. Leo.
他妈的离开这里。 狮子座。
Something's wrong with you.
你有什么问题。
Wow. Something's wrong with me. Wow.
哇。 我有什么问题。 哇。
Rude ass, motherfucker.
粗鲁的屁股，混蛋。
Oh, look.
哦，看。
Now. That's karma, bitch.
现在。 那是业力，婊子。
Good, dude. It right there.
很好，伙计。 它就在那里。
That's just gas. Doesn't matter.
那只是气体。 没关系。
Is gas poisonous?
煤气有毒吗？
No, oh, here we go.
不，哦，我们开始吧。
Shit.
拉屎。
There's gas in your ass.
你的屁股里有气体。
Open the door. Be useful.
打开门。 有用。
Be useful. Help me.
有用。 帮我。
I got a rock.
我得到了一块石头。
What do you want to do?
你想让我做什么？
All rocket.
全是火箭。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Do it. Nice
去做吧。 好的
Good shit.
好狗屎。
Thank you, Leo. All right, now give me back my flashlight.
谢谢你，狮子座。 好吧，现在把我的手电筒还给我。
No. I need it to see in the dark.
不，我需要它在黑暗中看到。
I need to see in the dark, too.
我也需要在黑暗中看到。
That was my flashlight. Original. Yeah.
那是我的手电筒。 原来的。 是的。
Just tell you, I.
告诉你，我。
I lent it to you. Give it back.
我借给你了。 放回去。
It's my flashlight now.
它现在是我的手电筒。
It's give me back my fucking flashlight, bitch.
把我他妈的手电筒还给我，婊子。
It's mine. I need inflicted.
这是我的。 我需要受到伤害。
I looked it. It was in my ass. It was in my fucking ghosts.
我看了看。 它在我的屁股里。 它在我他妈的鬼魂里。
It was literally in my ass.
它真的在我的屁股里。
Right now I need. To find. Ghosts.
现在我需要。 去寻找。 鬼魂。
Give me back my flashlight.
把我的手电筒还给我。
You Dick! It's my flashlight now.
你个迪克！ 它现在是我的手电筒。
Get over here.
到这里来。
Let's bust this up, OK?
让我们解决这个问题，好吗？
You win this time.
这次你赢了。
I'll remember this
我会记住这个
you remember this?
你记得这个吗？
Are we supposed to synchronise?
我们应该同步吗？
Ah, bang.
啊，砰。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I think we just keep going.
我想我们只是继续前进。
Oh, hey, see that?
哦，嘿，看到了吗？
Vincent,
文森特，
this place is giving me the creeps.
这个地方让我毛骨悚然。
I'll now have to rely on your attitude.
文森特，我现在只能依靠你的态度了。
I can't see anything so dark.
我看不到这么黑的东西。
You're not scared.
你并不害怕。
It says a area.
上面写着一个区域。
Which means it's down here. No, no, no, no, no.
这意味着它在下面。 不，不，不，不，不，不。
Look behind you.
看看你身后。
What's down here? What's on your right?
下面是什么？ 你的右边是什么？
What's down here? Yeah.
下面是什么？ 是的。
Let's not rush.
我们不要着急。
Let's take a look.
让我们来看看。
Enjoy the sights.
欣赏美景。
Look at this chair.
看看这把椅子。
Holy fuck.
他妈的。
How do I show?
我如何显示？
How do I unsub if I got gifted?
如果我有天赋，如何取消订阅？
Asof not can follow me. No.
Asof 不能跟着我。 不。
Then come on.
那就来吧。
Come on, baby.
来吧宝贝。
Yada, yada. Appreciate the gifted sub.
雅达，雅达。 欣赏有天赋的潜艇。
He uses so many emotes.
他使用了很多表情。
Subscribe now off switch prime.
立即订阅关闭 switch prime。
Shut your mouth.
闭上你的嘴。
I would wipe.
我会擦。
That was a guy there.
那是一个人在那里。
You see? Now, there's some people up there.
你看？ 现在，上面有一些人。
We can look up a skirt.
我们可以查一下裙子。
His skirt, all of.
他的裙子，全部。
So that's what you're into?
所以这就是你喜欢的吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Maybe. Bastard.
也许。 混蛋。
Maybe I'll.
也许我会的。
Hold it.
拿着它。
This way.
这边走。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Did someone, like, vacuuming?
有人喜欢吸尘吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I know. It's coming from outside.
我知道。 它是从外面传来的。
Oh, ok. OK.
哦好的。 好的。
I think there's, like, a truck coming by that's really obnoxious.
我认为有一辆卡车经过，真的很讨厌。
Here.
这里。
Add small ambience is fine. So scary.
添加小氛围很好。 太可怕了。
I've got an idea.
我有个主意。
Turn your back against mine.
背对着我。
Are you kidding me?
你在跟我开玩笑吗？
Chest against my best asthma.
胸部对抗我最好的哮喘。
It's never going to work. Relax.
它永远不会起作用。 放松。
The truck. Is solid. Noxious.
卡车。 是固体。 有毒。
You know, it's so obnoxious.
你知道，这太讨厌了。
Oh, wait. What is this?
等一下。 这是什么？
It'll be much quicker.
会快很多。
You fuck together at the same time.
你们同时他妈的在一起。
Oh, you're
哦，你是
we. Wait. Oh.
我们。 等待。 哦。
Oh, ok. OK. I see what's happening.
哦好的。 好的。 我明白发生了什么。
Oh, I see.
我懂了。
What's happening. Yeah.
怎么了。 是的。
This all. Up. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
这一切。 向上。 哦，是的，是的，是的。
You tap, tap, tap, tap, tap.
你轻敲，轻敲，轻敲，轻敲，轻敲。
You're all alone.
你都是一个人。
Doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo.
嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟。
Now, Mysta. Mayor,
现在，米斯塔。 市长，它起来了。 对你，好吗？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Hey, y'all divorced, man. Holy shit.
嘿，你们都离婚了，伙计。 天啊。
I didn't do anything.
我什么也没做。
You just keep going too fast.
你只是一直走得太快。
Keep up with the pace, bitch.
跟上节奏，婊子。
Mysta. Mysta. Mysta.
米斯塔。 米斯塔。 米斯塔。
Calm down.
冷静下来。
Mysta. Misconduct.
米斯塔。 不当行为。
Call them. OK.
给他们打电话。 好的。
So slow.
太慢了。
You got to adjust your slow, slow,
你必须调整你的慢，慢，慢，慢，慢，慢的混蛋。
Yeah. Yeah. You want talk about slow?
是的。 是的。 你要谈慢？
You want to talk about slow d just so you'll fucking follow us?
你想谈论slow d只是为了让你他妈的跟着我们？
Oh, my god.
我的天啊。
Oh, listen, calm down.
哦，听着，冷静下来。
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
停，停，停，停，停，停。
What one fuck up. You got to chill.
搞什么鬼。 你得冷静一下。
You got to chill.
你得冷静一下。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Please, please go off. OK. OK.
拜托，请走开。 好的。 好的。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
It's not that hard.
这并不难。
Is not our job.
不是我们的工作。
Stop. Go.
停止。 去。
We have to go at the same time.
我们必须同时去。
No, we're at a different level.
不，我们处于不同的水平。
We go. OK, ok.
我们去。 好的好的。
No. Fuck that. We got. Yeah, no fuck up this time.
不，去他妈的。 我们有。 是的，这次别闹了。
No fuck ups this time for you.
这次不给你搞砸了。
Take it easy. I'm fucked.
别紧张。 我完蛋了。
Calm.
冷静的。
You go now. I'm good. OK, I got. Yeah, yeah.
你现在走。 我很好。 好的，我明白了。 是啊是啊。
OK. Nice.
好的。 好的。
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
不错不错不错不错不错
Not only got them so close.
不仅让他们如此接近。
So close. I'm so close.
很近。 我是如此接近。
Yeah. Oh. Oh, my God.
是的。 哦。 我的天啊。
Are you sure that's team work. Oh.
你确定这是团队合作吗？ 哦。
Huh. Good job, man. Yeah.
嗯。 干得好，伙计。 是的。
I don't like you as much anymore.
我不再那么喜欢你了。
I mean, way I like you, man.
我的意思是，我喜欢你，伙计。
I like you a. Little bit more. Yeah, that's what I want.
我喜欢你一个。 稍微多一点。 是的，这就是我想要的。
Yeah.
是的。
What? I don't like you as much.
什么？ 我没那么喜欢你。
That's so shit.
那太狗血了。
The one place you can get that.
你可以得到的一个地方。
Job have to have it.
工作必须拥有它。
Such a dick, miss, though you're such a same way.
真是个混蛋，小姐，虽然你也是这样。
Don't run my body
不要跑我的身体
no. Charles thigh sleeve free not.
不。 查尔斯大腿袖子免不了。
Yeah. Where are we going to do now? We're up here.
是的。 我们现在要去哪里？ 我们在这里。
We vented now. Uh.
我们现在发泄了。 呃。
While we can slip through the cracks.
虽然我们可以从裂缝中溜走。
You know.
你知道。
I saw through your crack.
我看穿了你的裂缝。
Yeah, like you hear that grunting.
是的，就像你听到的咕哝声一样。
You have a dirty mind ,Shoto.
你有一个肮脏的头脑，Shoto。
I know. I do.
我知道。 我愿意。
I embrace it.
我拥抱它。
You need to be more say so.
你需要更多这样说。
At least in my stream.
至少在我的直播中。
He you were talking about a fucking, like, universal vibrator.
他你说的是一个他妈的通用振动器。
Like 10 minutes into the stream.
就像10分钟进入溪流。
You can't say anything.
你不能说什么。
To redeem yourself at this. Point.
在此赎回自己。 观点。
I was, like, the first 5 minutes.
我是，就像，前5分钟。
It's not even. Worse.
它甚至不是。 更差。
Not moving.
没有移动。
It doesn't help your case.
这对你的情况没有帮助。
The stuff, that's the points.
东西，就是要点。
I haven't said anything sexy since then.
从那以后，我没有说过任何性感的话。
Your you were literally.
你是字面上的。
Flaunting your armpit hairs. The the guard.
炫耀你的腋毛。 守卫者。
You're saying that's notSussy.
你说那不是苏西。
That's going to be hot.
那会很热。
Spit my ass.
吐我屁股。
Oh, I'm good.
哦，我很好。
Let me take it.
让我拿走。
Yeah, yeah, I'm good. I'm good.
是的，是的，我很好。 我很好。
I'm to talk to this guy.
我要和这个人谈谈。
I'm going to shave this wood while you go do that, OK?
你去的时候我要刮这块木头，好吗？
What do you want?
你想要什么？
Enjoy yourself.
玩的开心。
I want a hammer. Yeah. What do you want?
我想要一把锤子。 是的。 你想要什么？
I want a wrench.
我想要一个扳手。
It's all I got to deal
这就是我要处理的一切
with. Questions.
和。 问题。
I have a quick question for you.
我有一个简短的问题要问你。
Why are you talking to him?
你为什么和他说话？
What day is that? Why are you asking about it?
那是什么日子？ 你为什么要问这个？
The day, Monday?
那一天，星期一？
Because it's Monday.
因为是星期一。
I need to know the day.
我需要知道那一天。
Stanley, fuck is fine. Oh, man.
斯坦利，他妈的很好。 天啊。
You lose track.
你迷失了方向。
Of that shit here on this guy's pretty. Nice. You're nuts.
关于这家伙的狗屎很漂亮。 好的。 你疯了。
I'm being. You're nuts.
我正在。 你疯了。
I going to take the wrench right from him, then.
那我就直接从他手里接过扳手。
Hey, it's mine.
嘿，这是我的。
It is.
这是。
OK, just don't take a hit on somebody away.
好的，只是不要对某人进行打击。
You come in. Come in, you dummy.
你进来。进来，你这个笨蛋。
You could use this fucker.
你可以用这个混蛋。
You did not look at it.
你没有看它。
Look at it. There's a hatch.
看它。 有一个舱口。
It's a wall.
这是一堵墙。
No. Come down here and look at the fucking beds.
不，下来看看他妈的床。
Look at it.
看它。
How are you going to fit down that?
你要怎么适应呢？
Well, what are we going to do of that
好吧，我们该怎么办
you almost locked me in the corner, you know that.
你差点把我锁在角落里，你知道的。
I could move over to this fucking guy.
我可以转向这个该死的家伙。
Look, he's sad.
看，他很难过。
No, no.
不，不。
I'm enjoying. My work done to enjoy.
我很享受。 我的工作是为了享受。
Myself. OK?
我。 好的？
I'm going to enjoy myself for a little bit.
我要享受一下自己。
You should be patient.
你应该耐心等待。
You want everybody back home, get out.
你希望每个人都回家，出去。
Let's stop.
我们停止吧。
Crying words.
哭着说。
Is coming.
来了。
You get the fucking right.
你他妈的是对的。
Fuck off when I'm leaving.
我走的时候滚蛋。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
The only thing.
唯一的事情。
My God will be nice.
我的上帝会很好的。
I'll never amount to anything.
我永远不会有任何成就。
You're a bitch.
你是个婊子。
Well, what am I doing?
好吧，我在做什么？
Down here?
下来这里？
Earlier?
早点？
Oh, jeez.
哦，天哪。
That I've been behind the bin.
我一直在垃圾箱后面。
Because I'm so obsessed with these events, girl.
因为我对这些事件如此着迷，女孩。
Yeah. Why is. I mean, you're soSussy.
是的。 为什么是。 我的意思是，你太苏了。
Why do you keep. Looking at Vince?
你为什么留着。 看着文斯？
Oh, no, Vince.
哦，不，文斯。
What's going on, dude?
怎么回事，伙计？
I can't even do anything with events.
我什至不能对事件做任何事情。
Man. SNAFU.
男人。 大闹天宫。
Hey, I heard that. Watch your mouth, inmate.
嘿，我听说了。 注意你的嘴，犯人。
What is. It?
什么是。 它？
Amber Hey, OK, here's.
琥珀 嘿，好的，这是。
They got everything. Do you have the wrench? I push him into this.
他们得到了一切。 你有扳手吗？ 我把他逼到这个地步。
Yeah, like, click, click. I'll talk.
是的，就像，点击，点击。 我会说。
You got the wrench behind them. OK.
你把扳手放在他们身后。 好的。
What do you want?
你想要什么？
What do I want?
我想要什么？
Yeah, what do you want?
是啊，你想要什么？
I want nothing, bitch.
我什么都想要，婊子。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He got fucking.
他他妈的。
Bamboozled for dingle because he got diddled.
因为他被骗了，所以被骗了。
My guy got it all. You got date.
我的家伙得到了一切。 你有约会。
You got Joe beginning
你让乔开始了
show.
显示。
What can we do here?
我们可以在这里做什么？
Hello? Sure. I want to walk through.
你好？ 当然。 我想走过。
Yeah, I think I have to use the wrench on the vents.
是的，我想我必须在通风口上使用扳手。
Oh, what the fuck is this?
哦，这他妈是什么？
Sabotage. Sabotage?
破坏。 破坏？
Oh, here we go. Here we go. Here we go for this.
哦，我们开始吧。 开始了。 我们来做这个。
Oh, we go. That's off the metal detector.
哦，我们去。 那是关闭金属探测器。
No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no. No.
不，不，不，不，不，不。 不，不，不，不，不，不。 不。
I shoves a metal detector. For what, though?
我推了一个金属探测器。 不过为了什么？
Come over here.
过来这里。
Come over to the vent.
来到通风口。
OK. Now get over to the vent, and then I'll give you the other edge.
好的。 现在到通风口，然后我会给你另一边。
Oh. I don't know what this is supposed to do, but, I mean, I got a vent.
哦。 我不知道这应该做什么，但是，我的意思是，我有一个发泄。
Oh, and now I go back to here, and that was a lock
哦，现在我回到这里，那是一把锁
in there in it, and I can undo the lock.
在里面，我可以解开锁。
Except that doesn't happen, because that's not what wrenches do.
除非那不会发生，因为那不是扳手的作用。
What are you doing, dude?
你在做什么，伙计？
What the fuck are you doing?
你他妈在做什么？
You're running around, like, living out of your cock out in the back here.
你到处乱跑，就像在后面靠你的公鸡生活一样。
And then I'm going to go in this door. I'm going to.
然后我要走进这扇门。 我要去。
Go back to cutting board, fuck this guy.
回到砧板上，操这家伙。
And then I'm going to walk out.
然后我要走出去。
Wait.
等待。
OK, see ya later. Bye.
好的，待会见。 再见。
Oh, oh, oh, no.
哦，哦，哦，不。
He's been touched on the island.
他在岛上被感动了。
We want to be here. Hey,
我们想在这里。 嘿，
where are you, mister?
你在哪里，先生？
Hello.
你好。
I smuggled a wrench to your cell.
我把扳手偷运到你的牢房了。
Go to the cell now. My.
现在去牢房。 我的。
Oh, we all. We turn off the metal detector, right?
哦，我们都是。 我们关掉金属探测器，对吧？
Oh, shit. I got scared.
妈的。 我吓坏了。
You scared me very sick in there. Well,
你在里面把我吓坏了。 好，
uh, I have to go with you.
呃，我必须和你一起去。
I think I have to go with you. I think so.
我想我必须和你一起去。 我认同。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Oh, let's go to. I don't know.
哦，我们去吧。 我不知道。
Hold on. Let me look around here for a second.
坚持，稍等。 让我看看这里。
Yeah, let's look around.
是的，让我们环顾四周。
Go. There's not really anything to do here.
去。 这里真的没什么可做的。
E e why would we need to turn off the metal detector?
E e 为什么我们需要关闭金属探测器？
If you're going to give me the wrench?
如果你要给我扳手？
Doesn't make any sense.
没有任何意义。
Yeah, I don't understand either. Way.
是的，我也不明白。 方式。
So in here, there's this guard.
所以在这里，有这个守卫。
Is he chill his children?
他让他的孩子们冷吗？
Oh, wait.
等一下。
Get on the inside.
进入里面。
Oh, you.
哦，你。
Go in I give you a wrench, and I go in. He's going to give me a patch.
进去，我给你一个扳手，然后我进去。他会给我一个补丁。
A bomb that's going to be air.
一颗即将成为空气的炸弹。
Just let me touch you up for a little bit. Yeah. Fuck.
让我稍微抚摸一下你。 是的。 他妈的。
Why do I have to be the one to get touched? You know the drill.
为什么我必须成为被感动的人？ 你知道该怎么做。
You like being touched.
你喜欢被触摸。
Oh, all right.
哦那好吧。
There you go. OK, now you take this.
你去吧。 好的，现在你拿着这个。
Get on the other side and help me, ok?
到另一边帮助我，好吗？
I get all of a sudden.
我一下子明白了。
Help me
帮我
you can give it to me.
你可以给我。
He's worse.
他更糟。
A motherfucker.
一个混蛋。
E Oh,
哦，
my God.
我的上帝。
I pressed it already.
我已经按过了。
You dumb ass.
你这个笨蛋。
All right, now I come first.
好吧，现在我先来。
Oh, all right. Oh, oh.
哦那好吧。 哦，哦。
Then I forgot.
然后我忘记了。
Hey, I think I hooked up. Cool.
嘿，我想我上钩了。 凉爽的。
We're good now.
我们现在很好。
What are we going to do now?
我们现在要做什么？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
We talk to him.
我们跟他说话。
Oh, he's falling asleep.
哦，他睡着了。
He's.
他是。
He's falling asleep on the job.
他在工作中睡着了。
Yeah.
是的。
Well, he doesn't have to do much.
好吧，他不需要做太多事情。
Dozens on work in front of him with my ass.
用我的屁股在他面前工作几十个。
What if we just kiss in front of him right now?
如果我们现在就在他面前亲吻呢？
Look,
看，
oh, gosh.
哦，天哪。
Oh, oh, oh,
哦哦哦，
oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
All right.
好的。
Oh, oh, wait.
哦，哦，等等。
Oh, hello.
哦你好。
Boys. My name's.
男孩们。 我的名字是。
What is it?
它是什么？
Let me show you. Come on, let me show you this over here.
让我演示给你看。 来吧，让我在这里给你看这个。
Let me. Show you. OK, I guess.
让我来。 给你看。 我觉得可以吧。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thank you. What's going on?
谢谢你。 到底是怎么回事？
I like that voice you did.
我喜欢你的声音。
Was that like you're. It was that young, the stuff.
是不是和你一样。 那是年轻的东西。
Don't you feel like you're a kid?
你不觉得你是个孩子吗？
Yeah, I'm downstairs.
是的，我在楼下。
I sound like a little kid.
我听起来像个小孩子。
Now just go.
现在走吧。
Oh, Mysta. Smith.
哦，米斯塔。 史密斯。
Let's go
我们走吧
buy too easy.
买太容易了。
Shakedown up against the bars.
对酒吧进行调整。
Inmate Oh, shit. Help! Help!
囚犯 哦，该死。 帮助！ 帮助！
Help! Help! Help!
帮助！ 帮助！ 帮助！
Help me, help me!
帮帮我，帮帮我！
OK, and, uh.
好的，而且，呃。
Hey, guys, maybe
嘿，伙计们，也许你不应该在里面动摇这个，好吗？
Never mind. Oh, this is bad. This is really bad.
没关系。 哦，这很糟糕。 这真的很糟糕。
What if I go.
如果我去怎么办。
Behind here and grab it from behind the toilet?
在这里，从厕所后面抓住它？
No. Right help, vincent.
不，正确的帮助，文森特。
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
哦，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。
Grab it. Grab a crowded. Grab it, grab it.
抓住它。 抢一个拥挤的。 抓住它，抓住它。
I got it all.
我明白了。
I got you, babe.
我明白你的意思了宝贝。
There's got to be a better place. To hide it.
一定有更好的地方。 隐藏它。
I put in your butt and your butt.
我把你的屁股和你的屁股。
They never check. Their hind here behind her like.
他们从不检查。 他们的后背在她身后就好了。
Oh, that's true. Yeah, you're right.
哦，那是真的。 是的，没错。
I'll be a fuck my boss.
我会是他妈的我的老板。
Cool. OK.
凉爽的。 好的。
You look so smug.
你看起来很得意
All right, arms up.
好吧，举起手来。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Tiptoes to assert dominance.
踮起脚尖来维护统治地位。
Nice bars, sir.
不错的酒吧，先生。
Against the bars.
反对酒吧。
All right, all right. Hey.
好吧，好吧。 嘿。
Easy, easy game, dude.
简单，简单的游戏，伙计。
So now we have to rent so we can.
所以现在我们必须租，所以我们可以。
Uh. What are we. Doing with the ranch, though?
呃。 我们是什么。 不过，与牧场有关吗？
Probably kill each other with a bucket.
大概是用桶互相残杀吧。
Oh, well, you have a wife.
哦，对了，你有老婆了。
I have a you have a wife,
我有一个你有一个妻子，你这个混蛋。
Third wife.
第三任妻子。
I was like.
我像。
This is a present thing, OK?
这是礼物，好吗？
Like, oh, well, obviously prison stays in prison.
就像，哦，好吧，显然监狱一直在监狱里。
All right, ok. OK.
好的，好的。 好的。
We re
我们真的，拉里，就像亲热，而你，就像，吐在他身上，就像，
you know, a good 5 minutes ago.
你知道，5 分钟前。
Say, that was nothing. Yeah, you come in here.
说，那不算什么。 是的，你进来吧。
I have ruined our. Family, man.
我毁了我们的。 以家庭为重的（男）人。
Is that we don't have a family.
是我们没有家庭。
It seems. Like we.
它似乎。 像我们一样。
Were imagining all of this. Are you sure?
这一切都在想象。 你确定吗？
I have a wife and five kids.
我有一个妻子和五个孩子。
You call me crazy.
你说我疯了。
Stop coming on to me.
别来找我了。
I've never given you advances.
我从来没有给你预付款。
It's only your head.
它只是你的头。
Your so too.
你也是。
I don't know yet.
我还不知道。
Kim, my vein.
金，我的血管。
Holy shit. I can't stop looking at the beam bulge
天啊。 我无法停止看着光束凸起
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Like it's like a snickers. You know, the.
就像它就像一个窃笑。 你知道。
That's not he misses it.
那不是他想念它。
You know, I think there's a. Little getting rid of that. Yeah.
你知道，我认为有一个。 有点摆脱它。 是的。
So I saw an article saying that they're going to get rid of the dick vein.
所以我看到一篇文章说他们要去除鸡巴静脉。
Yeah.
是的。
Someone donated to me yesterday and said to a a suicide.
昨天有人给我捐款，说要自杀。
I think they're having an emotional moment, and we're talking about big veins.
我认为他们正在经历一个情绪化的时刻，我们正在谈论大静脉。
All right.
好的。
Uh. Don't worry about that.
呃。 不用担心那个。
You won't? Fine. And you're sure?
你不会？ 美好的。 你确定吗？
Yeah. I got us a new place Bishop.
是的。 我给我们找了一个新的地方主教。
Oh, for now. Woo! I got a new house.
哦，暂时。 哇！ 我有了新房子。
Nice. Baby, baby, listen.
好的。 宝贝，宝贝，听着。
Baby, baby, you.
宝贝，宝贝，你。
Have to. Stay first.
不得不。 先留着。
Why are you still waiting?
你为什么还在等？
I'm just watching. No, I have no big cheese.
我只是在看。 不，我没有大奶酪。
No, I have no meetings.
不，我没有会议。
No visitors are coming in.
没有访客进来。
No one came to visit me.
没有人来看我。
Don't call all go back. To yourself.
不叫都回去。 对自己。
That's so sad.
那太可悲了。
Actually, I'd like to make a phone call, sir.
实际上，我想打个电话，先生。
Let's go play
我们一起去玩吧
Osama drama wife.
奥萨马戏剧妻子。
I don't know yeah. Pregnant, Carol.
我不知道是啊。 怀孕了，卡罗尔。
Pregnant.
孕。
Oh, I have a wife.
哦，我有一个妻子。
At home expecting our baby.
在家期待我们的宝宝。
Oh, my. Sister.
天啊。 姐姐。
Did you call her my sister?
你叫她姐姐吗？
Did you want.
你想要吗。
My say at all? You're in prison.
我说的呢？ 你在监狱里。
I'm going to be out.
我要出去了。
Your sister can be pregnant.
你姐姐可能怀孕了。
And this isn't who you are.
这不是你。
Is this how you want your future child to remember you?
这就是你希望你未来的孩子记住你的方式吗？
But I need to take care of the Harvey situation.
但我需要照顾哈维的情况。
Oh, my God, Carol.
哦，天哪，卡罗尔。
You know that he killed Gary.
你知道他杀了加里。
He was my family, my own brother.
他是我的家人，我的亲兄弟。
I got revenge on you.
我报复你了。
But you can't bring him back.
但是你不能把他带回来。
You're just going to get yourself killed.
你只会让自己被杀。
My wife is hot.
我的妻子很热。
Police you know I have to do this.
警察你知道我必须这样做。
And she loves you, Vincent.
她爱你，文森特。
Well.
好。
I'm not really into. Looks like.
我不是很喜欢。 好像。
Well, after that, I don't know.
好吧，在那之后，我不知道。
What are you going to say?
你要说什么？
Or are you going to say?
还是你要说？
I'm not really into people who are, like,
我不太喜欢那些在他们他妈的肚子里创造出生点的人。
Right?
对？
I'm not really into that.
我不是很喜欢那个。
You don't.
你没有。
I? I don't think they can huh?
一世？ 我不认为他们可以吧？
I'm not into pregnant people, bro.
我不喜欢怀孕的人，兄弟。
That's.
那是。
That's beside the point.
这是题外话。
But not looking at the pregnant. Oh, my God.
但不是看着怀孕的。 我的天啊。
Our window will leave tonight.
我们的窗户今晚就要离开了。
You're acting like you're acting like we're saying pregnant.
你表现得就像我们说怀孕一样。
The pregnant people are a type that people are what the.
怀孕的人是那种人是什么的。
Shut up, shut up and just be quiet.
闭嘴，闭嘴，保持安静。
Just stop.
停下来。
I can't do this anymore. I'm pretty.
我不能再这样做了。 我很漂亮。
Sure that's like a category.
当然，这就像一个类别。
I if that's a category I don't want anything to do with it.
如果那是一个类别，我不想与它有任何关系。
Yes, this thing is not.
是的，这件事不是。
Anyways, cause we're both married men.
无论如何，因为我们都是已婚男人。
We know.
我们知道。
We both cheated on our wives.
我们都欺骗了我们的妻子。
In prison. Each other yeah. Yep. Uh huh.
在监狱。 彼此是的。 是的。 嗯。
Uh huh.
嗯。
Uh huh. Oh, and now we're just going to start shovel.
嗯。 哦，现在我们要开始铲了。
Yeah, just don't drop it.
是的，只是不要放弃它。
OK, so a lot of sexual tension here.
好的，这里有很多性紧张。
Yeah, we do. Have this. Engine.
是的，我们有。 拥有这个。 引擎。
Let's hope we don't have to.
希望我们不必这样做。
There's nothing to hope for.
没有什么可指望的。
It ain't happened.
它没有发生。
And it over.
它结束了。
Yeah. Give me the wrench.
是的。 把扳手给我。
Oh. Oh, boy.
哦。 好家伙。
What are we doing?
我们在做什么？
I don't do both these and a new one.
我不做这两个和一个新的。
Do both those.
做这两件事。
These you go.
这些你去。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Might
可能
fuck it up.
去他妈的。
What do you mean, don't fuck it up?
什么意思，别搞砸了？
What I heard the noise.
我听到了什么噪音。
I guess. I did.
我猜。 我做到了。
Yeah.
是的。
The blooming, the fucking boom in the background.
盛开，背景中的他妈的繁荣。
I mean, I fucked it up. Boom, boom.
我的意思是，我搞砸了。 轰，轰。
OK. What
好的。 什么
I. Up we go.
I. 我们上去。
I thought this is it.
我以为就是这样。
Really good escape now.
现在真的很好逃。
Huh? Huh?
嗯？ 嗯？
Is this actually.
原来是这样吗。
Escape?
逃脱？
My fat lady?
我的胖女人？
So we just run.
所以我们就跑。
Let's go. See? See what?
我们走吧。 看？ 看什么？
Pull up.
拉起。
Oh, my God, you bitch. You go in.
哦，我的上帝，你这个婊子。 你进去。
I'm gone, gone, gone, gone, gone.
我走了，走了，走了，走了，走了。
That's a yellow up that we can pull up.
那是我们可以拉起的黄色向上。
But it was like this way. Mm hmm.
但事情就是这样。 嗯嗯。
Hmm, hmm.
嗯，嗯。
I'm following. I'm following.
我正在关注。 我正在关注。
I'm on your ass somewhere else.
我在你的屁股其他地方。
Thank goodness.
谢天谢地。
You you do.
你你做。
You smart, you smart.
你聪明，你聪明。
Little cookie. You are a smart little cookie.
小饼干。 你是个聪明的小饼干。
I like fucking you probably.
我可能喜欢操你。
You probably got all the gold stars in pre-school.
你可能在学前班得到了所有的金星。
Probably.
大概。
Yeah. I didn't get any love as a kid.
是的。 我小时候没有得到任何爱。
Let's go. Woosh.
我们走吧。 哇哦。
And, yeah, I'm going in.
而且，是的，我要进去了。
It looks like you're hugging me.
看起来你在拥抱我。
You're hugging me from behind
你从背后抱住我
oh. OK, officer.
哦。 好的，警官。
Enough of. That noise. OK.
够了。 那个噪音。 好的。
Let me go in the
让我去后面。 不得不为你开门。
Hold on. No. Oh.
坚持，稍等。 不，哦。
I just jumped on it. Jump on through, then.
我刚跳上去。 那就跳过去吧。
I guess. A jump scared you.
我猜。 一跳吓到你了。
Not really.
并不真地。
What the fuck was that noise?
那是什么鬼声音？
Today? No, wait.
今天？ 不，等等。
There's guards. There's guards, there's guards, there's guards.
有警卫。 有警卫，有警卫，有警卫。
You have a lot of they guarding nothing.
你有很多他们什么都不守。
What are the chances.
有什么机会。
That I had which
我有哪个
who took you to?
谁带你去的？
Toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
You're so. Careless.
你太。 粗心。
You are so careless.
你太粗心了。
How do they not see you?
他们怎么看不到你？
Tell us they're not looking this way.
告诉我们他们不是这样看的。
That's why.
因此。
Let go. OK, ok,
松手。 好的好的，
I shit.
我拉屎。
Excuse guard you're a scaredy cat.
对不起，你是一只害怕的猫。
I thought it was be a dog. We want to go.
我还以为是狗 我们想去。
All right. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
好的。 坚持，坚持，坚持。
Me all that's more. OK.
我就是这样。 好的。
I like that.
我喜欢。
Oh. Meza.
哦。 梅萨。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
The thunder. I don't know.
雷声。 我不知道。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, which way
哦，哪条路
on your side?
在你身边？
No, no, not like that.
不，不，不是那样的。
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
哦，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh, my. God.
天啊。 上帝。
We're on time.
我们准时。
That time, the ac that you see that we can.
那个时候，你看到的交流我们可以。
We can be more in sync.
我们可以更加同步。
You're in sync.
你是同步的。
We have that synergy, see?
我们有这种协同作用，明白吗？
How are we going to play legal legends
如果我们没有这种协同作用，我们将如何相互扮演法律传奇？
I replied to. You.
我回复了。 你。
I was like, add me, and then you didn't add me.
我当时想，加我，然后你没有加我。
Oh, you did. See that? No, I did. Yeah.
哦，你做到了。 看到了吗？ 不，我做了。 是的。
Oh, you did. Oh, shit.
哦，你做到了。 妈的。
I didn't see it.
我没看到。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
It's not. I'm not trust.
它不是。 我不信任。
Oh, no, no, no. No, no. I get it.
哦，不，不，不。 不，不。 我得到它。
I know. I want to play. I will play league with me.
我知道。 我要玩。 我会和我一起打联赛。
Oh, hopefully we get to talk about this later.
哦，希望我们以后能谈谈这个。
We're trying to break out of prison bitch
我们正试图越狱婊子
now. Oh, and you think this is more important?
现在。 哦，你认为这更重要吗？
OK, yeah. I see what your priorities are. Yeah.
好的，是的。 我知道你的优先事项是什么。 是的。
Yeah, that's right.
是的，没错。
Time know priorities are.
时间知道优先级是。
Oh, my God. Yes.
我的天啊。 是的。
Take them down. I see
把它们拿下来。 我懂了
I got help. You want help?
我得到了帮助。 你需要帮助吗？
You all know, you just.
你们都知道，你只是。
You killed him.
你杀了他。
He's dead.
他死了。
You like that from over
你喜欢从头到尾
while. OK.
尽管。 好的。
Now this. We're killing people.
现在这个。 我们在杀人。
Now there's no going back to his office.
现在再也回不了他的办公室了。
I guess we just got.
我想我们刚刚得到。
Yeah, there's somebody at the top, though, so we got to watch out for him.
是的，虽然上面有人，所以我们要小心他。
You just teleport on my screen.
你只是在我的屏幕上传送。
Oh, do.
哦，做。
You remember when we were here and I couldn't see the door?
你还记得我们在这里的时候，我看不见门吗？
We were looking at each other through the window. That's.
我们透过窗户看着对方。 那是。
And you told me to go back to get them up and then break it, and then you told.
你告诉我回去把它们弄起来然后打破它，然后你告诉我。
Me to come back. Oh, it's like we're going to do it again.
我要回来。 哦，这就像我们要再做一次。
Look at this.
看这个。
All good times.
所有美好的时光。
Good times.
美好的时光。
Oh, maybe I can lift you up when I get up.
哦，也许我起床时可以把你扶起来。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
One bend over.
一弯腰。
I got you. I got you bend over.
我接到你了。 我让你弯腰。
Bend over. Wait. How am I supposed to stop?
弯腰。 等待。 我该怎么停下来？
What are you doing, you idiot?
你在做什么，你这个白痴？
I'm trying to get out. How do I get out?
我正试图出去。 我怎么出去？
Each space
每个空间
maybe move back a little bit
也许后退一点
but you.
但是你。
You're, like, crouched over.
你，就像，蹲着。
What? All I have to look at.
什么？ 所有我要看的。
Oh, that's so dumb. Hey, you guy.
哦，这太愚蠢了。 嘿，你这家伙。
Thank you. Hey, babe.
谢谢你。 嘿，宝贝。
Thanks babe.
谢谢宝贝。
I saw your wife the other day.
前几天我见到了你的妻子。
What was that about that year? Yeah.
那一年是怎么回事？ 是的。
Are you looking at my wife?
你在看我老婆吗？
I'm just.
我只是。
I'm just. I just. I want to know your type.
我只是。 我只是。 我想知道你的类型。
Maybe I can.
也许我可以。
I could change for you.
我可以为你改变。
You know, you don't have to be over after.
你知道，你不必结束之后。
Could you grow up real quick?
你真的能快点长大吗？
Well, OK, let's cut out the kids.
好吧，好吧，让我们把孩子们剪掉。
You that?
你那个？
I don't think so. Age.
我不这么认为。 年龄。
That's the one. Pleasure.
那就是那个。 乐趣。
I know.
我知道。
He said you wouldn't want to visit.
他说你不想去。
What's wrong with Asia? It's great.
亚洲有什么问题？ 太好了。
You're so of the globe.
你是如此的地球。
You look good to.
你看起来不错。
Stop. You English.
停止。 你英语。
You're smart. You are. You're, like, easily.
你很聪明。 你是。 你很容易。
You're easily distractable.
你很容易分心。
You know that you're easily answer. To looking for so
你知道你很容易回答。 如此寻找
it is it is pretty cool. OK,
它很酷。 好的，
cool.
凉爽的。
I'm just saying, like, can you do it again?
我只是说，像，你能再做一次吗？
No. Continual only it's my turn.
不，只有轮到我了。
It's my tour. By.
这是我的旅行。 经过。
The Pacific Ocean.
太平洋。
What I wouldn't give to be there right now.
我不会放弃现在在那里。
Sticking my hand up your ass just.
把我的手伸到你的屁股上。
What I was thinking.
我在想什么。
Why can't I.
为什么我不能。
Sailing the Atlantic Ocean?
航行大西洋？
Oh, I'm tired sailing.
哦，我厌倦了航行。
How how do you how do I get. Out of this?
你怎么我怎么得到。 出这个？
Oh, my God. I'm sorry, tiger.
我的天啊。 对不起，老虎。
Are you looking at my boat? The yacht?
你在看我的船吗？ 游艇？
Although I was literally sticking my whole fist on us.
虽然我真的把我的整个拳头都粘在了我们身上。
You see that?
你看到了吗？
Can you do that till you do that to them? Position?
在你对他们这样做之前，你能做到吗？ 位置？
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Come on, come on.
好啦好啦。
Come on, come on, come on.
来吧，来吧，来吧。
Get out.
出去。
Oh, get over you. Like, maybe like the
哦，克服你。 像，也许像
excitement.
激动。
Oh, my God. We're the dirt ton.
我的天啊。 我们是肮脏的吨。
Oh, hello.
哦你好。
Why? What?
为什么？ 什么？
Why am I walking through the window like that fucking plane?
为什么我像那架该死的飞机一样穿过窗户？
Uh, it's probably an escape route, bruh.
呃，应该是逃生路线吧，嗯。
You're you move. Out of the way. Whoosh.
你是你动。 不碍事。 嗖。
All right,
好的，
we. I don't even know he's on the way.
我们。 我什至不知道他在路上。
Would you go? There you go. Oh, God.
你会去吗？ 你去吧。 天啊。
Careful.
小心。
The you to go through me again.
你又要经过我。
Incredible. I'm pop face clan.
极好的。 我是流行面孔氏族。
Nah. Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
不。 喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔噢
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, walk this way.
跑，跑，跑，跑，跑，跑，跑，跑，跑，这样走。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I just heard voices.
我刚刚听到声音。
I'm scared.
我害怕。
Ooh, where are we going, dude?
哦，我们要去哪里，伙计？
You hear? Double take down.
你听？ 双重取下。
Don't take, don't wear.
请勿服用，请勿佩戴。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Look, they're, like, lined up for it.
看，他们就像，排队等候。
See, it turned around hold on, hold on.
看，它转身等一下，等一下。
Yeah. Oh.
是的。 哦。
I played Assassin's Creed.
我玩过刺客信条。
I know a shit. Shit.
我知道一个狗屎。 拉屎。
I already told you.
我已经告诉过你。
All right, OK. Which one do you want to get? I'll get the.
好的，好的。 你想得到哪一个？ 我会得到的。
I'll get the one on the right. You get one on the left.
我会得到右边的那个。 你在左边得到一个。
OK, stop. OK. All right.
好的，停下来。 好的。 好的。
Ready? Yeah.
准备好？ 是的。
Yeah, I'm good. I'm good to. Go.
是的，我很好。 我很乐意。 去。
Whoa!
哇！
Oh! Hey! Get off the block. A few seconds.
哦！ 嘿！ 离开街区。 几秒钟。
Oh, you get you say get the one on the right.
哦，你知道你说拿右边的那个。
I was trying to get the one on the right.
我试图找到右边的那个。
Oh. Oh, wait.
哦。 等一下。
That was my right
那是我的权利
I but,
我可是，
OK, you know, let's not I don't want to talk about it.
好吧，你知道的，我们不要我不想谈论它。
I thought you said you said right. Right.
我以为你说的对。 对。
Or you said left.
或者你说左边。
Right, right. Right.
是的是的。 对。
He said you told me.
他说你告诉我的。
Get the one on the other side.
拿到另一边的那个。
The one down there. Right, right, right.
下面那个。 对对对。
I'll get the one. On the right. You get the one on the last.
我会得到那个。 在右侧。 你得到最后一个。
OK? OK.
好的？ 好的。
OK, sure.
好的。
Ready?
准备好？
Yeah, yeah, yeah. OK.
耶耶耶。 好的。
OK, nice. Nice. Wow.
好的，不错。 好的。 哇。
Oh, jeez.
哦，天哪。
What was that so hard?
有什么难的？
Oh, look at that.
哦，看那个。
They're holding hands.
他们手牵手。
They're holding. Hands. Like.
他们正在举行。 手。 像。
That's kind of romantic.
那是一种浪漫。
Yeah, they die together.
是的，他们一起死去。
Yeah. So.
是的。 所以。
Like, step on that corpse
就像，踩在那具尸体上
oh, fucking idiots.
哦，他妈的白痴。
I can't get through.
我过不去
I can't get through always.
我总是过不去。
Because you're in the way
因为你挡路了
all right. Be careful.
好的。 当心。
We don't get seen here.
我们在这里看不到。
There's a light.
有一盏灯。
There's literally no one around to worry about.
几乎没有人可以担心。
What are you talking about? There's no light.
你在说什么？ 没有光。
There's a fucking massive light.
有一个他妈的巨大的光。
Oh, that's what you meant.
哦，这就是你的意思。
I thought you were talking about, like, a police officer holding a light out at us.
我以为你在说，就像一个警察对着我们开灯。
Shit.
拉屎。
I need to get out.
我需要出去。
Oh, you are so.
哦，你就是这样。
Oh, my God. OK, you know what? You.
我的天啊。 好的，你知道吗？ 你。
No, I did not mean to do that.
不，我不是故意的。
I tried to crouch on sob unfollow bullock.
我试图蹲下啜泣着取消关注公牛。
Oh. Shit.
哦。 拉屎。
I need to get out of the searchlight.
我需要离开探照灯。
Oh, is it that way?
哦，是这样吗？
OK, ok.
好的好的。
We go down. That's it.
我们下去。 这就对了。
I need to get out of the way.
我需要让开。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I don't understand.
我不明白。
I literally don't understand why I.
我真的不明白为什么我。
I I didn't even try to.
我什至没有尝试。
Even try to get up. I even tried to get up.
甚至尝试起来。 我什至试着站起来。
Saying this thing are stupid.
说这件事是愚蠢的。
This guy is just shit. Stop
这家伙简直就是狗屎。 停止
calling me stupid.
骂我傻。
Oh, ok. At least I attempted.
哦好的。 至少我尝试过。
All right.
好的。
Is the answer in the light real fast.
答案真的很快吗？
You better watch out. Watch out.
你最好小心点。 小心。
You better watch out.
你最好小心点。
He doesn't see me shoot.
他没有看到我开枪。
Better watch out.
最好小心点。
You a you're lying.
你一个你在说谎。
I didn't I didn't move.
我没有，我没有动。
I did. Not move.
我做到了。 不动。
I did not move at all. I literally held it.
我根本没有动。 我真的拿着它。
Just really, really held it.
真的，真的握住了它。
Just the one I'm going to be stuck on.
只是我要坚持的那个。
No, it's not.
不它不是。
No, it's not enough. To hold you just for the president.
不，这还不够。 只为总统抱你。
Oh, I. Urge such pressure once.
哦，我。一次敦促这样的压力。
I had to hold it, that's why.
我不得不握住它，这就是原因。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
OK, well, that's good to know.
好的，很好，很高兴知道。
Go, go, go.
去！去！去。
Shit.
拉屎。
Why is this
为什么是这样
so slow?
太慢了？
Holy shit.
天啊。
Listen, I'm like, 40 something this dude's 40.
听着，我想，40 岁，这家伙 40 岁。
He give him some time, he had to wait up for me.
他给他一些时间，他不得不等我。
Holy shit.
天啊。
I swear to God,
我向天发誓，
yeah.
是的。
Have you stupid fucking drink?
你他妈喝过酒吗？
Have a get, get up.
吃饱，起来。
Hurry up, hurry up, you griever.
快点，快点，你这个悲伤的人。
Oh, my God, you fiend.
哦，我的上帝，你这个恶魔。
I need to get out of this.
我需要摆脱这一切。
You feel like you are you?
你觉得你就是你吗？
Oh, my God. You know, I'm just going to wait for you, OK?
我的天啊。 你知道，我只是等你，好吗？
You go first.
你先走。
You go first. First I go first.
你先走。 首先我先走。
Holy fuck,
他妈的，
I didn't see one shot.
我没有看到一个镜头。
Don't go.
别去。
No, no, no. No, no, no.
不不不。 不不不。
Are are
是
all right, I go.
好吧，我去。
Yeah, I go
是的，我去
ok. OK, good job.
行。 好的，干得好。
Good job, good job.
干得好，干得好。
Now you chill.
现在你冷静下来。
Only out like I'm sorry.
只是像我很抱歉一样。
I'm so good. I'm so glad a video games
我太好了。 我很高兴一个电子游戏这么好，一个你冷静的电子游戏。
Don't fucking die.
别他妈死。
The lights right there. Oh, my God.
灯就在那里。 我的天啊。
How did you don't get seen how.
你怎么没看到怎么。
I'm so going to video games.
我很想玩电子游戏。
How is that possible?
这怎么可能？
Watch this.
看这个。
Oh, gunshots. Duck, duck, duck. Watch this.
哦，枪声。 鸭，鸭，鸭。 看这个。
Ha ha ha.
哈哈哈。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Who is he? Who is he?
他是谁？ 他是谁？
Who is he?
他是谁？
Look at that.
看那个。
Oh, my. Easy, easy fucking game.
天啊。 简单，简单的他妈的游戏。
Easy fucking game. I'm going to kill this guy now.
简单的他妈的游戏。 我现在要杀了这个人。
Ok? OK.
好的？ 好的。
Can I please.
我可以请。
I can.
我可以。
Wait.
等待。
I even get up here ok?
我什至在这里起床好吗？
I got a good view of this.
我对此有很好的看法。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Look, I got one watch here so bad,
看，我这里有一只手表太糟糕了，
so I go I was.
所以我去我是。
Do you hear this?
你听到了吗？
I'm clicking. I was clicking it. Oh, ok.
我正在点击。 我正在点击它。 哦好的。
Then reset me. Think God.
然后重置我。 想想上帝。
All right, I want to.
好吧，我想要。
I want to get a view of this.
我想了解一下。
You go kill him, OK?
你去杀了他，好吗？
All right, try again.
好吧，再试一次。
Camera angle.
相机角度。
I think it's because I was crouching.
我想是因为我蹲着。
Yeah, I'm still crouching.
是的，我还在蹲着。
I get up there it's like sniffing his butt.
我爬上去就像在嗅他的屁股。
Oh, Ow,
哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦~
OK, push.
好，推。
No, I want to push him off.
不，我想推开他。
Yeah.
是的。
But outside.
但在外面。
I turn off the lights still. Isn't that.
我还是把灯关了。 是不是这样。
Isn't that.
是不是这样。
Hey, babe, you want to go and get your get your.
嘿，宝贝，你想去拿你的。
Wire we just need something to slide down.
电线我们只需要一些东西可以滑下来。
Slide on this.
滑动这个。
We need a coat hanger,
我们需要一个衣架，你知道吗？
Yeah, there's there coat. Hangers on here.
是的，那里有外套。 衣架在这里。
That's convenient. OK.
那很方便。 好的。
When I saw this in, like, fucking family
当我看到这个，就像，他妈的家庭男人或什么狗屎。
Fucking family guy.
他妈的家庭人。
Oh, maybe this was.
哦，也许是这样。
Someone with box inside.
里面有盒子的人。
Oh, yeah, it's a buddy.
哦，对了，是朋友。
We was on Bart Simpson.
我们在巴特辛普森。
Family Guy.
家庭男。
Raoul
拉乌尔
I can't slide down.
我不能滑下来。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, I can't wait for you.
哦，我等不及你了。
It's not fun. I want to slide with you.
这不好玩。 我想和你一起滑。
I can't.
我不能。
Oh, no, oh, no.
哦，不，哦，不。
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。 不好了。
Look. Oh, my God. Oh, oh,
看。 我的天啊。 哦，哦，
shit.
拉屎。
Oh, my God. They know. They know.
我的天啊。 他们知道。 他们知道。
They know. They know.
他们知道。 他们知道。
No, he's shooting you here.
不，他在这里向你开枪。
Shooting you. Oh.
射击你。 哦。
Come on, come on.
好啦好啦。
Keep holding, keep holding, keep holding, keep holding. Oh.
坚持住，坚持住，坚持住，坚持住。 哦。
I'm going to get shot, danger.
我要中枪了，危险。
I'm trying you.
我在试你。
Yeah.
是的。
Well, he's had us so bad, the aim is just terrible.
好吧，他对我们太糟糕了，目标太糟糕了。
Oh, my.
天啊。
God. Oh,
上帝。 哦，
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，哦，哦。
Guess.
猜测。
Stop the bullets. Oh, yeah.
停止子弹。 哦耶。
We dodged the bullet.
我们躲过了子弹。
Dodged the bullet.
躲过了子弹。
Yeah, they're actually.
是的，他们实际上是。
They actually want to kill us.
他们实际上想杀了我们。
No, it's good.
不，很好。
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
走，走，走，走，走，走。
Oh, no. This is bad.
不好了。 这是不好的。
Is bad, dude.
很糟糕，伙计。
You sound like such a turkey.
你听起来像一只火鸡。
Oh, boy.
好家伙。
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
Oh, my God. Easy, easy game.
我的天啊。 轻松，轻松的游戏。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Easy fucking games.
简单的他妈的游戏。
Look, good.
看起来不错。
That was first try. First try.
那是第一次尝试。 第一次尝试。
It was that. Easy to escape from prison?
就是这样。 越狱容易吗？
Is that it?
是这样吗？
Keep that in mind.
记住这一点。
There's no way.
不可能。
That's it.
这就对了。
And that's how we got into Fortnite Battle Bus.
这就是我们进入 Fortnite Battle Bus 的方式。
What's that?
那是什么？
OK, the truth I'm not quite sure.
好吧，事实我不太确定。
You know.
你知道。
You can make me choke on my water.
你可以让我被水呛到。
What about it?
怎么样？
Did you do that when you were a kid?
你小时候做过吗？
Nope.
没有。
What do what?
做什么做什么？
When I was a kid, I saw. It in a comic book once when I was a kid.
小时候看过。 小时候漫画里有一次。
Tell me your joke.
告诉我你的笑话。
No, I'm just glad it worked.
不，我很高兴它奏效了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I can't fucking believe you talked me into it.
我他妈的不敢相信你把我说服了。
How we get into a helicopter.
我们如何进入直升机。
Me neither.
我也不。
Or this is a helicopter right now.
或者这是一架直升机。
It's a plane. A copter.
这是一架飞机。 一架直升机。
It has, like, wings and the front, the one with the spinning.
它有，就像，翅膀和前部，一个有旋转的。
I I want to choke you.
我想掐死你。
That.
那。
That's fine.
没事儿。
You like that kind of stuff? That chopper?
你喜欢那种东西？ 那个直升机？
Yeah.
是的。
I prefer choking, but we really piss them off.
我更喜欢窒息，但我们真的很生气。
Oh, God. They're losing everything they've got.
天啊。 他们正在失去他们所拥有的一切。
We have to be careful.
我们必须小心。
Yeah. Why am I following you?
是的。 我为什么跟着你？
Fine, Leo. Fine. Vincent.
好的，狮子座。 美好的。 文森特。
What am I?
我是什么？
Larry, you're right here.
拉里，你就在这里。
You're in front of me.
你在我面前。
Why what do you mean, fine?
为什么你的意思，好吗？
Leo, you're, like, right in front of my face.
狮子座，你就像，就在我面前。
Hey, what if I hide in here?
嘿，如果我躲在这里呢？
Oh, no, I don't think you are. Oh, shit.
哦，不，我不认为你是。 妈的。
I don't care. Right. And here.
我不在乎。 对。 和这里。
You go.
你去。
This is for it.
这是为了它。
Now, you what
现在，你什么
yeah.
是的。
We're in the new seise the fort. Like,
我们在新的夺取堡垒。 比如，我们走吧。
E Oh.
哦。
I'm just going to sit here.
我只是要坐在这里。
Hey, why clapping on me, bro? To send me.
嘿，为什么要为我鼓掌，兄弟？ 寄给我。
You offered.
你提供了。
I was just.
我只是。
You offered. Get your butt. Off here now.
你提供了。 得到你的屁股。 现在离开这里。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
What happened to my floral shirt and this?
我的花衬衫怎么了？
That there are cops everywhere.
到处都有警察。
Uh. Yeah.
呃。 是的。
The game realised it wasn't drip come on.
游戏意识到它不是滴水来的。
I had more drip than you.
我滴的比你多。
So much more.
这么多。
Spit on the from more drip.
吐在从更多滴。
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
Yes, of course.
是的当然。
That would better than we kill him.
那比我们杀了他要好。
They don't see us in the bushes because that dumb
他们在灌木丛中看不到我们，因为那个愚蠢
I will kill them right now.
我现在就杀了他们。
OK? OK, Assassin's Creed II fucking.
好的？ 好吧，刺客信条II他妈的。
I'm glad we get this guy.
我很高兴我们得到了这个人。
Oh, this is fucking easy.
哦，这太他妈容易了。
Easy way. How does he not see me?
简单的方法。 他怎么看不到我？
How does he not see me?
他怎么看不到我？
Took to the streets.
走上街头。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
We. Oh, my God.
我们。 我的天啊。
His arm
他的胳膊
dude.
老兄。
Fuck that kid.
去他妈的那个孩子。
He died.
他死了。
Do you miss this offer?
你想念这个优惠吗？
Blood right now?
马上血？
I am.
我是。
I just only. I got one. Yeah, away from.
我只是而已。 我得到了一个。 是的，远离。
I love the taste of blood.
我喜欢血的味道。
However we have to do another.
然而，我们必须做另一个。
Another double.
另一个双。
OK, let me write you laughs.
好吧，让我写给你笑。
Same time. OK, great.
同时。 好的，不错。
Or are you.
或者你是。
I'm. I'm on my way, ok?
我是。 我在路上，好吗？
I'm not as fast as I'm guessing. Bones.
我没有我想象的那么快。 骨头。
It's Vincent.
是文森特。
Hello. Hello.
你好。 你好。
Hello? Oh, my God.
你好？ 我的天啊。
What did you come from? Hello? Wait, wait, wait.
你是什​​么来的？ 你好？ 等等，等等，等等。
Why are you coming with me, you bitch?
你为什么跟我来，你这个婊子？
What you saying? I'll go wait for you.
你在说什么？ 我去等你。
Come on.
来吧。
You were waiting for me.
你在等我。
You said I get the love. You get the right.
你说我得到了爱。 你说对了。
You got to go, go, go, go, go, go.
你得走，走，走，走，走，走。
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走。
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走。
I grab my damn.
我抓住我的该死的。
That's the animation went off on my screen.
那就是我的屏幕上的动画。
Oh, my. God. Did that.
天啊。 上帝。 做过某事。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Miss Star.
星小姐。
OK again.
再次确定。
Yeah, this is. Wait, wait.
是的，这是。 等等。
OK, ready? Go.
准备好了？ 去。
Nice,
好的，
easy teamwork. Yeah.
轻松的团队合作。 是的。
That's good, man.
那很好，伙计。
That's that's collaboration.
那就是合作。
That's teamwork.
那就是团队合作。
I love.
我爱。
Collaboration.
合作。
I like your face.
我喜欢你的脸。
How many cops I know. Thanks.
我认识多少警察。 谢谢。
Just keep your head low.
只是低着头。
That's all I get is thanks they got man here.
这就是我得到的只是感谢他们在这里找到了人。
Oh, thank you.
哦谢谢。
What's a lot of people? That's a lot of people.
什么是很多人？ 那是很多人。
I need you to get Johnson over there at the booth.
我需要你把约翰逊带到展位那边。
Well, if I say Johnson. He could do man.
好吧，如果我说约翰逊。 他可以做人。
He could do it back up from the sheriff.
他可以从治安官那里得到支持。
Well, all right,
好吧，好吧，
well, I'll see us
好吧，我会看到我们
hello?
你好？
There's one.
有一个。
No, you.
不，你。
Because you shot down.
因为你击落了。
He hit me on the head.
他打我的头。
Hands above your head.
双手举过头顶。
Oh, my God. Straight up.
我的天啊。 直接上。
Thinks me deserves a name.
认为我应该得到一个名字。
Here, here. Man.
这儿这儿。 男人。
I'm running.
我在跑步。
And I'm gonna kill over there.
我要去那里杀人。
This one's mine. You can't have this kind of spying.
这是我的。 你不能有这种间谍活动。
No, it's mine. It's mine.
不，是我的。 这是我的。
Why are you so much faster than me?
为什么你比我快那么多？
Why are you so much smarter than me? Fuck all.
为什么你比我聪明那么多？ 去他妈的。
You're a bitch.
你是个婊子。
I'm going to agree with you.
我会同意你的。
I'm going to go and get caught right now.
我现在要去被抓住。
Oh, yes. Coming right now? Yes.
哦是的。 马上来？ 是的。
I wanted that kill.
我想要那个杀戮。
Hey, I will.
嘿，我会的。
I'll get caught right now.
我马上就会被抓住。
Wait.
等待。
I don't think we're supposed to go this way.
我不认为我们应该走这条路。
I'm not going to.
我不会。
Yeah, we're not supposed to go this way.
是的，我们不应该走这条路。
I like my eyes.
我喜欢我的眼睛。
Yeah, I know.
是的，我知道。
You're looking at it every 40 seconds.
您每 40 秒查看一次。
Oh, you can see my screen. Yes.
哦，你可以看到我的屏幕。 是的。
Thank you. Yeah.
谢谢你。 是的。
This entire time I could see your skin.
这整个时间我可以看到你的皮肤。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Um, it's been like this for the past 2 hours, babe.
嗯，过去2个小时都是这样，宝贝。
I've had
我已经有了
I've had my bad.
我有我的坏。
OK, let's go out here and see my wife.
好，我们出去看看我的妻子。
I can't wait to get out here and see my child
我迫不及待地想出去看看我的孩子还在我的妻子我的妹妹体内。
My wife.
我的妻子。
If you dare shut off.
如果你敢关机。
That's why your wife.
这就是为什么你的妻子。
Is giving birth to the baby.
正在生孩子。
Just sister
只是妹妹
I'm so tired out, guys.
我太累了，伙计们。
I'm so tired.
我很累。
I'm so tired already.
我已经很累了。
Is is.
伊斯兰国。
Hiding under a. Rock somewhere. Anyway.
躲在a下。 在某处摇滚。 反正。
I've had enough. I've had enough. Mysta..
我已经受够了。 我已经受够了。 米斯塔..
I'm going to get on the other side where how do I get on the.
我要去另一边我怎么上去。
Other side or. Get on the other side?
另一边或。 去另一边？
Oh, get over here. The dump.
哦，到这里来。 垃圾场。
Nothing beats being dumped.
没有什么比被抛弃更重要的了。
I need your help. No, I don't.
我需要你的帮助。 不，我没有。
Do we doing OK over that?
我们在这方面做得好吗？
Why? You got
为什么？ 你得到了
no way.
没门。
No, I want to talk to you. I want to go with you.
不，我想和你谈谈。 我想和你一起去。
I'm going over here. Then. Stay.
我要去这里。 然后。 停留。
Stay, dog.
留下来，狗。
Stay down, boy.
趴下，男孩。
OK, stay there.
好的，呆在那里。
Ha ha ha ha oh, my God.
哈哈哈哈我的天
Oh, OK. Go, go, go, go. I'm pharmacy.
哦好的。 去去去去。 我是药房。
I just want to see your face. And no way. I want to go back up.
我只是想看看你的脸。 而且没办法。 我想回去。
We don't go back up.
我们不回去。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
OK, ok. Sorry. I didn't mean.
好的好的。 对不起。 我不是这个意思。
I did not actually mean to go down that time.
那时我实际上并没有打算下去。
You've been a blast, dog.
你是一个爆炸，狗。
OK, you ready?
好的，你准备好了吗？
You're right. Three, two, two. One.
你说的对。 三，二，二。 一。
That freaks you just and freaks you 71.
这让你吓坏了，让你吓坏了 71。
I thought we do got one. You didn't even say one.
我以为我们确实有一个。 你一个都没说。
You said three, two, three.
你说三，二，三。
I said one.
我说一个。
No, I think live.
不，我认为是生活。
I said one, I said one. I said one.
我说一个，我说一个。 我说一个。
Shut all I said one in the morning.
闭嘴我早上说的一个。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
I'm going to run. OK, I could do it again. All right.
我要跑了。 好的，我可以再做一次。 好的。
Three, two, one.
三二一。
Michael, is that easy?
迈克尔，这容易吗？
It's that easy. Ba Oh.
就这么容易。 巴哦。
I need any more tea. Any more tea?
我需要更多的茶。 还有茶吗？
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Yeah, well, audible water.
是的，嗯，听得见的水。
Well.
好。
The OK,
好的，
you are you ok?
你还好吗？
With the gargle? Yes.
用漱口水？ 是的。
Yeah, sure.
当然可以。
Sound like you're in something there.
听起来你好像身处其中。
OK, cool.
嗯不错。
I'm going to climb up here.
我要爬上这里。
Oh, I need to give you a boost again because it's so tiny.
哦，我需要再给你一个动力，因为它太小了。
Small, so small.
小，那么小。
My form is like, non.
我的形式是，非。
Not even joking.
甚至不开玩笑。
I'm so much bigger than you.
我比你大很多。
Oh, yeah? How tall are you?
哦耶？ 你有多高？
Shove my balls in your face.
把我的蛋蛋推到你脸上。
That's a lot.
那是很多。
Big speed limit is 35.
大限速是35。
I know you got neutered.
我知道你绝育了。
That's not we.
那不是我们。
What is getting neutered, dammit.
什么是绝育，该死的。
Oh, this is it, really.
哦，原来如此。
Snip, snip.
剪，剪。
Snip, snip under the bridge.
剪断，在桥下剪断。
Oh, that's so size nipple.
哦，那是这么大的乳头。
It's way too high.
它太高了。
Yeah, but you can't come anymore.
是的，但你不能再来了。
But can, can you still bulk up?
但是可以，你还能胖起来吗？
Yes, of course.
是的当然。
But you just.
但你只是。
Can't nothing is produce.
不可能什么都生产。
You nuts, man. OK. Let's see.
你疯了，伙计。 好的。 让我们来看看。
I don't know how he works.
我不知道他是如何工作的。
Oh, wait. You under the bridge?
等一下。 你在桥下？
Are way we can choose?
我们可以选择的方式吗？
Which one do we want to do?
我们想做哪一个？
I don't mind. Over under the bridge.
我不介意。 在桥下。
Go over the bridge.
过桥。
Do you want me a top or bottom base itself?
你想要我一个顶部或底部基地本身？
Let's come.
让我们来。
Connelly sweetie, why is mine under?
康纳利宝贝，为什么我的在下面？
I I mean, makes sense.
我的意思是，有道理。
You know, you're like, you know.
你知道，你就像，你知道的。
You are ballsy. You are so ballsy.
你是个胆小鬼。 你太牛了。
That's why I'm the top.
这就是为什么我是顶级的。
Telling you this is going to work.
告诉你这是行得通的。
Just jump in the back and stay.
只是跳到后面留下来。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I can't believe this is what we're doing right now. What?
我不敢相信这就是我们现在正在做的事情。 什么？
You're driving. You put up the police car
你在开车。 你放了警车
this is, like, so dumb.
这就像，太愚蠢了。
What? We're going to get coverage.
什么？ 我们将获得报道。
I run him over. Run him over.
我把他碾过去。 把他碾过去。
You think you want me.
你以为你想要我。
You so stupid with your hat on?
你戴帽子就这么傻？
Oh, my God. Why did he dive that way?
我的天啊。 他为什么要那样潜水？
Even what it's like in the way he was scared.
甚至是他害怕的样子。
Anyone over there?
有人在那边吗？
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。 不好了。 不好了。
Oh, no, miss that we. Fucked up we walked out.
哦，不，想念我们。 操蛋我们走了出去。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Where are we going? What?
我们去哪？ 什么？
We're going.
我们要走了。
And don't worry.
别担心。
You're going on a trip and out there.
你要去旅行，然后出去。
Good shit. Oh.
好狗屎。 哦。
All according to plan.
一切按计划进行。
This is your fault.
这是你的错。
Your fucking fault. I'm a detective.
你他妈的错。 我是一名侦探。
I finds the best ways out.
我找到了最好的出路。
Look at that. See that?
看那个。 看到了吗？
No, it's fine, but oh, my God.
不，这很好，但是哦，我的上帝。
Thank you, dogs. That's also coming. The dogs are coming.
谢谢你，狗。 那也即将到来。 狗来了。
You're not with me.
你不在我身边。
Where are you?
你在哪里？
I'm just running. I'm just running.
我只是在跑步。 我只是在跑步。
Stuffing ducks. How are we alive after that?
填鸭。 在那之后我们还怎么活着？
They're on the slow.
他们走得很慢。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh. Oh, come on, do something.
哦。 哦，来吧，做点什么。
Describe the dogs.
描述狗。
Now. Let's stop.
现在。 我们停止吧。
Oh, oh, get off.
哦，哦，下车。
You know, I'm showing.
你知道，我在展示。
Who killed you.
谁杀了你。
Why are you running?
你为何跑？
He fucking kill you.
他他妈的杀了你。
There was a shit.
有一个狗屎。
Just Matt. Just spell it.
只是马特。 拼一下就行了。
Just spam it easy.
只是垃圾邮件很容易。
I kicked out.
我踢出去了。
I'll catch you.
我会抓到你。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Yeah, I'll catch you. I'll catch you.
是的，我会抓住你的。 我会抓到你。
I promise.
我保证。
Oh. This is a very nice trip.
哦。 这是一次非常愉快的旅行。
Yeah. We got to get out of here. Oh.
是的。 我们必须离开这里。 哦。
Oh, wait and watch.
哦，等着看。
Catch me, baby.
抓住我，宝贝。
Oh, my God. What happened to you?
我的天啊。 你怎么了？
That's me, baby. That's.
那就是我，宝贝。 那是。
Holy shit.
天啊。
You look like you slid off and fell.
你看起来像滑倒了。
Really?
真的吗？
Yeah.
是的。
And that was, like, the slowest slide ever.
那就像，有史以来最慢的幻灯片。
Shit. Dammit.
拉屎。 该死。
Almost.
几乎。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Well, if I didn't catch you there, dammit.
好吧，如果我没有在那儿抓到你，该死的。
And I would have died.
我会死的。
But maybe I wanted to see that.
但也许我想看看。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I'll keep that in mind. OK?
我会记住这一点。 好的？
I mean, I didn't do it, though.
我的意思是，虽然我没有这样做。
I didn't follow through.
我没有跟进。
I could have the thoughts about it, but I didn't follow through with it, you know?
我可以有关于它的想法，但我没有坚持下去，你知道吗？
Huh, uh huh.
呵呵呵。
Like, wow.
比如，哇。
Hey, man, I.
嘿，伙计，我。
Just tell him this is the deal.
只是告诉他这是交易。
This is part of the mind. Oh, no, I got it.
这是头脑的一部分。 哦，不，我明白了。
It's Harvey Dent into notice.
哈维·登特引起了人们的注意。
Did he go down? She grabbed my
他下去了吗？ 她抓住了我的
hand, and.
手，和。
I like his hair.
我喜欢他的头发。
It's like Jamma.
这就像贾玛。
He says, no, there's too much risk.
他说，不，风险太大。
Well, it's not going to happen.
好吧，这不会发生。
But listen, I was not going to have Harvey.
但是听着，我不会有哈维。
I need to wait
我需要等待
OK? Fucking Jeremiah.
好的？ 该死的耶利米。
This.
这。
Look.
看。
Take the deal or stop wasting my time.
接受交易或停止浪费我的时间。
All right?
好的？
Yeah. OK.
是的。 好的。
What's up?
怎么了？
Lee, you busted out of prison. What?
李，你出狱了。 什么？
I just got the call.
我刚接到电话。
Isn't he supposed to be dead?
他不是应该死了吗？
A guy fucked up, got himself killed by the guard's.
一个人搞砸了，自己被守卫杀死了。
Good for nothing.
没事便是好事。
Piece of shit.
一坨屎。
Sorry. Boss.
对不起。 老板。
Look, Sean, we need to find him.
听着，肖恩，我们需要找到他。
I'll come tomorrow morning.
我明天早上会来。
Who, me?
谁，我？
Why are you my name? Who, me? My problem.
你为什么叫我的名字？ 谁，我？ 我的问题。
Yeah, you.
是的你。
I'm clearing my throat.
我清了清嗓子。
I don't give a fuck. How?
我不在乎。 如何？
Just make it happen.
只要让它发生。
I need to clear my throat. All right. Yes.
我需要清清嗓子。 好的。 是的。
So you decided I need us
所以你决定我需要我们
OK? No deal.
好的？ 没有成交。
Whoa! Oh, my God.
哇！ 我的天啊。
He has a gold gun.
他有一把金枪。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Oh, my God. Is this bougie
我的天啊。 这是布吉吗
He's really wavy.
他真的很波浪。
He had to complete all of the
他必须完成所有的皮肤挑战才能做到这一点。
Is this. Is this a Cisco reference?
这是。 这是思科的参考吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I don't see or call anything.
我没有看到或呼叫任何东西。
I don't know. I don't play.
我不知道。 我不玩。
I don't play those games. Really?
我不玩那些游戏。 真的吗？
Cisco I don't play it.
思科我不玩它。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
I only play like.
我只玩喜欢。
Violence and.
暴力和。
It's.
它的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
It's Skyrim.
这是天际。
It's professional.
这是专业的。
Wild damn dumb-ass. I'm hungry. Me too.
疯狂的该死的笨蛋。 我饿了。 我也是。
Was that DLC?
是那个DLC吗？
I missed that shitty food.
我错过了那个糟糕的食物。
We got to go over hungry. I'll show you some food.
我们得饿着肚子过去。 我会给你看一些食物。
But I definitely.
但我绝对。
Yeah, I mean, we probably can get. Some food anyway.
是的，我的意思是，我们可能会得到。 反正有点吃的。
Let me.
让我来。
I guess. Let me baby. Something on the. Way.
我猜。 让我宝贝 上的东西。 方式。
I got some cake for
我有一些蛋糕
dessert.
甜点。
I can't get them out.
我不能把它们弄出来。
Before we got the full meal right. Here.
在我们得到正确的全餐之前。 这里。
I mean, look at it right now.
我的意思是，现在看。
All right.
好的。
You do that.
你做吧。
This is actually really beautiful.
这实际上真的很漂亮。
What the hell?
我勒个去？
I, I thought we were going to be spending most of our time in the prison.
我，我以为我们会在监狱里度过大部分时间。
This is odd.
这很奇怪。
I didn't think we were going to be outside
我没想到我们会在外面
Why are we here?
我们为什么在这里？
Who am I?
我是谁？
Where are you?
你在哪里？
Huh? Huh huh huh?
嗯？ 嗯嗯？
Oh, well, you teleporter.
哦，好吧，你这个传送器。
Behind me.
在我后面。
On my will not let me show
我不会让我给你看的。
Those incredible
那些不可思议
phasing in and out.
逐步进入和退出。
I on the.
我上。
Simulator.
模拟器。
This is actually touching grass.
这其实是摸草。
I think shy lily sent me that
我想害羞的百合给我发了那个
I saw that.
我看到了。
Came on steam.
来的蒸汽。
I don't know what that's about.
我不知道那是关于什么的。
Why are you going to play it?
你为什么要玩它？
No, I'm going to play.
不，我要去玩。
Touching grass simulates a well, what I play that.
摸草模拟一口井，我玩那个。
I'll. I think it might help.
患病的。 我认为这可能会有所帮助。
Oh, I touched grass. A lot, actually.
哦，我摸到草了。 很多，其实。
Yeah, I got a deal.
是的，我达成了协议。
I try to touch grass at least once a month.
我试着每个月至少摸一次草。
As a streamer.
作为流光。
That's a lot. To be fair.
那是很多。 公平起见。
There's a camp down there.
下面有一个营地。
My. You know, I'm proud of you.
我的。 你知道，我为你感到骄傲。
Good job. At least you're touching grass.
做得好。 至少你在摸草。
Yeah, you're probably right.
是的，你可能是对的。
At least you're touching grass and not such a nice, you know?
至少你在摸草而不是那么好，你知道吗？
I mean, you could probably touch your ass.
我的意思是，你可能会碰你的屁股。
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
Well, if your ass was full of grass,
好吧，如果你的屁股全是草，
then I would be. Touching my.
那么我会的。 抚摸我的。
Own grass.
自己的草。
I'm gonna have more of that ass of a lawn mower.
我将拥有更多的割草机。
Right? Right.
对？ 对。
Oh, my God. That's like, few times.
我的天啊。 就像，几次。
Final destination, death scene.
最终目的地，死亡现场。
Jesus. My uncle actually.
耶稣。 原来是我舅舅。
Played in Splash last
最后在 Splash 中播放
got a.
有一个。
Perfectly. Good I love what's hot.
完美。 很好，我喜欢热的东西。
Lol and getting your pants right and in your pants. What
大声笑，让你的裤子穿对了。 什么
you stupid.
你这个笨蛋。
Why do we look so stupid.
为什么我们看起来如此愚蠢。
Oh, I look.
哦，我看。
Like a Pokémon and.
像神奇宝贝和。
I'm flying.
我在飞翔。
Cooking over anal you. Oh, God, it.
在肛门上做饭。 哦，天哪，它。
Mostly do you.
主要是你。
Say that?
比如说？
Well, it's.
嗯，是的。
Well, let's shower with it.
好吧，让我们用它洗澡。
I want to stick my head in your ass.
我想把头伸进你的屁股。
Oh, my back and like, give you a blowjob.
哦，我的背和喜欢，给你一个口交。
Oh, by the way, can you do it?
哦，顺便说一句，你能做到吗？
Do it again.
再来一遍。
Well,
好，
goddamn it.
他妈的。
Grab the fish. I think we're supposed to grab fish.
抓住鱼。 我想我们应该去抓鱼。
Oh, right. Yeah. Go the other way. Go the other way.
啊对。 是的。 走另一条路。 走另一条路。
We're supposed to drop them, you know?
我们应该放弃它们，你知道吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Oh, pincer them into one spot.
哦，把它们夹在一个地方。
Go and fish. Where you going?
去钓鱼。 你去哪里？
Okay.
好的。
What the fuck.
什么鬼。
Do they just one pass you.
他们只是一个通过你。
Some of those swimming into the rocks.
其中一些游入岩石中。
I'm not supposed to do this.
我不应该这样做。
Light fire.
点火。
Catch one fish each. How?
每人钓一条鱼。 如何？
What?
什么？
How are we supposed to catch fish like
我们应该怎么钓到这样的鱼
I feel like I'm missing something.
我觉得我错过了什么。
I mean, this fire is not yet, is it?
我的意思是，这火还没有，是吗？
No, it's not.
不它不是。
Spear. Oh.
矛。 哦。
Are you kidding.
你在开玩笑吗。
Me? You. You made us look like idiots.
我？ 你。 你让我们看起来像白痴。
I thought we were supposed to, like, grab it off our hands for the fire.
我想我们应该，比如，把它从我们的手上拿下来生火。
This isn't fire enough for the fire.
这火还不够火。
Almost there.
差不多好了。
Oh, I need more wood for the fire.
哦，我需要更多的木头生火。
Wood for the fire.
生火用的木头。
Wait for the fire.
等着火。
Get some more wood, bitch.
多弄点木头，婊子。
All right, I'll get the word.
好吧，我会得到消息的。
You get the meal.
你得到饭菜。
All right. Blowing and blowing.
好的。 吹着吹着。
Oh, this
哦，这就像以前的穴居人对待他们的妻子一样。
What? Blowing?
什么？ 吹？
No, like, one of them's going to, like, spear.
不，就像，他们中的一个会像长矛一样。
The other one's going to prepare for the food for it.
另一个人会为它准备食物。
How do I get there?
我如何到达那里？
I think I need your help over here.
我想我在这里需要你的帮助。
Yeah, we go. Yeah.
是的，我们去。 是的。
Come on. Herd. Herd the fish over.
来吧。 放牧。 把鱼赶过来。
Bring them to me.
把它们带给我。
All right, all right. All right.
好吧，好吧。 好的。
I think.
我认为。
Stand still. Yeah, yeah, I'll stay still.
站着不动。 是的，是的，我会保持不动。
I'm sharpening my tools again.
我又在磨我的工具了。
I'm comin.
我来了
Oh, I don't even need you.
哦，我什至不需要你。
I didn't even need you, bitch.
我什至不需要你，婊子。
Look, that free fish.
看，那条免费的鱼。
Yeah, I don't need you.
是的，我不需要你。
Ever watch the ship?
有没有看船？
Oh. Yeah, I can throw it.
哦。 是的，我可以扔。
No, you don't throw it.
不，你不要扔它。
You just got to starve. Them when they're underneath. Yeah,
你只得饿死。 当他们在下面时。 是的，
I know.
我知道。
They eat my fish.
他们吃我的鱼。
I watch the ship.
我看船。
You. Yeah, I'll wait for you.
你。 是的，我会等你。
I'll wait for you.
我会等你的。
Be courteous. OK?
要有礼貌。 好的？
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
I'm waiting.
我在等。
We are waiting for the fish to come in.
我们在等鱼上来。
You're not going to come. Swords?
你不会来的。 剑？
I was
我曾是
come on.
来吧。
How do I get it?
我如何得到它？
How did you get it?
你是如何得到的？
I got. Lucky.
我有。 幸运的。
I think.
我认为。
Oh. Well,
哦。 好，
I can't stop laughing.
我忍不住笑了。
I just can't
我就是不能
it's so funny.
太有趣了。
This is a fad so fast.
这是一种如此迅速的时尚。
So quick.
这么快。
Bob, I got this one.
鲍勃，我得到了这个。
Stupid fish. Oh, my God.
傻鱼。 我的天啊。
Oh, my God. You got it.
我的天啊。 你说对了。
Dan, let's go. Oh, shit.
丹，我们走吧。 妈的。
Let's go. Well, you were just sitting there.
我们走吧。 好吧，你只是坐在那里。
Yeah, I was walking also.
是的，我也在走路。
I was. I'm.
我曾是。 我是。
I'm way eating for you.
我正在为你吃东西。
So we can eat together.
这样我们就可以一起吃饭了。
She could have helped me.
她本可以帮助我的。
You could have helped me. Oh.
你本来可以帮助我的。 哦。
You just eat your fish sticks.
你只吃你的鱼条。
They stick where I don't even get to eat it.
它们粘在我什至无法吃到的地方。
That tasted like shit, man.
那味道像狗屎，伙计。
Huh? Well, you know, it is what it is.
嗯？ 嗯，你知道，它就是这样。
It is what it is.
就是这样。
And I fucking feel
我他妈的觉得
you complain. What
你抱怨。 什么
I I'm good.
我我很好。
Really?
真的吗？
So we're going to do this now, huh?
所以我们现在要这样做，对吧？
You come. In a. Lot now, huh?
你来。 在一个。 现在很多吧？
Vince is just like.
文斯就是这样。
Yeah, well, I don't really like your attitude.
是啊，好吧，我不是很喜欢你的态度。
What are you in for? You're very snarky all the time.
你来干什么？ 你总是很狡猾。
You know, I don't know why you need to clean.
你知道，我不知道你为什么需要清洁。
Your nose in nice clean. You're used to.
你的鼻子很干净。 你习惯了。
You have no dry all the time.
你一直没有干。
I mean, I look at my collared shirt.
我的意思是，我看看我的领衬衫。
What do you have, bitch?
你有什么，婊子？
It's just a white t shirt.
这只是一件白色的T恤。
I have layers.
我有层次。
You know about layers. You watch Shrek.
你知道图层。 你看史莱克。
You probably don't want Shrek.
你可能不想要史莱克。
Back to basics.
回归本源。
Get with the times, bitch. You
与时俱进，婊子。 你
the kiss you so hard on the face later.
后来吻你的脸那么用力。
Alex.
亚历克斯。
Oh, you set my face
哦，你让我的脸
right into my.
直接进入我的。
Mouth, man.
嘴巴，伙计。
Yeah.
是的。
Did you see my face
你看到我的脸了吗
I. Got to get.
I. 得到。
They look as they are.
他们看起来像他们一样。
Ha! Wow! OK,
哈！ 哇！ 好的，
all right.
好的。
I was surprised.
我很惊讶。
That they got a logo in Daddy's lap is free.
他们在爸爸的腿上得到一个标志是免费的。
One day my brother brings in a new client.
有一天，我哥哥带来了一位新客户。
I rather take a log than that tiny peep money you have.
我宁愿拿日志也不愿你有的那点小钱。
Yeah,
是的，
money was easy,
赚钱很容易，但哈维总是带着越来越多的现金进来，我无法应付。
It was too risky, so I told them I wanted out.
这太冒险了，所以我告诉他们我想出去。
Emotional.
情绪化的。
Damage, like brother as a warning.
损坏，就像兄弟一样警告。
After that, I lost it.
在那之后，我失去了它。
I planned on killing him,
我打算杀了他，但这个王八蛋却把这一切都寄托在了我身上。
I feel like we missed out on, like, a good important.
我觉得我们错过了，就像，一个很好的重要。
Part of murder.
谋杀的一部分。
Because I'm lost right now. Wow.
因为我现在迷路了。 哇。
Fucking rough, man. Mysta..
他妈的粗鲁，伙计。 米斯塔..
Yes. Man.
是的。 男人。
So sorry.
非常抱歉。
Why are you so sad?
你为什么这么伤心？
So messed up?
这么乱？
What's your story with Harvey, huh?
你和哈维有什么故事，嗯？
I saw you get you good. Yeah, I'm good.
我看到你让你好。 是的，我很好。
I'm good.
我很好。
OK, ok. I'm good.
好的好的。 我很好。
You're is good.
你是好的。
Yes. Nice. Compact.
是的。 好的。 袖珍的。
Compact. That's the right word.
袖珍的。 那是正确的词。
Thank you for closing in.
谢谢你关门。
We got to move.
我们得搬家了。
Oh, my fucking feet.
哦，我他妈的脚。
See? There you go. Complaining again about. It.
看？ 你去吧。 再次抱怨。 它。
I got it. OK.
我得到了它。 好的。
You know.
你知道。
Do you want me to rub your front OK? Sure.
你要我擦你的前脸好吗？ 当然。
You're aware of your feet.
你知道你的脚。
You can rub your feet as an apology.
你可以揉脚作为道歉。
I'll rub your feet
我会揉你的脚
a little. You're telling me. You suck my toes?
一点。 你在告诉我。 你吸我的脚趾？
Yeah. You
是的。 你
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You know me so well.
你真了解我。
And I'm kind of forced to.
我有点被迫这样做。
So you used to work in a bank.
所以你以前在银行工作。
Oh, is that how it is?
哦，是这样的吗？
What are you implying?
你在暗示什么？
Look at me.
看着我。
Well, to see my moves.
好吧，看看我的动作。
You're kind of uptight.
你有点紧张。
I'm sorry. Now type in.
对不起。 现在输入。
A loose cannon.
一门松散的大炮。
Thanks for the compliment.
谢谢你的赞美。
You OK?
你还好吗？
You know what?
你知道吗？
What you saw? The first thing.
你看到了什么？ 第一件事。
The bank that I've talked to you.
我和你谈过的银行。
You losing brain.
你失去了大脑。
Cells. I'm losing actual brain cells.
细胞。 我正在失去真正的脑细胞。
Components of persevere right now.
现在坚持的组成部分。
You solids.
你固体。
You still believe bones are in your dick?
你还相信骨头在你的鸡巴里吗？
Why else would they call it a boner?
否则他们为什么会称其为蠢货？
First of all, you. Still believe that.
首先，你。 还是相信的。
You still believe that? No.
你还相信吗？ 不。
But you can understand why.
但你可以理解为什么。
I believe to kind. Of understand kind of.
我相信善良。 有点明白的。
Your ribs. Have flexible bones, you know.
你的肋骨。 有灵活的骨头，你知道的。
When you say that's not is it is if it's a very flexible bone rib
当你说那不是如果它是一个非常灵活的骨肋
when you breathe in and out.
当你吸气和呼气时。
Oh. Your rib cage expands and expands.
哦。 你的胸腔扩张和扩张。
So you think that's how that's how it worked with figure dick.
所以你认为这就是它与figure dick一起工作的方式。
That's solid work.
那是扎实的工作。
So bones are bendable like your fingers
所以骨头像你的手指一样可以弯曲
bend those.
弯曲那些。
I have joints. There.
我有关节。 那里。
There's there's a.
有一个。
Thing called joints, you know, mom's right
叫做关节的东西，你知道，妈妈是对的
now these are still well.
现在这些都还好。
Bendable me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
弯曲我，我，我，我，我，我，我。
The fugitives are still at large.
逃犯仍然逍遥法外。
I considered are so stupid.
我认为是那么愚蠢。
You're so stupid. Please put that off.
你是如此愚蠢。 请把它关掉。
She has a gun only I just found this.
她有一把枪，只是我刚找到的。
She just have a gun on the table.
她的桌子上只有一把枪。
Don't you worry, honey.
别担心，亲爱的。
Those two fools. That's what it's like in America.
那两个傻子。 这就是美国的情况。
You just have this on the table.
你只是把这个放在桌子上。
I guess so. I mean, this is America.
大概吧。 我的意思是，这就是美国。
This is America.
这是美国。
Yes. I caught up my breakfast about my shotgun on the table.
是的。 我赶上了关于桌上霰弹枪的早餐。
That man. I mean, we tied him up with something.
那个人。 我的意思是，我们用什么东西把他绑起来了。
Clothes.
衣服。
We can't walk around like this.
我们不能这样走来走去。
I don't like it.
我不喜欢它。
It's better to get them out of the house.
最好把他们赶出家门。
What you have in mind.
你有什么想法。
All we get, it's hot.
我们所得到的，它是热的。
Oh, see that barn over there?
哦，看到那边的谷仓了吗？
Smooth. Right?
光滑的。 对？
We release the horses. Mm. You move.
我们释放马匹。 emm。 你挪开。
Yeah. Milk.
是的。 牛奶。
You trust me?
你信任我？
Oh, he'll be forced to go get them back.
哦，他将被迫去把他们找回来。
Oh, God. No mind
天啊。 没关系
release the horses or subdue the couple.
释放马匹或制服这对夫妇。
I want to release the horses.
我想放马。
Yeah, release the horses. That's all. Fine.
对，放马。 就这些。 美好的。
Whatever, man. Let's try.
不管怎样，伙计。 咱们试试吧。
OK, come on.
好的，来吧。
We don't need to kill anyone now.
我们现在不需要杀任何人。
Are we gonna kill the couple?
我们要杀了这对夫妇吗？
We didn't do anything.
我们什么也没做。
Get the horses out of here.
把马赶出去。
It's locked.
它被锁定。
Yeah.
是的。
Can horses even survive in the wild
马甚至可以在野马中生存吗？ 是的，有野马。
You play Minecraft. What else should they have?
你玩我的世界。 他们还应该拥有什么？
So, yeah, but in microfossils, a red dust explode.
所以，是的，但是在微化石中，红色的尘埃会爆炸。
I mean, green. Red
我是说，绿色。 红色的
what?
什么？
Green, green.
绿色，绿色。
Yeah, but.
好但是。
Like, there's also cows and pigs in sheds here.
就像，这里的棚子里也有牛和猪。
It's like saying, like, oh, there's a cowboy there.
这就像说，就像，哦，那里有一个牛仔。
I want it.
我要它。
Can we touch it?
我们可以触摸它吗？
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
I think we can get over at least the horses.
我认为我们至少可以克服马匹。
Hello.
你好。
My re going to do.
我要去做。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Sorry, my hand.
对不起，我的手。
I can't help but thinking about a big juicy steak right now.
我现在忍不住想吃一块多汁的大牛排。
It's fucked up. What off?
完蛋了。 怎么了？
He doesn't like you.
他不喜欢你。
He doesn't like you. Get out!
他不喜欢你。 出去！
Oh, my God. You do it in his face.
我的天啊。 你当着他的面做。
That's not how you treat a cow.
这不是你对待牛的方式。
Look, watch the master.
看，看师傅。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
哈哈哈哈哈哈。
Yeah, he likes me. Wait. Let me try again.
是的，他喜欢我。 等待。 让我再试一次。
Ooh, ooh.
哦，哦。
You know, you don't understand.
你知道，你不明白。
He doesn't. You don't understand.
他没有。 你不明白。
You don't understand how it is.
你不明白它是怎么回事。
C c you stink.
C c 你很臭。
Stink more than the cow.
比牛还臭。
What you're saying the cows normally stink.
你说的牛通常很臭。
You try to say.
你试着说。
I mean.
我是说。
You know, my lord, I don't know if you have this problem.
您知道，我的主，我不知道您是否有这个问题。
I mean, every time someone says fuck, you might wake up.
我的意思是，每次有人说他妈的，你可能会醒来。
How bad? Every time someone says what?
多么糟糕？ 每次有人说什么？
Every time someone says, cow girl.
每次有人说，牛姑娘。
I think of like, cow girls, you know, like others.
我想像，牛女孩，你知道，像其他人一样。
I mean, isn't that what that means?
我的意思是，这不就是这个意思吗？
Like.
像。
Oh, like they're supposed to be, like, cowgirl, like the cowboy, but with a girl,
哦，就像他们应该是，像，女牛仔，像牛仔，但有一个女孩，
you know,
你知道，
we know the ha oh.
大家知道的哈哦。
Like, way, huh?
就像，方式，是吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, exactly.
是的，正是。
OK, I'm not alone in that. Then
好的，我并不孤单。 然后
okay. Hold on, hold on.
好的。 等一下，等一下。
What's the original?
什么是原版？
I thought.
我想。
I thought you could be a cow. What?
我以为你可能是一头牛。 什么？
How, girl?
怎么样，姑娘？
Yeah, ok. I never heard of the cow girl.
是的，好的。 我从没听说过牛姑娘。
Like the position
喜欢的位置
the position.
位置。
What's the position?
职位是什么？
That was his. Should I look it up?
那是他的。 我应该查一下吗？
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Give me a second.
你稍等一会儿。
Cowgirl.
女牛仔。
Position
位置
Cowgirl sex position works best if you bend slightly
如果你稍微向前弯下你的伴侣允许你的报价，女牛仔的性爱姿势效果最好。
OK? OK.
好的？ 好的。
All right.
好的。
I see. I get it now. I get it now.
我懂了。 我现在明白了。 我现在明白了。
Thank you, miss.
谢谢你，小姐。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I, i tell. Them why, why, why, why?
我，我告诉。 他们为什么，为什么，为什么，为什么？
You bring that up for why all girls.
你提出来为什么所有的女孩。
Oh, would you put that up for us?
哦，你能帮我们解决这个问题吗？
It's a horse. Pelicans, a horse.
它是一匹马。 鹈鹕，马。
I like others.
我喜欢别人。
First release the horse. How you do.
先放马。 你怎么做。
Then we push this piece of shit down. Bitch.
然后我们把这块狗屎推下去。 婊子。
I like those big mummy milk because.
我喜欢那些大妈咪奶，因为。
They're not. Even.
他们不是。 甚至。
Do you like udders or do you like weight?
你喜欢乳房还是喜欢体重？
Which one? Which one are you talking about?
哪一个？ 你说的是哪一个？
You're talking about two different things right now.
你现在在谈论两件不同的事情。
Right here.
就在这儿。
What's happening?
怎么了？
You're like, Mama.
你就像，妈妈。
I like it. Please.
我喜欢。 请。
I like otters.
我喜欢水獭。
Yeah, it was mommy milk white fever. Yup.
是的，那是妈妈乳白热。 是的。
Let's free them all.
让我们释放他们。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
We shot this.
我们拍了这个。
Why can't we just.
为什么我们不能。
Take the horses with us?
把马带走？
Why can't we ride them?
为什么我们不能骑它们？
You can just shut up for one minute.
你可以闭嘴一分钟。
Can we just take the horses and say, fuck the couple?
我们能不能只拿马说，操这对夫妇？
I mean, the horses are going to get released and then it's locked.
我的意思是，马会被释放，然后它被锁定。
It's locked. Can't open this one.
它被锁定。 这个打不开
Wait, where are you?
等等，你在哪里？
A horse?
一匹马？
Yeah, we have to open the other one.
是的，我们必须打开另一个。
This one behind you.
你身后的这个。
You make a chicken noise.
你发出鸡的声音。
I tried to open this.
我试图打开这个。
It was close. Dumb-ass.
它很接近。 笨蛋。
OK, we'll call. We both do at the same time.
好的，我们会打电话的。 我们俩同时做。
No, it's not.
不它不是。
Light bulb.
灯泡。
With this lab.
有了这个实验室。
We're doing the light bulb lamp.
我们正在做电灯泡灯。
And I know how we go.
我知道我们该怎么走。
OK, what's the point of that?
好吧，那有什么意义呢？
What's the point of that?
那有什么意义呢？
We're fixing that fucking barn for them.
我们正在为他们修好那个该死的谷仓。
What's OK?
什么是好的？
Yeah, maybe maybe you unlocked a secret ending
是的，也许你解锁了一个秘密结局，他们就像，哦，谁修了我们的灯？
Oh, it must have been those two kind gentlemen that came by.
哦，一定是那两位好心的先生走过来的。
Oh, we just did some partially, you know, and they'll show up in our trial.
哦，我们只是做了一些部分，你知道，他们会出现在我们的试验中。
And vouch for us, work
为我们担保，工作
on Dong.
在东。
Dong.
董。
Not loud enough.
不够响亮。
Mami.
妈咪。
Oh, my God. What is that?
我的天啊。 那是什么？
It's a going to work.
这是一个工作。
Or maybe I can get back out, like, on
或者也许我可以回来，比如，在
the fuck.
他妈的。
Oh, I don't know what to do.
哦，我不知道该怎么办。
I ever.
我曾经。
I'm looking for everything right now.
我现在正在寻找一切。
Everything
一切
I'm looking.
我在看。
For you leave now.
因为你现在离开。
And I push this.
我推动这个。
I'm slopping in. There.
我正在溜进去。在那里。
And I'm just putting him slap me.
而我只是让他打我耳光。
OK, you do this.
好的，你这样做。
So come on.
那来吧。
Oh, oh, now we have to do that.
哦，哦，现在我们必须这样做。
Now we could do something.
现在我们可以做点什么了。
OK, we just had to let the horses out first.
好的，我们只需要先让马出去。
Where are you?
你在哪里？
Well, I'm a pit stop.
好吧，我是一个进站。
Like. This myself.
像。 这是我自己。
Come on, Vincent, over here.
来吧，文森特，过来。
Yes. So blind
是的。 如此盲目
oh, hey.
噢！嗨。
He's so blind. Blend in my defence.
他太盲目了。 融入我的防守。
You blend in with the background pretty well.
你很好地融入了背景。
Fuck you, man.
去你妈的，伙计。
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
That's so strong.
那太强大了。
Oh, hell, the horses are escaping.
哦，见鬼，马逃跑了。
Honey. What?
蜜糖。 什么？
What kind of horses are escaping?
逃跑的是什么马？
Honey,
蜜糖，
it didn't seem that bothered to be.
它似乎并不那么麻烦。
Oh, he is.
哦，他是。
He's running like one more power I mean, they're old and, like, hey, you.
我的意思是，他像另一种力量一样奔跑，他们很老，就像，嘿，你。
Yeah, look, just once, but it's.
是的，看，只有一次，但它是。
Probably happened before.
可能以前发生过。
You know, it's not the first time, though.
你知道，虽然这不是第一次。
How the shame horses escaped
耻辱马是如何逃脱的
OK, we got to be quick about this shit.
好的，我们必须快点处理这件事。
They're got to come back once they get the horses.
一旦他们得到马匹，他们就必须回来。
All right, I'm going, I'm going.
好吧，我去，我去。
Then I'm going to catch two horses.
然后我要去抓两匹马。
They're running like one of our
他们像我们的一员一样奔跑
yeah.
是的。
I don't know, man.
我不知道，伙计。
The country folk or party are pretty sturdy.
乡下人或党派相当健壮。
Found the way. And wait, I think. Oh, wait.
找到了路。 等等，我想。 等一下。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
There was a door that. Oh, Frank, call somebody.
有一扇门。 哦，弗兰克，打电话给某人。
OK, I found the TV.
好的，我找到了电视。
Welcome back to our show, Paranormal Activity. And.
欢迎回到我们的节目，超自然活动。 和。
Oh, man, the Cold War may be perfect.
哦，伙计，冷战可能是完美的。
That you will claim.
你会声称。
Oh, I. Called my wife.
哦，我。打电话给我的妻子。
When he finally saw fresh water.
当他终于看到淡水时。
Ooh, fresh water.
哦，淡水。
Are you going? Were you doing over there?
你要去吗？ 你在那边做的吗？
What were you doing?
你在做什么？
I'm looking for clues.
我正在寻找线索。
You're looking for clues?
你在寻找线索吗？
What kind of clues?
什么样的线索？
Uh, hold on.
呃，等一下。
And from what? My foot. Yeah.
从什么开始？ 我的脚。 是的。
Hey, hey.
嘿，嘿。
No, no, no. No.
不不不。 不。
Can you move?
你能动吗？
Move, like, two centimetres in left. How?
向左移动两厘米。 如何？
When did you have a left?
你什么时候有左？
And you had this pretty good looking bitch?
你有这个漂亮的婊子？
Give me a lap dance right now to levitate you.
现在就给我跳一圈圈舞让你飘起来。
You were. Useless.
你之前是。 无用。
I was.
我曾是。
You interrupted me in the being.
你打断了我的存在。
No, stay there.
不，呆在那里。
How do you.
你怎么。
How did you. Find?
你怎么了。 寻找？
I'm gonna stay there.
我要留在那里。
Say they're. And Gordon. Gordon.
说他们是。 还有戈登。 戈登。
Not until. You turn off the TV.
直到。 你关掉电视。
Because this is this a personal moment yet?
因为这是个人的时刻了吗？
Pay attention to me. All right?
请听我说。 好的？
All right.
好的。
You like that.
你喜欢。
The one 8360 manoeuvre the rich round.
一个8360操纵富轮。
I call this the rich realm. Oh, look at this.
我称之为富国。 哦，看看这个。
I have never been so blessed in my life.
我这辈子从来没有这么幸运过。
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
yeah, it is.
是啊，就是。
I didn't know it was.
我不知道它是。
Possible to be blessed. Blessed did.
有可能得到祝福。 有福了。
Good and.
好和。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Can we take the matches?
我们可以参加比赛吗？
I only take them. Yes.
我只带他们。 是的。
That looks good.
这看起来不错。
Far away.
远处。
Oh, no, this is.
哦，不，这是。
This is more like the rapids. Ah.
这更像是急流。 啊。
What is your high?
你的高潮是什么？
Holy shit.
天啊。
Hold on, hold on.
等一下，等一下。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Boy, I want to go to tryouts and close till.
男孩，我想参加选拔赛并结束比赛。
You have a grip.
你有把握。
Can we take that fool?
我们能接受那个傻瓜吗？
I got Lucas hot hillbilly.
我得到了卢卡斯热乡下人。
Oh, no, well, you say hillbilly.
哦，不，好吧，你说的是乡巴佬。
What does like hillbilly?
什么像乡巴佬？
It's just solidly. On the hill.
它只是坚固。 山坡上。
It's slang for.
它是俚语。
I've never really been a hard man.
我从来都不是一个真正的硬汉。
Oh, I'm not a hot person, dammit. OK.
哦，我不是一个热的人，该死的。 好的。
Oh, look, you are a child.
哦，看，你还是个孩子。
You are an absolute child.
你是一个绝对的孩子。
What is that, huh?
那是什么，嗯？
What the fuck is that?
那是什么鬼？
I didn't mean to. I didn't mean to.
我不是故意的。 我不是故意的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I'm going to build this. Oh, I wiped it off.
我要建造这个。 哦，我擦掉了。
Oh, shit. Bob, oh.
妈的。 鲍勃，哦。
I corrected his his on his errors.
我纠正了他的错误。
But when you do one of two new fancy models.
但是当你做两个新的花式模型之一时。
Can you can you move?
你能动吗？
So I. Can.
所以我可以。
He moves so I can see what's happening.
他移动，所以我可以看到发生了什么。
I'm very.
我很。
Good at this. This.
擅长这个。 这。
What is he playing?
他在玩什么？
Oh, from scratch, I guess.
哦，从头开始，我猜。
All. All or all.
全部。 全部或全部。
We cannot what I wanted to do.
我们不能做我想做的事。
I want to build a house of cards down it.
我想在它下面建一座纸牌屋。
Oh, here we go.
哦，我们开始吧。
Change clothes. All right. Don't look.
更衣。 好的。 不要看。
No. Yeah.
不，是的。
Oh, like a peeping tom.
哦，就像一个偷窥狂。
No, no, I can.
不，不，我可以。
I can. I can smell you, like, in Somalia.
我可以。 我能闻到你的味道，就像在索马里。
All right, I got a fucking gun.
好吧，我有一把他妈的枪。
Did you get that gun?
你拿到那把枪了吗？
All right, sir, I'm ready.
好的，先生，我准备好了。
OK? You don't look
好的？ 你不看
dumb, okay?
笨蛋，好吗？
You ready for this? You ready for this?
你准备好了吗？ 你准备好了吗？
Come of massive drip.
大量滴水而来。
All Yeah.
都是的。
Oh, yeah. Look at me.
哦耶。 看着我。
Look at the floor. Old pattern.
看看地板。 旧模式。
You forgot. To drip.
你忘了。 滴水。
Yes, I bet it is germ.
是的，我敢打赌它是细菌。
Oh, we get all.
哦，我们得到了一切。
If you want to use it for.
如果你想用它。
This comfortable. I think we can wait.
这个舒服。 我想我们可以等。
Is that kind of fucked? Up to fuck on another couple of spat?
有这么操蛋吗？ 去他妈的另外几个口角？
Um. I think it
嗯。 我认为这取决于你是否足够了解他们。
You don't know them. Yeah, we don't know.
你不认识他们。 是的，我们不知道。
That's fine. I mean. Are you aren't you into that stuff?
没事儿。 我是说。 你不喜欢那些东西吗？
I always.
我总是。
Family's kind of like.
一家人的样子。
Non-Toxic relationships or whatever.
无毒的关系或其他。
Ntaiya.
恩泰亚。
Yeah. Mm hmm.
是的。 嗯嗯。
I think it's OK sometimes.
我觉得有时候还可以。
I started with everything, you know?
我从一切开始，你知道吗？
You know, I saw a fucking thing before my eyes.
你知道，我在我眼前看到了一个他妈的东西。
I made a joke. I don't actually like NTR chat.
我开了个玩笑。 我其实不喜欢 NTR 聊天。
If I said it as a joke one time.
如果我把它当成笑话说一次。
And some I saw some fucking, like, hate coming.
还有一些我看到一些他妈的，比如，讨厌来了。
I was like.
我像。
This fucking.
这他妈的。
Cut. Claude, what the fuck is this?
切。 克劳德，这是什么鬼？
I'm sobbing.
我在抽泣。
It's like, what the fuck did way oh, god.
就像，他妈的做了什么，哦，上帝。
What's up?
怎么了？
I think we just lost a joke.
我想我们只是失去了一个笑话。
You know something?
你知道一些事情？
I think we just left fingerprints all over this fucking house.
我想我们只是在这该死的房子上留下了指纹。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I'm. I'm worried.
我是。 我很担心。
About that.
关于那个。
Why are you worried?
你为什么担心？
We just shoot them and kill them so you don't.
我们只是开枪杀了他们，这样你就不会了。
Actually like NCR?
真的像NCR吗？
Know what I guess we won't make funny at this point.
知道我猜我们不会在这一点上搞笑。
Said, I know. I don't.
说，我知道。 我不。
I'm not disappointed.
我并不失望。
Why are you putting words into my mouth?
你为什么要把话塞进我嘴里？
What's I'm not too surprised?
什么是我不太惊讶？
I can change for you if you like it.
如果你喜欢，我可以为你改变。
Now, you don't have to change.
现在，您不必改变。
I was just shocked.
我只是震惊了。
Because this entire time, it's
因为这整个时间，就像过去几个月一样，什么，四个月，五个月？
This entire time, I. Thought, like, hey, you.
这整个时间，我想，就像，嘿，你。
You know, good for you.
你知道，对你有好处。
I guess you.
我猜你。
Could relate to me or something. No, I didn't. Think I could relate to you.
可能与我有关。 不，我没有。 我想我可以和你联系。
Stop it.
停下来。
Stop trying to make an image.
停止尝试制作图像。
Mysta. Miss that. Mysta..
米斯塔。 错过了。 米斯塔..
Look, look, I can like what you like.
看，看，我可以喜欢你喜欢的。
I was just surprise that information I had about you this entire time.
我只是惊讶于我一直以来掌握的关于你的信息。
So it's not Suzie.
所以不是苏西。
It's not Suzie. You're Suzie.
不是苏西。 你是苏西。
And we will pet the cow again.
我们将再次抚摸那头牛。
Will you pet. Me? Yeah.
你会宠。 我？ 是的。
That's what I'm talking about.
这就是我所说的。
Oh, wow. Not
哦，哇。 不是
where the fuck is the truck, bro?
卡车在哪里，兄弟？
Yeah. I don't know where the truck is.
是的。 我不知道卡车在哪里。
There's a truck that.
有一辆卡车。
Maybe it's back this way.
或许又是这样回来的。
No, it's not maybe it's in the back.
不，它不是，也许它在后面。
Maybe we're just completely dumb.
也许我们只是完全愚蠢。
I didn't even know there was a truck, to be completely honest.
老实说，我什至不知道有一辆卡车。
Oh, maybe it's down here.
哦，也许它在下面。
Look at those fields. Of corn.
看看那些领域。 玉米。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Oh, that's not corn.
哦，那不是玉米。
What is that? Here it. Is.
那是什么？ 在这里。 是。
I don't need. No, no, no, no. Give it here.
我不需要。 不不不不。 给这里。
Oh, give me a fucking.
哦，给我一个他妈的。
Give me a second. I don't know. If.
你稍等一会儿。 我不知道。 如果。
I would like to look. Around. Okay,
我想看看。 大约。 好的，
I'll show you.
我给你看。
Chop wood. I'll help them out.
伐木。 我会帮助他们。
Might as well help them out.
还不如帮助他们。
Oh, sure.
行，可以。
Damn.
该死。
Oh, look at me.
哦，看着我。
Look at me.
看着我。
You're selling the house three.
你卖房子三。
Can you do this shit?
你能干这种事吗？
You do this. You can do that.
你来做这件事。 你可以这样做。
I could do that with one hand.
我一只手就能做到。
This look this far, OK, number five
这看起来这么远，好吧，第五
or six
或六个
or your turn, bitch. Go.
还是轮到你了，婊子。 去。
You try.
你试试。
Let's chop.
我们砍吧。
What's a shell?
什么是贝壳？
Let's chop some wood.
让我们砍一些木头。
This is how you do it.
这就是你的做法。
Come look at speed.
快来看看速度。
I'm going to pace.
我要加快步伐。
Like the pace.
喜欢节奏。
Look at pace.
看节奏。
For you tapping.
为你敲击。
Yeah, OK.
是的，好的。
Again, your way again your way.
再次，你的方式再次你的方式。
No, no. OK, fine.
不，不。 好的。
I like when you're in my way.
我喜欢你挡在我的路上。
And yet you don't like ends here.
然而你不喜欢这里的结局。
Interesting.
有趣的。
Oh, you still on this canister?
哦，你还在这个罐子上吗？
So I didn't know it was like this.
所以我不知道它是这样的。
Stewart, I'm so sorry.
斯图尔特，我很抱歉。
Shut up.
住口。
Anyways, what are we doing with this car?
不管怎样，我们用这辆车做什么？
Wait, where it's Albion?
等等，阿尔比恩在哪里？
Where? Where? Hello. With the pussy.
在哪里？ 在哪里？ 你好。 与猫。
OK, like.
好的，喜欢。
I'm literally right behind you. You're a fucking idiot.
我真的就在你身后。 你真是个白痴。
I can't.
我不能。
I'm stuck
我被困住了
I'm stuck.
我被困住了。
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
哦谢谢。 谢谢你。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I couldn't move.
我动弹不得。
The gas canister cocks me.
煤气罐让我兴奋。
Oh, you're right.
哦，你是对的。
There's a cat on.
有一只猫在。
His smug face.
他得意的脸。
Is he alive?
他还活着吗？
Yes, he's alive. He's not believes.
是的，他还活着。 他不相信。
He's not blinking. Oh, he was here.
他没有眨眼。 哦，他在这里。
Yeah, he's alive. Yeah. All right.
是的，他还活着。 是的。 好的。
He took my gas canister.
他拿走了我的煤气罐。
I did.
我做到了。
I'm assuming we need it for the wait, wait.
我假设我们需要它等待，等待。
What was that.
那是什么。
Huh? Was what?
嗯？ 是什么？
It was like shoot horseshoe throwing or something.
这就像射击马蹄铁投掷之类的。
All we could.
我们所能做的。
All we could play a mini game.
我们只能玩一个迷你游戏。
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
You are getting.
你得到了。
Your ass beat.
你的屁股打。
Oh, I don't know about that.
哦，我不知道。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Oh, wait. I did get. It. That
等一下。 我确实得到了。 它。 那
night.
夜晚。
What's all.
什么都是。
Dude, you're gonna get your ass manhandled by this.
伙计，这会让你的屁股被粗暴对待。
This cowboy right here.
这位牛仔就在这里。
You ain't ready, son.
你还没准备好，儿子。
Oh, look at that.
哦，看那个。
Look at that.
看那个。
Perfect. Five, four, five.
完美的。 五，四，五。
I see you do that.
我看到你这样做了。
Go ahead.
前进。
Do it right now.
现在就去做。
I rock
我好棒
oh, jackpot.
哦，大奖。
We. You hit it.
我们。 你打它。
I miss my screen, OK?
我想念我的屏幕，好吗？
I was crazy.
我疯了。
Wait, wait for a miss two I'm.
等等，等我二小姐。
I'm confused.
我很困惑。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
I'm the king.
我是王。
Why you lost?
你为什么输了？
What do you mean, you're the king?
什么意思，你是国王？
Well,
好，
what do you mean you're the king?
什么你是国王？
You lost
你输了
it's 25 to 15.
这是25到15。
This is. OK.
这是。 好的。
I'm thinking you guys.
我在想你们。
So little in the.
中的那么少。
Other.
其他。
It's OK to be hurt.
受伤是可以的。
I want to open my mouth on this one.
我想对这个张开嘴。
No, not so much.
不，没有那么多。
Oh, you mix the walls, the new house.
哦，你混合墙壁，新房子。
The fuck.
他妈的。
All. Whose house is this?
全部。 这是谁的房子？
This house we want in you fucking Thomas. No, it's not.
这房子我们想要你他妈的托马斯。 不它不是。
This is different one.
这是不一样的。
Isn't it? It was the same one.
不是吗？ 这是同一个。
Oh, it is.
哦，是的。
OK, so look, there's there's a.
好的，所以看，有一个。
There's a lot of there's a lot of buildings around us, right?
我们周围有很多很多建筑物，对吧？
It's easy to get confused.
很容易混淆。
All right, I'm walking.
好吧，我在走路。
See this?
看到这个了吗？
That's the same house.
那是同一所房子。
A real shit.
一个真正的狗屎。
Barn.
谷仓。
Not the wrong one. Back that.
不是错的。 回那个。
Back. Hold on.
后退。 坚持，稍等。
Like a bye bye hold on.
像再见一样坚持。
Fucking guy. This fucking guy.
他妈的家伙。 这该死的家伙。
I'm coming. I'm coming. Hold on.
我来了。 我来了。 坚持，稍等。
Wait. There's a truck right over there.
等待。 那边有一辆卡车。
That's not true. Yo.
那不是真的。 哟。
I'm on my way.
我在路上。
Give me a second. All right, dude, I got it.
你稍等一会儿。 好的，伙计，我明白了。
I can't get something.
我什么也得不到。
I can't get this drip dirty.
我不能把这滴水弄脏。
I I take my time
我慢慢来
I take my time.
我慢慢来。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You know you can't rush.
你知道你不能着急。
You can't rush an old man like this.
你不能像这样催促一个老人。
Yeah.
是的。
Come on.
来吧。
I'll hold your hand. OK, ok. Hold my hand. OK.
我会握住你的手。 好的好的。 抓住我的手。 好的。
Oh, man one I don't even want I don't want to move at this point.
哦，伙计，我什至不想在这一点上移动。
I just want keep holding your hand
我只想继续牵着你的手
come on.
来吧。
Hold you.
抱你。
You are so slow.
你太慢了。
Vincent, come over here and help me.
文森特，过来帮帮我。
Up, ok? OK.
起来，好吗？ 好的。
I think you need.
我想你需要。
I need so much help. You're so needy.
我需要这么多帮助。 你太需要了。
I need.
我需要。
Why can't you do it by yourself?
为什么你不能自己做？
I'm weak. I need you.
我没有力气。 我需要你。
This car is a piece of junk.
这辆车是个垃圾。
What do you. Mean?
你是什​​么。 意思是？
It's actually, it's pretty.
事实上，它很漂亮。
Cool as like a hat and everything.
酷得像帽子和一切。
Doesn't look like.
看起来不像。
It's even missing. It doesn't have a wheel.
它甚至不见了。 它没有轮子。
I'm sure there's a spare around here somewhere.
我敢肯定这里的某个地方有备用的。
I think cars can drive on free wheels.
我认为汽车可以在自由轮上行驶。
It's not like we have a choice.
这不像我们有选择的余地。
Sure, but running on foot.
当然可以，但要步行。
Let's fix it up and we'll be out of here in no time, right?
让我们把它修好，我们很快就会离开这里，对吧？
Do these old people are, like, taking forever
难道这些老人是，就像，永远
because we've been fucking around for, like, the past?
因为我们一直在他妈的，比如，过去？
Well, you can't catch horse horses.
好吧，你不能抓马。
Horse. Horse.
马。 马。
Cause you can't catch horses.
因为你抓不到马。
Why do you say it like that?
你为什么这么说？
Horses?
马匹？
Yeah. Horses. Yeah. Why you police?
是的。 马匹。 是的。 你为什么要警察？
Why are you so much, like, emphasis on the on the mule?
为什么你这么强调骡子？
Yeah.
是的。
Walk the walk.
走走。
No sound like that. I can.
没有那种声音。 我可以。
You know, the one. It's all like a white.
你知道的，那个。 这一切都像一个白色的。
You know that.
你知道的。
Like, puffer fish farm.
比如，河豚养殖场。
We could use this new tire.
我们可以使用这个新轮胎。
Stone, it sounds like. Yes, it does.
石头，听起来像。 是的，它确实。
Get up there it's it gills like.
上去就是它的鳃。
Oh, yeah, you know that. That's the noise.
哦，是的，你知道的。 那就是噪音。
That's the noise.
那就是噪音。
Not what it is. The noise.
不是它是什么。 噪音。
Oh, is that so the noise I had
哦，是这样吗？我听到的噪音在我的信息流中确实有声音警报，而且人们发送垃圾邮件。
That's literally what it sounds like. I hear it like every single day.
这就是字面意思。 我每天都听到它。
Somebody play it right now.
马上有人玩。
Please.
请。
And the guy who this all.
和这一切的人。
He Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
他嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
Believe you there
相信你在那里
my house
我家
was oh, wait. It brings you back.
是哦，等等。 它带你回来。
That's bullshit.
那是胡说八道。
It's actually back.
它实际上又回来了。
Now. Dammit.
现在。 该死。
Hold on a minute.
坚持一分钟。
OK, fine. I'll bring you over.
好的。 我带你过去。
Be forward.
前进。
Late. Oh, that's the wrong direction.
晚的。 哦，那是错误的方向。
On the other side.
另一方面。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Here
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。 这里
you me a oh.
你我一个哦。
A job, boy.
一份工作，男孩。
Job, boy.
工作，男孩。
Thanks man.
谢啦。
Yeah, because a tire.
是的，因为轮胎。
Bring the tires down.
把轮胎放下。
Bring the tire down. Oh, let me go
把轮胎放下。 哦，让我去看看这个。
A tire. Haha.
一个轮胎。 哈哈。
So it was so fucking funny.
所以这太他妈搞笑了。
You're so fucking funny.
你太他妈搞笑了
No, why would I, why would I leave.
不，我为什么要离开，我为什么要离开。
The wrench up there?
上面的扳手？
What's dumb-ass.
什么是笨蛋。
He he, like, went down. Without the wrench.
呵呵，就这样下去了。 不用扳手。
I'll wait for you.
我会等你的。
I'll wait for you here.
我会在这里等你。
I need to check something.
我需要检查一些东西。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh, my God. Yeah, that's what it sounds like.
我的天啊。 是的，听起来就是这样。
Oh, it doesn't sound like that shot solid, but.
哦，这听起来并不像那个镜头，但是。
Yes, it does. What do you think?
是的，它确实。 你怎么看？
It sounds like they make the noise right now.
听起来他们现在正在制造噪音。
Oh. That's not that at all.
哦。 根本不是这样。
So what kind of porn are you watching?
那么你在看什么样的色情片？
That's what
那是什么
the fog in this
这里面的迷雾
hello?
你好？
Hello.
你好。
OK, where's the tire, man?
好的，轮胎在哪里，伙计？
Show me the fucking site.
给我看看他妈的网站。
I dropped it right here.
我把它丢在这里了。
Where are you?
你在哪里？
Right here. Inside, baby.
就在这儿。 里面，宝贝。
Put it in the side. The inside the socket.
放在一边。 插座内部。
I put it inside. OK, good. Man.
我把它放在里面。 好的，很好。 男人。
Good job. Good job.
做得好。 做得好。
Now it's inside.
现在它在里面。
OK. Ok.
好的。 行。
Now we just need to screw in the starts.
现在我们只需要拧紧开始。
And we're screwed.
我们被搞砸了。
And and now I. Oh, yeah.
而现在我。哦，是的。
Front thingy and I grab the gasoline.
前面的东西，我抓起汽油。
Juice.
果汁。
Yeah, all my sounds are off. They are.
是的，我所有的声音都关闭了。 他们是。
There are at least OK.
至少有OK。
And then I go hit something and then I keep.
然后我去打东西然后我继续。
The support. And then I open.
支撑。 然后我打开。
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
What are you saying? Right now. It's like the.
你在说什么？ 现在。 它就像。
Best way is out of the. Boy.
最好的办法就是出去。 男生。
The battery is out to juice. And to take the gas.
电池没电了。 并取气。
And then I open.
然后我打开。
And go back in the house.
然后回到屋里。
You watch TV, you continue the job.
你看电视，你继续工作。
Yes. Let me know when you're done.
是的。 完成后告诉我。
What am I supposed to do?
我应该做些什么？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'm going to go watch the go watch Cartoon Network.
我要去观看去观看卡通网络。
Maybe some fuck was wasn't on the clock.
也许有些他妈的不在时钟上。
There is some Nickelodeon's on the channel.
频道上有一些 Nickelodeon。
Oh, I want to watch Home Alone on the Air.
哦，我想看《独自在家》。
Does this even fit? And what is. This?
这还合适吗？ 是什么。 这？
Oh, is that we put the gas.
哦，是我们放的气。
Get over here.
到这里来。
Why did you take the gas all the way with you?
你为什么一路带煤气？
You fucking asshole.
你个混蛋。
I'm just sitting on it.
我只是坐在上面。
Literally sitting on that
从字面上看
wait.
等待。
Hold on, OK?
等等，好吗？
I don't grab the gas.
我不抢气。
Oh, no. Oh, no, I don't think I can grab it.
不好了。 哦，不，我不认为我能抓住它。
People said, you bitch, that's mine.
人们说，你这个婊子，那是我的。
I don't give a shit you.
我不理你。
That's mine. Oh, my God. Wait, no, I'm sitting down. Fine.
那是我的。 我的天啊。 等等，不，我正在坐下。 美好的。
You sit down. No, sit down.
你坐下。 不，坐下。
It's not. My gas. I don't care
它不是。 我的气。 我不在乎
I don't give a fuck.
我不在乎。
I'm going to put it in.
我要把它放进去。
Firefights with my guys.
和我的人交火。
Bring it back.
把它带回来。
Oh, ha ha ha ha.
哦，哈哈哈。
Good fill tank.
良好的填充油箱。
There we go.
我们去吧。
OK, so that's how you fill a car.
好的，这就是你给汽车加油的方式。
Show you how to fill, or I'll show you how to fill.
教你怎么填，或者我教你怎么填。
Can you drive?
你会开车吗？
I can drive. Yeah. Can you drive?
我会开车。 是的。 你会开车吗？
All right. No.
好的。 不。
I can drive. Then let me drive.
我会开车。 然后让我开车。
We saw you driving last time.
上次我们看到你开车了。
Now get the fuck right.
现在去他妈的吧。
Like I'll get out.
就像我会出去一样。
Look, you can drive. Show.
看，你会开车。 显示。
Yeah, you're amazing driving skills. OK, ok.
是的，你的驾驶技术很棒。 好的好的。
I got this on and you're not ready.
我穿上这个，你还没准备好。
Oh, I got I once I got what is it called?
哦，我知道了，我知道了它叫什么？
What what do people get in Mario Kart?
人们在马里奥赛车中得到了什么？
The the stars, the trophies, the the mushrooms.
星星，奖杯，蘑菇。
The batteries. Oh. The batteries dead. Oh.
电池。 哦。 电池没电了。 哦。
Iris dead.
艾丽丝死了。
Oh. All Yeah.
哦。 都是的。
That's nice.
那很好。
We fix the battery.
我们修理电池。
The battery seems dead.
电池好像没电了。
How is fix the battery? Fine.
怎么修电池？ 美好的。
How do we live?
我们如何生活？
Oh. Oh, that's a hope. You.
哦。 哦，那是希望。 你。
And then I push this. Yeah. Yeah.
然后我推这个。 是的。 是的。
Nice. Nice.
好的。 好的。
OK, good, good, good.
好，好，好，好。
Right now can at least.
至少现在可以。
Oh, ok.
哦好的。
You push it.
你推它。
I think you push it, and then I'll try to start it.
我想你推动它，然后我会尝试启动它。
OK? OK,
好的？ 好的，
I'm pushing, I'm pushing, I'm pushing and pushing.
我在推，我在推，我在推，在推。
I'm pushing and pushing and pushing.
我在推，推，推。
I'm pushing.
我在推。
Oh, Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔」
Ow, Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Is he going to crash?
他会崩溃吗？
Did you let it go?
你放了吗？
Uh oh, it's fine.
哦哦，没关系。
You let it go.
你放手了。
Let it go.
放手吧。
All right, get in the car.
好了，上车吧。
You're driving. Yeah. This is my turn, isn't my turn?
你在开车。 是的。 轮到我了，是不是轮到我了？
Get in way for this.
为此做好准备。
Get in that hold him.
进去抱他。
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
What? Hold on.
什么？ 坚持，稍等。
Keep going. Keep going.
继续前进。 继续前进。
It's not going to work.
这是行不通的。
What do you mean, it's not going to repair it? No.
你的意思是，它不会修复它？ 不。
Third time's a charm.
第三次是魅力。
All right.
好的。
We'll keep playing the sound, maybe.
也许我们会继续播放声音。
Oh, wait, wait.
哦，等等，等等。
The jumper cables. Wow.
跨接电缆。 哇。
Wow. Oh, I want it now.
哇。 哦，我现在就想要。
Yeah,
是的，
well, down.
干得好。
OK. OK.
好的。 好的。
That's how you do it.
你就是这样做的。
Yeah, I told you so.
是的，我告诉过你。
So you didn't.
所以你没有。
You just got to have.
你必须拥有。
Yeah, I did tell you so.
是的，我确实告诉过你。
I told you so. No.
我已经告诉过你了。 不。
That's all it is. So next time.
就是这样。 所以下次。
Just trust me, ok?
相信我，好吗？
I will never trust you.
我永远不会相信你。
You got to trust oh. Oh, no.
你要相信哦。 不好了。
I don't know why. When the fuck do they get back?
我不知道为什么。 他们什么时候回来？
We need your help now.
我们现在需要你的帮助。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. He has it gone.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。 他已经走了。
Is he loading a gun?
他在装枪吗？
He's gone.
他已经去了。
Oh, my God. It's not a Rubik's Cube here.
我的天啊。 这里不是魔方。
Any minute.
任何一分钟。
He's gone.
他已经去了。
It's a Rubik's cube.
这是一个魔方。
Why would he be seraphin sku?
为什么他会是六翼天使？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Oh, shit. Take cover.
妈的。 掩护。
You're going to pay for this oh, let's go.
你会为此付出代价的，我们走吧。
That is not cover. He's right in line of sight.
那不是封面。 他就在视线之内。
OK. OK, ok. OK, ok.
好的。 好的好的。 好的好的。
Oh, you're shooting another the gun
哦，你又在用枪射击
don't worry.
不用担心。
I got this. OK. I got the aim.
我懂了。 好的。 我得到了目标。
You just focus on driving
你只专注于驾驶
ok? OK, ok, ok.
好的？ 好好好。
Oh, this is going to be easy.
哦，这很容易。
Easy money.
快钱。
Wait, do I not even get to drive.
等等，我什至不会开车。
Dude.
老兄。
They can't just they can't just like it.
他们不能只是他们不能只是喜欢它。
Hey, basically, we got cops.
嘿，基本上，我们有警察。
Come on, step on it.
来吧，踩它。
Oh. Oh, my God.
哦。 我的天啊。
Here we go. Here we go. GCA.
开始了。 开始了。  GCA。
Yeah, now you guys shoot.
是的，现在你们开枪了。
Don't cut this piece of shit. Going to die.
不要剪掉这块狗屎。 快死了。
Just sit down, Leo.
坐下吧，里奥。
You're going to fall off
你会掉下来
here we go.
开始了。
All right. Oh, my God.
好的。 我的天啊。
What is this? Oh, and shoot. Wow.
这是什么？ 哦，射击。 哇。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
OK, oh, my God.
好的，哦，我的上帝。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。
I'm throttling. I'm throttling him.
我正在节流。 我正在扼杀他。
Oh, he. Oh,
哦，他。 哦，
fine. Dude, dude, dude.
美好的。 伙计，伙计，伙计。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
What are you doing to them?
你在对他们做什么？ 你在对他们做什么？
I'm sure a lot of them.
我相信他们中的很多人。
I mean, nothing really, like, bang, bang, oh.
我的意思是，真的没有什么，比如，砰，砰，哦。
Holy shit. What the fuck are you doing?
天啊。 你他妈在做什么？
I'm trying.
我在尝试。
I'm driving. I'm keeping you alive right now.
我在开车。 我现在让你活着。
I could crash his car at any time.
我随时都可能撞坏他的车。
I can.
我可以。
I control.
我控制。
I control that. You.
我控制它。 你。
Oh. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
哦。 不好了。 不好了。 不好了。 不好了。 不好了。
Oh, no.
不好了。
I'm ok.
我很好。
OK. OK.
好的。 好的。
We're going to talk about a problem.
我们要谈一个问题。
And I need to reload.
我需要重新加载。
Holy shit. Reloading.
天啊。 重新加载。
Oh, I messed up.
哦，我搞砸了。
I messed up. Oh, God.
我搞砸了。 天啊。
Oh, God.
天啊。
You know that.
你知道的。
That's ok.
那没问题。
Wow. Oh, my God.
哇。 我的天啊。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
哦。 不好了。 不好了。 不好了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Yo, yo, I'm sick.
哟哟，我病了。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
I can't even see my crosshair. See, they call me.
我什至看不到我的十字准线。 看，他们打电话给我。
They call me the pile driver.
他们叫我打桩机。
I guess at this woman.
估计是这个女人
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Well, goodbye.
那再见吧;好吧再见。
Oh, I got a little group I go with.
哦，我有一个小团体。
I go. Let's go this way.
我去。 让我们走这条路。
Well, you didn't even care.
好吧，你甚至不在乎。
Oh, what's the time? Oh. Oh.
哦，几点了？ 哦。 哦。
I thought I was.
我以为我是。
I thought it was a cliff, but that was a cliff.
我以为那是悬崖，但那是悬崖。
I'm keeping you alive so bad. I'll show you bad.
我让你活得很糟糕。 我会告诉你不好的。
No, I'll show you bad.
不，我会给你看不好的。
Oh, so I am driving the car right now.
哦，所以我现在正在开车。
Are you sure you want to test?
你确定要测试吗？
Are you sure you want to test this? Yeah,
你确定要测试这个吗？ 是的，
I was talking about the fucking car.
我说的是他妈的车。
Do it again.
再来一遍。
I'll do it all.
我会做这一切。
You talk about the cop.
你说的是警察。
Oops. I'm so sorry, Mama.
哎呀。 我很抱歉，妈妈。
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉。
I get you thoughts of holy shit.
我让你想到了神圣的狗屎。
Oh, he's dead. He's dead.
哦，他死了。 他死了。
That guy died mocking God.
那家伙是嘲笑上帝而死的。
Do I need some?
我需要一些吗？
You need initial music playing right now.
您现在需要播放初始音乐。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
They don't do that and they don't play.
他们不这样做，他们不玩。
That's not that's not Mitchell D
那不是那不是米切尔 D
That's the root sense stuff on the.
那就是根义上的东西了。
Oh, like gas, gas, gas.
哦，就像煤气，煤气，煤气。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
The vibe. Tonight.
气氛。 今晚。
Yeah,
是的，
I know.
我知道。
Oh, God damn.
哦，该死的。
This car so slow.
这车好慢
Come on. No, no, you're doing good.
来吧。 不，不，你做得很好。
I'm good. We're doing good.
我很好。 我们做得很好。
We're doing good. OK, ok. Yeah.
我们做得很好。 好的好的。 是的。
And get, get, get, get, get, get, get.
得到，得到，得到，得到，得到，得到，得到。
All I di di di di di move all the way.
All I di di di di di 一路移动。
Karen reloading.
卡伦重装。
I'm reloading guns.
我正在重新装填枪支。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
That's cause that's nice, right?
那是因为那很好，对吧？
Oh, I got to go back there just like that.
哦，我必须就那样回到那里。
Mysta. Mysta.
米斯塔。 米斯塔。
Mysta. As I don't know about this.
米斯塔。 因为我对此一无所知。
I don't know about this. Mysta. Where we going to?
我不知道这件事。 米斯塔。 我们要去哪里？
I know i don't know my entire life, but i actually believe that
我知道我不知道我的整个人生，但我真的相信你你真的是一个很酷的游戏。
You believe in me.
你相信我。
You believe me. Believes in me.
你相信我。 相信我。
He believes in me.
他相信我。
I have to do it. I have to do it.
我必须这样做。 我必须这样做。
Believe me the whole time.
一直相信我。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
He could find down. The.
他可以找到下来。 这。
Oh, my fucking God.
哦，我的他妈的上帝。
You go down the middle.
你走中间。
Nice guy.
好人。
Keep going, keep going.
继续，继续。
Keep going, keep going. Yeah, I got this.
继续，继续。 是的，我得到了这个。
I got this. I'm not worried at all.
我懂了。 我一点也不担心。
Everything's under control.
一切都在掌控之中。
I'm keeping him off your back.
我让他远离你。
I'll just give it a little fuck bust.
我只会给它一点他妈的半身像。
Oh, no, you're out.
哦，不，你出去了。
We got him now.
我们现在得到了他。
The spikes are out. The spikes, blue spikes.
尖刺出来了。 尖刺，蓝色尖刺。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
Oh, we got to run.
哦，我们得跑了。
We got to run.
我们得跑了。
Got to get out.
该出去了。
Get out.
出去。
Rest.
休息。
Stay where you. Are, please.
留在你的地方。 是，请。
OK, Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
好吧，他妈的，他妈的，他妈的，他妈的，他妈的。
We got to run.
我们得跑了。
You got to be God's about
你必须是上帝的
it. Shooting like got something.
它。 射击就像得到了什么。
Why you you why you not moving?
为什么你你为什么你不动？
Oh, wait. You not moving?
等一下。 你不动？
I'm on the bottom of the screen, bro.
我在屏幕底部，兄弟。
Oh, shit. Oh, come on.
妈的。 哦，来吧。
This is a boat. Yeah. Take a boat. Take a bottle of the boom.
这是一条船。 是的。 乘船。 拿一瓶繁荣。
Ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba.
巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴巴。
That shot right?
拍的对吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Dude, how are we going to get away.
伙计，我们要怎么逃走。
From them in a fucking. Boat?
从他们他妈的。 船？
We're using horns well, the easiest targets in the world.
我们很好地使用了喇叭，这是世界上最容易瞄准的目标。
Yeah, well, I feel they could literally just come after us.
是的，好吧，我觉得他们真的可以追我们。
Still like this.
还是这样。
Walk on the side and don't I don't get it, OK?
一边走，我不明白，好吗？
I mean, it.
我是认真的。
Got it, I guess. OK.
明白了，我猜。 好的。
That was the better.
那是更好的。
Yeah, sure.
当然可以。
You're right.
你说的对。
All right.
好的。
I guess.
我猜。
Yeah.
是的。
All right.
好的。
Come on.
来吧。
Eventually we can. You actually did that? No. Oh, no.
最终我们可以。 你真的这样做了？ 不，哦，不。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Hold on, hold on. Wait.
等一下，等一下。 等待。
This shit. Oh, no, no.
这玩意。 哦，不，不。
I think I saw. Wait, wait.
我想我看到了。 等等。
Probably a shark. Leo.
应该是鲨鱼吧 狮子座。
I can't believe you didn't crash.
我不敢相信你没有崩溃。
I didn't believe in you.
我不相信你。
No, don't go that way. Don't go. Oh, you know, I'm supposed to.
不，不要那样做。 别去。 哦，你知道，我应该这样做。
You're clever.
你很聪明。
Yeah, yeah, yeah. And then go back. Back. OK,
耶耶耶。 然后回去。 后退。 好的，
they got straightened up.
他们得到了整理。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
Oh, way too much.
哦，太过分了。
Too much, too much. Too cold.
太多了，太多了。 太冷。
Oh, you know what?
哦，你知道吗？
We could have. Oh, no, it's ok.
我们可以有。 哦，不，没关系。
It didn't hurt that much.
它并没有那么痛。
Yeah, this is nice. OK.
是的，这很好。 好的。
All right.
好的。
Watch out there. Oh.
当心那里。 哦。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
You two, are you doing some popping me?
你们两个，你们是不是在打我？
I'm trying to get ok. You busy?
我正在努力让自己好起来。 你很忙？
I'm trying to.
我在尝试着。
Oh, no, they're my.
哦，不，它们是我的。
Fucking gotha.
他妈的哥达。
Oh, dude, your griefing, your griefing, your griefing.
哦，伙计，你的悲伤，你的悲伤，你的悲伤。
You griefing your griefing me. OK,
你难过你难过我。 好的，
ok, ok.
好的好的。
OK, let's keep going straight for it. Here.
好的，让我们继续前进。 这里。
Tom, tom, tom, tom, tom.
汤姆，汤姆，汤姆，汤姆，汤姆。
I need your help.
我需要你的帮助。
I need your god.
我需要你的上帝。
We need to do it together.
我们需要一起做。
We need to do it together. Mysta.
我们需要一起做。 米斯塔。
If we don't do it together, we're going to die.
如果我们不一起做，我们就会死。
Oh, my god. Our boat static.
我的天啊。 我们的船静。
Oh, my god. It's so that it's so.
我的天啊。 就是这样。
This is fine.
这可以。
Row, row, row, row, row, row, row, row.
行，行，行，行，行，行，行，行，行，行。
Row, row, row, row, row.
行、行、行、行、行。
OK, we've got the timing.
好的，我们有时间。
Good. Nice, nice that we guy row.
好的。 很好，很高兴我们排。
Nice straight.
好直。
Right, but straight.
对，但很直。
Nicely down the. Street. I'm turning.
很好地下来了。 街道。 我在转。
I need your help.
我需要你的帮助。
We're dead.
我们死了。
Fucking God, all your fault. It's not all your fault.
妈的，都是你的错。 这不全是你的错。
No, it's not oh, my God. Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
不，这不是哦，我的上帝。 等等，哇，哇，哇，哇。
Hold on. Just don't, don't, don't.
坚持，稍等。 只是不要，不要，不要。
OK, ok, nice, nice, nice. OK, now.
不错不错不错不错不错 现在没事了。
OK, we are turning.
好的，我们正在转弯。
We are turning.
我们正在转弯。
Let's turn together.
一起转吧。
Turn together row now we hold we hold down the.
转在一起排现在我们按住我们按住。
Stream
溪流
merrily, merrily, merrily life is what I dress for.
快活，快活，快活的生活是我穿衣的目的。
Right, right. Mysta.
是的是的。 米斯塔。
the bloody we go do it together.
该死的我们一起去做。
OK, ok, ok, ok.
好的，好的，好的，好的。
Left, left, left, left, left, left, left. OK.
左，左，左，左，左，左，左，左。 好的。
Right, right.
是的是的。
Right, right, right, right, right, right, right.
对，对，对，对，对，对，对，对。
Right, right, right, right, right.
对，对，对，对，对，对。
Oh, that's bullshit.
哦，那是胡说八道。
So left, left, left, left, left, left.
所以左，左，左，左，左，左。
Is so hard.
太难了。
Why is that so?
为什么呢？
Yeah, yeah, right, right, right, right.
对对对对对对。
Oh, my God. That's always.
我的天啊。 总是这样。
That's left.
那是留下的。
That's rotten. No. Oh, no, we're dead.
那是烂。 不，哦，不，我们已经死了。
We're dead.
我们死了。
Oh, no, we're fine.
哦，不，我们很好。
Oh, it's not winnable.
哦，赢不了。
Winnable and winnable. It's winnable.
可赢且可赢。 这是可赢的。
It's winnable.
这是可赢的。
I know.
我知道。
So what about you are so bad.
那你那么坏怎么办。
So bad.
太糟了。
It's not winnable.
这是无法获胜的。
It's not. Well, all I do, dude.
它不是。 好吧，我所做的一切，伙计。
How do how.
怎么办怎么办。
This is so hard to control I want to see.
这太难控制了，我想看看。
I want to see you. Guys do this shit acting like it's.
我要见你。 伙计们做这件事就像它一样。
So easy left there.
很容易离开那里。
OK, ok. OK.
好的好的。 好的。
OK. Gently, gently down the stream, right?
好的。 轻轻地，轻轻地顺流而下，对吗？
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
对，对，对，对。
OK, but why the side that? Well, this side.
好的，但为什么偏偏呢？ 嗯，这边。
That's good.
那很好。
I got it. I got it.
我得到了它。 我得到了它。
Got bad. OK, that's fine.
变坏了 好的，没关系。
That's fine. Fine. Left, left on the left.
没事儿。 美好的。 左边，左边左边。
See, I would like to see the opening stuff sliding, the sliding, complicated.
看，我想看开东西滑动，滑动，复杂。
Lubricated, lubrication lubricating this lubricant.
润滑，润滑润滑这种润滑剂。
Do you not know what lubricating is?
你不知道什么是润滑？
Are you oh, god.
你是哦，天哪。
Gently, gently, gently.
轻轻地，轻轻地，轻轻地。
OK, right.
好的，对。
Right. Yeah, you got it. You're under control.
对。 是的，你明白了。 你在控制之中。
I got it. Got it. Nice.
我得到了它。 知道了。 好的。
OK, a little bit more a little bit more.
好的，多一点点多一点点。
Just the right little love top.
恰到好处的小爱上衣。
Little left up.
有点左了。
OK, nice. OK.
好的，不错。 好的。
Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh.
嗯。 嗯。 嗯。 嗯。
Uh huh.
嗯。
Oh, I think we're through the worst of it.
哦，我想我们已经度过了最糟糕的时期。
Uh huh. The is just uh huh.
嗯。 这只是嗯。
It's just a smooth ride. Is it.
这只是一个平稳的旅程。 是吗。
I think you're supposed to see this straight ahead.
我认为你应该直接看到这一点。
What is this?
这是什么？
It's just a smooth ride behind ass
这只是屁股后面的平稳骑行
good. Oh.
好的。 哦。
Oh, my.
天啊。
Goes down on it.
继续下去。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Ow, ow, ow, ow,
呜呜呜呜呜呜
ow, ow, ow,
喔喔喔喔喔
oh. I got messed up.
哦。 我搞砸了。
Miss the l l That's all right.
想念 l l 没关系。
What is going on?
到底是怎么回事？
I can't move the left, left, left, left, left, right, right, right, right,
我动不了 左 左 左 左 左 右 右
right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right,
右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右
right, right, right, right.
对，对，对，对。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You fucking bottom. No, but I am moving.
你他妈的底。 不，但我要搬家了。
I'm telling you, bro, I'm pummelling as much as I can
我告诉你，兄弟，我尽我所能
talk. You paddle doggy bottle.
讲话。 你划狗奶瓶。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
OK, ok. All right. OK, ok.
好的好的。 好的。 好的好的。
OK. Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
好的。 哦，不，不，不，不，不，不。
No, no.
不，不。
Please do. That is a tight squeeze.
请做。 那是紧缩。
We know we can't make it.
我们知道我们做不到。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, oh.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Oh, no, no.
哦，不，不。
Oh, my god. Oh, my God.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。
How how. High. You were just better.
怎么怎么。 高的。 你只是更好。
You were just better.
你只是更好。
Just better.
更好。
We're just better.
我们只是更好。
OK? No, we're not. No, we're not.
好的？ 不，我们不是。 不，我们不是。
Look, it do go down.
看，它确实下降了。
You go down you go down it goes down.
你下去你下去它就下去。
I'm dead. Oh, no. Help!
我死了。 不好了。 帮助！
Help! You have to help me.
帮助！ 你必须帮助我。
I'm coming.
我来了。
I got you. I got you. Help.
我接到你了。 我接到你了。 帮助。
Oh, I got you.
哦，我得到你了。
I got you.
我接到你了。
You oh.
你哦。
Come on.
来吧。
No, you bitch, you bitch, you bitch.
不，你这个婊子，你这个婊子，你这个婊子。
Hold it.
拿着它。
Now, why are you doing this up?
现在，你为什么要这样做？
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Grab my hand.
抓住我的手。
Grab my fucking hand.
抓住我他妈的手。
You grab it
你抓住它
come on, guys.
拜托了伙计们。
I'm trying. I'm trying so hard.
我在尝试。 我很努力。
I'm trying my hand.
我正在尝试我的手。
I'm trying to reach out, reach out, reach out
我试图伸出手，伸出手，伸出手
reach out. Mysta.
伸手。 米斯塔。
I got you, man.
我得到你了，伙计。
I got you,
我接到你了，
I got you
我把你带到这里，好吗？
I never betray.
我从不背叛。
Let's get.
让我们得到。
Out cutesy pie now,
现在出可爱的馅饼，
that was a test.
那是一个考验。
You know, when you're at the peak of, like,
你知道，当你处于巅峰时，就像，
death, you show your true colours and you know what?
死亡，你展现了你的真面目，你知道吗？
You you called for my name.
你呼唤我的名字。
What if I.
如果我。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You're going to make. Me so now.
你要做。 我现在也是。
I'm going to go to Dairy Queen after this and buy a large blizzard because of you.
之后我要去Dairy Queen，因为你买了一个大的暴风雪。
A large blizzard.
一场大暴风雪。
Blizzard it's an ice cream.
暴雪是冰淇淋。
I need. I need. I need some ghost Tranter.
我需要。 我需要。 我需要一些幽灵Tranter。
You know, that's when I was craving ice cream, too.
你知道，那时我也想吃冰淇淋。
Oh, are. You. Are you Kurt?
哦，是。 你。 你是库尔特吗？
What is he? Once you want to get some ice cream together.
他是什么？ 一旦你想一起吃一些冰淇淋。
I want to get creamed. You know that cream can.
我想得到奶油。 你知道奶油可以。
Without them.
没有他们。
So give you a little something, a little.
所以给你一点东西，一点点。
Drizzled, give you a little drizzle on top of that till.
下毛毛雨，再给你一点毛毛雨。
Your favourite ice cream never.
你最喜欢的冰淇淋永远不会。
Told me. Leo, I love coffee.
告诉我。 狮子座，我喜欢咖啡。
What is your strawberry with Harvey.
你和哈维的草莓是什么？
And mint chocolate chip. Sauce?
还有薄荷巧克力片。 酱？
OK, you know what? Do you like it?
好的，你知道吗？ 你喜欢它吗？
Yeah, what you like?
对，你喜欢什么？
And which chocolate? Vanilla, strawberry.
哪种巧克力？ 香草，草莓。
You're so basic.
你太基础了。
Oh, my God. What's what else?
我的天啊。 还有什么？
How the hell did you pull that off?
你到底是怎么做到的？
Chocolate sauce sprinkles. OK,
巧克力酱洒。 好的，那发生了什么？
Everything was going our way.
一切都如我们所愿。
We even had a buyer.
我们甚至有一个买家。
But that greedy fuck a.
但是那个贪心的操啊。
Flake, chocolate flake.
片状，巧克力片。
What the fuck is a chocolate flake?
巧克力片是什么鬼？
It's like a chocolate bar that you put on top of ice cream.
它就像你放在冰淇淋上的巧克力棒。
That's flaky. Oh.
那是片状的。 哦。
You know
你知道
why you need.
为什么你需要。
Do you not like coffee? Ice cream?
你不喜欢咖啡吗？ 冰淇淋？
You only coffee? I don't. Like coffee.
你只喝咖啡？ 我不。 就像咖啡一样。
You only coffee flavour or coffee flavour, huh?
你只有咖啡味还是咖啡味，对吧？
No coffee. Cake. Same thing.
没有咖啡。 蛋糕。 一样。
No coffee cake.
没有咖啡蛋糕。
No coffee is gross.
没有咖啡是恶心的。
So what is this like? Gross.
那么这是什么样的呢？ 总的。
You are so gross.
你太恶心了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
John Wick.
约翰威克。
Oh, dude, I love that.
哦，伙计，我喜欢那个。
This is actually, like, the first. Star scene there.
这实际上是第一个。 那里的明星场景。
Yeah, like, we're far.
是的，就像，我们很远。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
The car shop
汽车店
oh, we're having a flashback right now.
哦，我们现在正在闪回。
Looks about right.
看起来是对的。
Chatter is not based.
Chatter 没有基础。
Shut up. Shop shuttle is based. Chocolate ice cream.
住口。 商店班车是根据。 巧克力冰淇淋。
I can agree with that.
我可以同意。
You know what? Being your favourite, I'm a little weird.
你知道吗？ 作为你的最爱，我有点奇怪。
Vanilla is not my favourite.
香草不是我的最爱。
You say that's my favourite.
你说那是我最喜欢的。
You said chocolate, vanilla?
你说巧克力，香草？
Strawberry. Yes.
草莓。 是的。
All the fucking Neapolitan flavours. Yeah.
所有他妈的那不勒斯风味。 是的。
And you said sprinkles. Oh, my God.
你说洒。 我的天啊。
What do you think? Gold gone
你怎么看？ 黄金不见了
oh, every.
哦，每一个。
That. I saw it.
那。 我看到了。
Wait, this is how he dies.
等等，他就是这样死的。
I know this is not his product, is it?
我知道这不是他的产品，是吗？
Pleasure doing business with you guys.
很高兴和你们做生意。
You two
你们俩
give me the case.
把案子给我。
What the fuck are you doing?
你他妈在做什么？
Give me the fucking case, Leo.
把他妈的案子给我，里奥。
Hand it over now.
现在交出来。
Jemma, what the fuck is wrong when I'm wrong?
杰玛，当我错的时候，他妈的怎么了？
It's nothing personal.
这不是个人的。
It's just. Business.
这只是。 商业。
What the fuck? Charmer.
什么鬼？ 魔术师。
Jealous? Oh,
嫉妒的？ 哦，
he wasted all those bullets. Easy to reload.
他浪费了所有这些子弹。 易于重新加载。
Quickly back
快速返回
it's out of there.
它在外面。
Unless they all know he's out.
除非他们都知道他出去了。
Do you think that guy was Vincent's brother?
你认为那个人是文森特的兄弟吗？
The whole time? Next thing.
整个时间？ 接下来的事情。
I know. As I remember, he said that his brother died.
我知道。 我记得，他说他哥哥死了。
I don't. Think Salisbury.
我不。 想想索尔兹伯里。
There's no way this is related, is it? Trust me.
这没有任何关系，是吗？ 相信我。
All we know, he said Harvey killed his brother Ross.
我们都知道，他说哈维杀了他的兄弟罗斯。
He probably came across, right? I might be him.
应该是碰到了吧？ 我可能就是他。
Damn. You're your detective for a.
该死。 你是你的侦探。
Reason, bro. Look.
理由啊老哥 看。
Actual wrinkles, folds in your brains.
实际的皱纹，褶皱在你的大脑中。
This thing.
这东西。
You know, one of these guys way, you know for sure.
你知道，这些人之一，你肯定知道。
So I want to kiss your beard.
所以我想亲吻你的胡子。
Let's go after him.
我们去追他吧。
I kiss your forehead, and we'll lick your sideburn.
我吻你的额头，我们会舔你的鬓角。
You just have to take it too far, man.
你只是太过分了，伙计。
You really want to take Harvey down? You have to take it too far.
你真的想打倒哈维？ 你必须走得太远。
What do you mean, take it to you for me? Would you touch my beard.
什么意思，替我拿给你？ 你会摸我的胡子吗？
With or without?
有还是没有？
It's like sacred territory. That is sacred territory.
它就像神圣的领土。 那是神圣的领域。
That's equivalent to my pubic hair.
那相当于我的阴毛。
And you wanna say you want to kiss it?
你想说你想亲吻它吗？
No, it's not.
不它不是。
You're saying you taking it too far, and you say, I'm
你说你太过分了，你说，我是
OK anyways.
无论如何都可以。
All right,
好的，
where can we find this guy?
我们在哪里可以找到这个人？
Oh. Going to be easy to find anyone.
哦。 会很容易找到任何人。
I'm easy to find. Family. Safe anyways.
我很容易找到。 家庭。 反正安全。
Of course.
当然。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
I'm saying I took it.
我说我拿走了。
You father. What the hell.
你父亲。 我勒个去。
Happened?
发生了？
What? Don't listen to yourself, man.
什么？ 不要听自己的，伙计。
Listen, what about the words that, like you.
听着，像你这样的词呢。
Spew out of my mouth of your mouth at your mouth?
从我的嘴里喷出你的嘴在你的嘴里？
Son, I don't listen to it.
儿子，我不听。
Oh, is that your son?
哦，那是你儿子吗？
My mouth I'm not speaking.
我的嘴我不说话。
He looks like he looks like Gregory.
他看起来像格雷戈里。
That's not my son, Alex.
那不是我的儿子，亚历克斯。
I looks like a little bitch.
我看起来像个小婊子。
That's your wife.
那是你的妻子。
Hey, my son. That's your wife.
嘿，我的儿子。 那是你的妻子。
That's her son.
那是她的儿子。
He said, Mom, that's not my kid.
他说，妈妈，那不是我的孩子。
Is it? Honey.
是吗？ 蜜糖。
My kid has bad. Then that's wrong.
我的孩子坏了。 那么这是错误的。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
That's not my son.
那不是我的儿子。
Ow, ow.
呜呜呜
Ow. Shit.
哦。 拉屎。
Alex.
亚历克斯。
Alex,
亚历克斯，
oh. Dude.
哦。 老兄。
He reminds me of Gregory.
他让我想起了格雷戈里。
Leo only ask you something personal.
狮子座只问你一些私人的事情。
Yeah, sure.
当然可以。
Gregory from Fanatic.
来自狂热的格雷戈里。
How do you.
你怎么。
Know the one?
知道那个吗？
The pledge to stay together in this line of work.
承诺在这项工作中团结一致。
You heard of a moment now, kid?
你现在听说过吗，孩子？
We've always been together the whole.
我们一直在一起。
Well, have you all we know you don't play poor games, right?
好吧，我们都知道你不玩糟糕的游戏，对吧？
I know myself.
我了解自己。
I've played some horror games.
我玩过一些恐怖游戏。
Yeah, I was.
是的，我是。
Wait for you to play well, last we met.
等你玩好，我们最后一次见面。
That awful. Oh, yeah. I think Fletch.
那太可怕了。 哦耶。 我认为弗莱奇。
You could say that.
你可以那样说。
Yeah, that's going to be, like, next week, I think.
是的，这将是，就像，下周，我想。
Actually. I'm sorry to hear that.
实际上。 我很遗憾听到。
I know.
我知道。
I need to get to 500 k. I bet I'm so close.
我需要达到 500 k。 我敢打赌，我是如此接近。
You're so close. Yeah.
你是如此接近。 是的。
They technique.
他们技术。
I was fortunate enough to have Linda.
我很幸运有琳达。
Linda, these nice.
琳达，这些不错。
That this even though sense. Away together.
这虽然有道理。 一起走。
That doesn't even make sense.
这甚至没有意义。
It wasn't even me.
甚至不是我。
And I'm laughing with you. I'm laughing.
我和你一起笑。 我在笑。
See, why am I laughing at it?
看，我为什么笑呢？
Well, well, you sound so disappointed, though.
好吧，好吧，不过，你听起来很失望。
That's that's.
就是这样。
Too many.
太多。
These nuts jokes used on me like that.
这些疯狂的笑话就是这样对我说的。
They're
他们是
I've.
我有。
Never thought I you know, I've.
没想到我知道，我知道。
Never thought I could be physically exhausted from colliding with somebody.
从来没有想过我会因与某人相撞而筋疲力尽。
You're, like, hitting the world record, and I'm.
你，就像，打破世界纪录，而我。
I'm impressed.
我很佩服。
That's all them alongside. Who?
旁边就是他们。 谁？
Marlon Dick in your mouth.
马龙迪克在你的嘴里。
Film.
电影。
It's a woman and a boy about this
这是一个女人和一个男孩关于这个
this.
这。
They had to move while I was inside.
当我在里面时，他们不得不移动。
I'm sure we'll find them.
我相信我们会找到他们的。
Huh? Well, it's.
嗯？ 嗯，是的。
Rough out here. Well.
这里粗暴。 好。
You got that right.
你说对了。
Well, I.
嗯，我。
Never actually set foot in a place like that.
从来没有真正踏足过那样的地方。
Thank you guys for coming to today's club.
感谢你们来到今天的俱乐部。
I thank you for coming to this club.
我感谢你来到这个俱乐部。
I'll see you.
回头见。
I'll see you tomorrow. All right.
明天见。 好的。
See you guys tomorrow.
明天见。
OK? I'm just kidding.
好的？ 我只是开玩笑。
Hello. Hi.
你好。 你好。
I'm gonna pretend that didn't happen.
我会假装那没有发生。
So my goddamn husband.
所以我该死的丈夫。
Oh, he better be back soon.
哦，他最好快点回来。
Oh, I think this is your wife.
哦，我想这是你的妻子。
That's not my wife.
那不是我的妻子。
We saw my wife on the screen knowing me.
我们在屏幕上看到我的妻子认识我。
Yeah, she's not. This lady's not. Pregnant.
是的，她不是。 这位女士不是。 孕。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
How can we bother these people?
我们怎么能打扰这些人呢？
If you see him, they're grilling barbecue.
如果你看到他，他们正在烤烧烤。
I want barbecue.
我要烧烤。
All had a barbecue and so many years.
所有人都有烧烤和这么多年。
What I'm not.
我不是什么。
Talk to you, lady.
和你谈谈，女士。
What's up?
怎么了？
You look upset.
你看起来很沮丧。
Oh, I am.
哦，我是。
I'm waiting for my goddamn husband.
我在等我该死的丈夫。
I'm going to beat his ass.
我要打他的屁股。
Yeah, that's you.
是的，就是你。
Have I seen him? What's he do?
我见过他吗？ 他是做什么的？
So why do.
那为什么要这么做。
I look at this?
我看这个？
He's been cheating on me, and nobody cheats on Martha Sansa.
他一直在欺骗我，没有人欺骗玛莎珊莎。
For what they. Censor.
他们为了什么。 审查。
What are we censoring, boy?
我们在审查什么，男孩？
Why are we fuckery censoring, huh?
为什么我们他妈的审查，是吧？
Let me get the sense already.
让我已经明白了。
I did.
我做到了。
I can't even.
我什至不能。
What's going to be shown cock
什么会显示公鸡
again or ass we've seen already
再次或我们已经见过的屁股
oh, hey, you want to ride on this with me?
哦，嘿，你想和我一起骑这个吗？
I don't think we can.
我不认为我们可以。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
We can't see on television. Cute
我们在电视上看不到。 可爱的
I just look at
我只是看看
baited me.
引诱我。
I thought we could have, you know, had a little had a little moments on the swings.
我以为我们可以，你知道，有一点在秋千上的时间。
I I'm not a swinger.
我不是浪荡公子。
Hey, there. Whoa.
嘿。 哇。
What the hell happened to this car?
这车到底是怎么回事？
Oh. Beats me.
哦。 打败我。
Just OK. I don't care anymore.
一般般啦。 我不在乎了。
Wow. Oh,
哇。 哦，
he bored me.
他让我厌烦。
He got me bored, man. Oh, I'll. Talk to you instead.
他让我感到无聊，伙计。 哦，我会的。 而是和你说话。
You look like you know you do.
你看起来就像你知道你做的那样。
You just grab the hammer and start going to work at their place.
你只需拿起锤子，开始在他们的地方工作。
I might have a job for you.
我可能有一份工作给你。
Interesting.
有趣的。
What job?
什么工作？
What are we talking about?
我们在说啥啊？
Oh, he wants me to join him. Oh, my God.
哦，他想让我加入他。 我的天啊。
That's your son. It strange.
那是你的儿子。 很奇怪。
That's not my son.
那不是我的儿子。
Well, let's check it out, ok?
好吧，让我们检查一下，好吗？
Maybe you are allergic to cash.
也许你对现金过敏。
All right, fine. I'll go see my kid.
好吧，好吧。 我会去看我的孩子。
Yeah, let's go look for. Look for your family.
是的，我们去寻找。 寻找你的家人。
You got to go see your wife and.
你得去见你的妻子。
Trying to find the
试图找到罚款。
What?
什么？
Get over here where we were.
到我们原来的地方过来。
Are you you mind you.
你介意吗。
Back in the shop.
回到店里。
Past the shop. OK?
过了那家店。 好的？
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, not
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不
my. This is pastiche.
我的。 这是拼贴。
Oh, my God. We can't play baseball. Holy shit.
我的天啊。 我们不能打棒球。 天啊。
Would you play baseball? Fine, fine, fine.
你会打棒球吗？ 不错不错不错
You interested?
你有兴趣吗？
I'll do a few pitches. Yeah, yeah. Come over here.
我会做几个投球。 是啊是啊。 过来这里。
Come over here.
过来这里。
Play with me. Thank you.
和我一起玩。 谢谢你。
I fucking hate you.
我他妈讨厌你。
Wait. Someone's moaning.
等待。 有人在呻吟。
Who's moaning?
谁在呻吟？
In the trailer?
在预告片中？
What's up?
怎么了？
Can I take a swig?
我可以喝一口吗？
Yep. Go ahead.
是的。 前进。
I threw it at your nuts.
我把它扔在你的坚果上。
Bitch.
婊子。
Like that oh.
那样哦。
Oh, bang.
哦，砰。
Right, dude, oh.
对了，伙计，哦。
That was good one.
那是一个很好的。
Oh. Oh,
哦。 哦，
right.
对。
OK, curveball.
好的，曲线球。
All I could. Curve it to.
尽我所能。 将其弯曲到。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
Oh. Good. OK.
哦。 好的。 好的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
How are you hitting these?
你怎么打这些？
Oh, oh, yeah.
哦，哦，是的。
Curveball.
曲线球。
Dude is bullshit.
哥们是胡说八道。
Oh. Yes.
哦。 是的。
I'm gonna fall. On. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
我要倒下了。 在。 坚持，坚持，坚持。
OK. OK,
好的。 好的，
all right.
好的。
Oh, my. God. All right, that's enough. It's my turn.
天啊。 上帝。 好吧，这就够了。 轮到我了。
Give me, give me, give me the bat.
给我，给我，给我球棒。
OK. Holy shit.
好的。 天啊。
I'm crazy.
我疯了。
Hi there.
你好呀。
Hi there. Give me your bet.
你好呀。 给我你的赌注。
Can I have a go? Sure.
我可以试试吗？ 当然。
Can I go on your baseball? Thanks, sir.
我可以去打你的棒球吗？ 谢谢先生。
Hey. Hey. Want to try?
嘿。 嘿。 想试试吗？
Yeah.
是的。
I don't care. Those balls throw those balls and I hit.
我不在乎。 那些球扔那些球，我击中了。
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
I just got to swing.
我只好荡秋千了。
How come on, one.
怎么来的，一个。
Throw it.
丢它。
Huh? What?
嗯？ 什么？
Come on.
来吧。
What's OK?
什么是好的？
OK, I'll do it earlier.
好的，我会早点做的。
Huh? Got it.
嗯？ 知道了。
All right. I got it now.
好的。 我现在明白了。
I got it now.
我现在明白了。
Huh? Huh.
嗯？ 嗯。
We come on. Oh.
我们来吧。 哦。
Oh. Fuck.
哦。 他妈的。
Oh, no.
不好了。
I got swinging, miss. Oh.
我摇摆不定，小姐。 哦。
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
Oh. Yeah. OK.
哦。 是的。 好的。
All right.
好的。
I get.
我明白了。
It. Come on. Come on. Come on, come on.
它。 来吧。 来吧。 好啦好啦。
Judy so lame.
朱迪好蹩脚。
Come on, come on, come on.
来吧，来吧，来吧。
Come on. Do it.
来吧。 去做吧。
Do it. Whoo!
去做吧。 哇！
Oh, nice.
不错哦。
Fuck. Huh?
他妈的。 嗯？
Now that's a homerun.
现在这是一个本垒打。
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha. Yeah.
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈。 是的。
What the hell? I'll do it.
我勒个去？ 我会做的。
I'm under. Nice.
我在下。 好的。
Under underwear.
内衣下。
Got it.
知道了。
I get it. Underwear.
我得到它。 内衣。
Oh. OK. That's enough. Thanks for. This.
哦。 好的。 足够了。 感谢。 这。
OK, you were supposed to be always.
好吧，你应该一直都是。
You are so bad. I want to hear.
你是如此糟糕。 我想听听。
What's nearby the trailer. Hold on. I'm done.
拖车附近有什么。 坚持，稍等。 我做完。
OK, so you're out.
好的，所以你出去了。
If you all said go check the trailer out, there's stuff happening in there.
如果你们都说去看看预告片，那里有事情发生。
You just stop because, like, you're bad and then you lost.
你只是停下来，因为，就像，你很糟糕，然后你输了。
No, I'm not bad.
不，我不坏。
This trailer
这个预告片
Are they jumping?
他们在跳吗？
I think they're playing jumping jacks or something.
我认为他们在玩跳跃千斤顶之类的。
Probably exercise you Mysta. the.
可能锻炼你的Mysta。 这。
So look it so.
就这样看吧。
Mysta. Mysta. Mysta.
米斯塔。 米斯塔。 米斯塔。
Mysta. Bad. Bad boy.
米斯塔。 坏的。 坏小子。
Can't see anything. Bad boy.
什么都看不见。 坏小子。
You can't see anything.
你什么都看不见。
Or you can't.
或者你不能。
I couldn't see anything. Hold on. I'm going.
我什么也看不见。 坚持，稍等。 我要去。
Take another look.
再看看。
If you tell me if you're trolling me right now.
如果你告诉我你现在是否在拖钓我。
I can't see anything.
我什么都看不见。
I can't.
我不能。
Yeah. I can't hear anything either. What's.
是的。 我也什么也听不见。 什么是。
I mean, I can.
我的意思是，我可以。
I can. I can hear. I just can't see.
我可以。 我可以听到。 我只是看不到。
Tell me, like, go inside.
告诉我，就像，进去。
No. You want to join them? Why?
不，你想加入他们吗？ 为什么？
I just want to.
我只想。
I just want to watch.
我只是想看看。
While you can enjoy while I'm gone.
当我不在的时候你可以享受。
OK, let's.
好吧，让我们。
I'm going to continue with the game.
我将继续比赛。
You can try to give me a. Boost, and I go in for the top.
你可以试着给我一个。 升压，我进入顶部。
Stop.
停止。
Ha ha ha.
哈哈哈。
Oh, God.
天啊。
And, you.
和你。
Know, you're not insensitive, and you can handle me through things right now.
要知道，你不是麻木不仁，你现在可以把事情搞定。
You're sexy.
你很性感。
You're fucking sexy. Because I want to watch someone.
你真他妈性感。 因为我想看一个人。
Doesn't mean that I'm into NPR.
并不意味着我喜欢 NPR。
As voyeurism. Voyeurism. That's what it's.
作为偷窥狂。 窥淫癖。 就是这样。
Guess I have 100% on voyeurism, actually.
猜猜我有 100% 偷窥，实际上。
Oh, hey.
噢！嗨。
I see just fine.
我看就好了。
Cops.
警察。
08. 080.
08. 080.
Oh. Now big. Oh.
哦。 现在大了。 哦。
Mind if we ask you a few questions?
介意我们问你几个问题吗？
Yeah, I do mind.
是的，我介意。
I'm kind of busy here.
我在这里有点忙。
And your husband has broken out of prison.
你丈夫已经越狱了。
Stop calling me ma'am. OK.
别再叫我夫人了 好的。
I have no clue where he is. Oh, shit.
我不知道他在哪里。 妈的。
If he tries. She looks like someone.
如果他尝试。 她看起来像一个人。
Yeah.
是的。
From like who? Oh, I don't know.
像谁？ 哦我不知道。
She looks like someone from, like, left for dead or something.
她看起来像一个人，就像，离开死亡或什么的。
I don't know.
我不知道。
One or two to four.
一到二到四个。
So she looks for the poor little girl.
于是她去找那个可怜的小女孩。
I've never played Portal. Oh,
我没玩过传送门。 哦，
so you're.
所以你。
Stupid.
愚蠢的。
So that makes sense. I
所以这是有道理的。 一世
you need to have, like,
你需要有一些脑细胞来玩传送门，你就像，你知道的。
Of course we are.
我们当然是。
Are you OK?
你还好吗？
You know, you're going to slam my.
你知道，你会猛烈抨击我的。
Cock against your face, you. Stupid little.
公鸡抵着你的脸，你。 小笨蛋。
Oh, it's.
哦，是的。
Like a moulding.
就像一个模具。
I'm officially not.
我不是正式的。
Your son rejected you.
你儿子拒绝了你。
Like it's stupid.
就像是愚蠢一样。
Ozzy, man, I got out of prison.
奥兹，伙计，我出狱了。
Don't worry, Leo.
别担心，狮子座。
He's just a little bit upset.
他只是有点不高兴。
Why He found out.
为什么他发现了。
Yeah, he saw it in the papers.
是的，他在报纸上看到了。
Oh, shit. So what?
妈的。 所以呢？
It's OK, baby.
没关系，宝贝。
So what.
所以呢。
You're wants it. Criminal. You escaped.
你是想要的。 刑事。 你逃了。
He committed you.
他答应了你。
You murdered people.
你杀了人。
Do you like me now? Yes, you are.
你现在喜欢我吗？ 是的，你是。
Yeah. I'm murder. Yeah. You murdered people along the way.
是的。 我是谋杀。 是的。 你一路杀了人。
Did you not see the cop car?
你没看到警车吗？
I fell off the cliff. I need to tell you what's going on.
我从悬崖上掉了下来。 我需要告诉你发生了什么事。
You shot. People.
你开枪了。 人们。
You just leave all this stuff.
你把所有这些东西都留下。
You were sitting in the back of the pickup truck shooting people the entire time.
你一直坐在皮卡车的后面向人开枪。
You're telling me you didn't kill anyone.
你告诉我你没有杀任何人。
But that's after I went to prison.
但那是在我入狱之后。
He doesn't know that.
他不知道。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He knows me. For well, in prison.
他认识我。 好吧，在监狱里。
Oh, he doesn't know that I did.
哦，他不知道我知道。
The cops.
警察。
Oh, go on the volunteer trail and take your food.
哦，走志愿者之路，带走你的食物。
What? They said?
什么？ 他们说？
Can I keep my food? Bullshit.
我可以保留我的食物吗？ 废话。
Oh, trust me.
哦，相信我。
I know
我知道
Still fixing bikes.
还在修自行车。
Still fixing those bikes.
还在修理那些自行车。
You know I do.
你知道我会的。
Oh, can we do dogs?
哦，我们可以做狗吗？
Yeah, I'm doing it right now.
是的，我现在正在做。
This is not Alex.
这不是亚历克斯。
Whereas I want to do that.
而我想这样做。
Oh. Oh, my God. Who
哦。 我的天啊。 谁
All right.
好的。
Why are you doing this?
你为什么做这个？
Over here.
这边。
Oh! Oh, my God.
哦！ 我的天啊。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Dude, OK. Yeah. 103.
伙计，好的。 是的。  103.
All right, your turn.
好吧，轮到你了。
I'm good at darts.
我擅长飞镖。
You're about to see right now.
你马上就要看到了。
And can you get out the way I call for when you're in the way?
当你挡道时，你能按照我要求的方式离开吗？
I can't. For what?
我不能。 为了什么？
Am I in your way?
我妨碍你了吗？
I mean, the way out the way. Am I in the way?
我的意思是，出路。 我挡路了吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I was in the way.
我挡路了。
I'm sorry. I didn't.
对不起。 我没有。
I was in the way. Oh, my God.
我挡路了。 我的天啊。
I'm giving you a tattoo. Right now.
我给你纹身。 现在。
OK. Move.
好的。 移动。
More.
更多的。
OK. More. OK.
好的。 更多的。 好的。
Dad, I just don't know why
爸爸，我只是不知道为什么
Fucking God.
他妈的上帝。
Look.
看。
Beat this.
打这个。
These
这些
Move it, move it.
移动它，移动它。
Move it down to the centre.
将其向下移动到中心。
Move it to the centre.
将其移至中心。
I don't need it.
我不需要它。
And since a couple of baby.
自从有了几个宝宝。
Triples, why me?
三胞胎，为什么是我？
I don't. Understand. I don't understand what you just did.
我不。 理解。 我不明白你刚刚做了什么。
What just happened there? Oh, boy.
那里刚刚发生了什么？ 好家伙。
What did you do?
你做了什么？
Is that, like, a rule?
像这样的规则吗？
I don't know about darts.
我不知道飞镖。
I'm playing.
我在玩。
Darts for.
飞镖。
Holy crap. And
碉堡了。 和
that's pretty cool, I guess.
这很酷，我猜。
Yeah.
是的。
Pretty cool.
很酷。
Yeah, I got good aim.
是的，我的目标很好。
Wow, dude. Wow.
哇，伙计。 哇。
OK, you're setting goals.
好的，你正在设定目标。
You know.
你知道。
However, what what do you mean?
然而，你是什么意思？
How many points ahead of me?
领先我多少分？
Have you got three bull's eyes?
你有三只牛眼吗？
Because you suck
因为你很烂
you're not supposed to go for bull's eyes.
你不应该去追求公牛的眼睛。
And darts are supposed to get four triples.
飞镖应该得到四个三倍。
What do you mean, triples?
三连是什么意思？
I don't understand what that means.
我不明白那是什么意思。
Whoa.
哇。
Beautiful lights.
美丽的灯光。
How does this work?
这是如何运作的？
I've never played darts before.
我以前从未玩过飞镖。
You never play darts? No.
你从来不玩飞镖？ 不。
I don't know. How this works. I just got to go for this answer.
我不知道。 这是如何工作的。 我只好去找这个答案。
What is that?
那是什么？
What is that? What?
那是什么？ 什么？
I thought you just got to.
我以为你刚到。
You got to go for this answer one half oh.
你必须为这个答案一半哦。
Not a bull's eye. Sucks. Did.
不是牛眼。 糟透了。 做过。
Bull's eye socks? Yes.
牛眼袜？ 是的。
You go for triple 20.
你去三倍20。
Is the.
是个。
The inner ring is a triple. Right. OK, OK.
内圈是三圈。 对。 好的好的。
And then the outer ring is a double fuck.
然后外环是双重他妈的。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Oh, the hell with sammy. OK.
哦，萨米见鬼了。 好的。
All right.
好的。
I understand.
我明白。
OK, you're not serious.
好吧，你不认真。
You. I had a I have a z buff.
你。 我有一个我有一个 z buff。
I had a fucking z buff. I don't know if they died so far.
我有一个他妈的z buff。 我不知道他们到目前为止是否死了。
I got I got gypped by the rolls.
我得到了我得到了卷。
Nice bike.
不错的自行车。
Thanks, guys. This is so good at darts.
多谢你们。 这在飞镖方面非常好。
I like darts.
我喜欢飞镖。
How long have you known Leo?
你认识狮子座多久了？
A while, I guess. It'll fuck you. This.
一段时间，我猜。 它会操你的。 这。
This is so shit.
这太狗血了。
That's your son's drawing.
那是你儿子的画。
So shakey.
好动摇。
Fuck. Is that your son?
他妈的。 那是你的儿子吗？
That's your son.
那是你的儿子。
What do you mean? Who the fuck is this?
你什么意思？ 这他妈是谁？
59. Violence. Bike.
59. 暴力。 自行车。
Yeah.
是的。
Thanks.
谢谢。
No wonder he hates you.
难怪他讨厌你。
OK, let's watch this house.
好吧，让我们看看这个房子。
Leave me.
离开我。
Alone. Well, fuck you.
独自的。 好吧，去你妈的。
Go to hell.
去死吧。
Whoa, kid.
哇，孩子。
Hold up. Hold up, kid. You can't just.
耽误。 坚持住，孩子。 你不能只是。
Where are you? Going
你在哪里？ 去
once you could stop him.
一旦你可以阻止他。
You know I can't stop.
你知道我停不下来。
No, I can't stop him. No, he's doing.
不，我不能阻止他。 不，他在做。
He's. He's too switch partners.
他是。 他也是开关伙伴。
He's too slick with it.
他太狡猾了。
Man. I watched you.
男人。 我看着你。
Piece you sick with it.
让你觉得恶心。
And I watched you let him go.
我看着你让他走。
Go to the tree house where we had to go to a tree house.
去树屋，我们不得不去树屋。
A tree house?
树屋？
Oh, it's over there. OK, can I go with you now?
哦，在那边。 好的，我现在可以和你一起去吗？
This is your money. This is only for you. Yeah.
这是你的钱。 这只是给你的。 是的。
Have you ever been to a tree house before?
你以前去过树屋吗？
I've never had a tree house.
我从来没有树屋。
I've never been to one now. Same.
我从来没有去过一个。 相同的。
I feel like doing some good this way.
我觉得用这种方式做一些好事。
Oh, you can.
哦，你可以。
So what do you do?
所以你会怎么做？
You just get no clocks?
你只是没有时钟？
Yeah, I just got talk to your wife. I think I'm.
是的，我刚和你妻子谈过。 我想我是。
Waiting.
等待。
You're cooking me something.
你在给我煮东西。
And schmoozing your wife. Grab me a wrench.
和你的妻子闲聊。 给我一把扳手。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Oh, my God. I am. Man. You're cooking me.
我的天啊。 我是。 男人。 你在给我做饭。
I am cooking you.
我在给你做饭。
Come on, slap me up, Alex.
来吧，打我一巴掌，亚历克斯。
Dude, hey.
伙计，嘿。
Vincenzo.
文森佐。
That's my wife now.
那是我现在的妻子。
This.
这。
What is this?
这是什么？
This is an axe cut.
这是一个斧头切割。
I know it is broken. Yeah, I could do that.
我知道它坏了。 是的，我可以这样做。
Oh, it's a sign.
哦，这是一个标志。
Come down and help me fix it.
下来帮我修一下。
Just won't come down until I fix it.
在我修好之前不会下来。
I'm having a touching moment right
我现在有一个感人的时刻，你只会玩摩托车。
I got an achievement for that.
我为此取得了成就。
I think I'm going to need it. I didn't get share
我想我会需要它。 我没有分享
you need a hammer and a hammer to fix this one.
你需要一把锤子和一把锤子来修理这个。
There's a hammer right there.
那里有一把锤子。
It's got to be cut the hammer
它必须被砍断锤子
You're really just helping my wife, right?
你真的只是在帮助我的妻子，对吧？
Yes, I am.
我是。
Maybe you're
也许你是
downtown the bank.
市中心的银行。
Oh, this sign is beautiful.
哦，这个标志很漂亮。
Alex, you should come down and see it.
亚历克斯，你应该下来看看。
Give your give your wife's ride on the spike
让你的妻子骑上钉鞋
what's it?
它是什么？
This kid is so easily influenced me.
这孩子太容易影响我了。
What happened? I wasn't paying attention. It was.
发生了什么？ 我没注意。 它是。
All I did was fix a sign, and I was back down oh.
我所做的只是修复一个标志，然后我就退缩了哦。
Fuck you.
去你的。
He loves you. Oh, yeah. I see a lot of him.
他爱你。 哦耶。 我看到他很多。
What do you mean, you don't want to hug him?
什么意思，你不想抱他？
That's your child.
那是你的孩子。
Would just run away.
只会逃跑。
From me like an asshole. He's.
从我那里像个混蛋。 他是。
He's confused.
他很困惑。
He doesn't know, like, what to think. Basketball.
他不知道，比如，在想什么。 篮球。
I just play basketball. Basketball?
我只是打篮球。 篮球？
I'm better than. You at basketball right. Now. You're not?
我比。 你在篮球对。 现在。 你不是？
Yes, I am.
我是。
OK, this guy might.
好吧，这家伙可能会。
Want to shoot some hoops.
想投篮。
That could be fun, but maybe we should get going.
那可能很有趣，但也许我们应该开始。
Oh, come on. Just one game.
哦，来吧。 一场比赛而已。
Just one. Just one, guys. One game.
只有一个。 只有一个，伙计们。 一场比赛。
Get ready.
做好准备。
That boy seems like a terrible idea when I.
当我的时候，那个男孩似乎是个糟糕的主意。
You know, I win.
你知道，我赢了。
I ain't like a kid. Beat me.
我不像个孩子。 打我。
I think he's going to roll you.
我想他会滚你。
I don't know.
我不知道。
It's you thinking this kid is going to roll me.
是你认为这孩子要滚我。
He got one. It's yours. Ok?
他得到了一个。 这是你的。 好的？
Oh, shit.
妈的。
OK. Oh, shit. OK.
好的。 妈的。 好的。
Wait. Five
等待。 五
Daddy, pass it to me.
爸爸，把它交给我。
Knock, knock him over.
敲，敲他。
Knock him over. Come over. Vincent.
打倒他。 过来。 文森特。
I don't know
我不知道
oh, you suck my ball now going.
哦，你现在吮吸我的球。
What's. That's it.
什么是。 这就对了。
Ow! Ow! Ow!
哦！ 哦！ 哦！
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, fell.
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊摔
Oh, there you go.
哦，给你。
No, my now, bitch.
不，我现在，婊子。
Oh, oh, fuck off. That's mine.
哦，哦，滚蛋。 那是我的。
Wait, your kids sucks.
等等，你的孩子很烂。
Yes, I know.
是的，我知道。
This kid's OK.
这孩子没事。
Why is this kid so bad?
这孩子怎么这么坏？
Oh, my God. On he got the bad genes.
我的天啊。 他得到了坏基因。
Oh, look.
哦，看。
See that
看到那个
you fucking
你他妈的
proposed to me by Kobe you.
科比你向我求婚的。
You're such a gremlin.
你真是个小鬼。
What's it?
它是什么？
Schoenbaum
勋鲍姆
oh, now he has it.
哦，现在他有了。
How did he get.
他是怎么得到的。
I don't know.
我不知道。
How he. Doing? What? Help, Alex?
他怎么。 正在做？ 什么？ 帮助，亚历克斯？
What is he doing?
他在做什么？
What am I supposed to be?
我应该是什么？
I'm his phone
我是他的电话
why did you do that?
你为什么这么做？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I thought you know this. You're you're. Good.
我以为你知道这一点。 你就是你。 好的。
You think? Yeah.
您认为？ 是的。
What the hell, man?
什么鬼，伙计？
Really I'm trying to hype him up.
我真的是想炒作他。
He wants to be.
他想成为。
He wants to be a basketball player.
他想成为一名篮球运动员。
That's my kid, bro.
那是我的孩子，兄弟。
Hey, beautiful.
你好，漂亮的女士。
Hey. I think I'm just taking your family.
嘿。 我想我只是带走你的家人。
Yeah,
是的，
I hope I.
我希望我。
Your wife. Fine.
你老婆。 美好的。
He's my son.
他是我的儿子。
I know.
我知道。
And I took your basketball school.
我带走了你的篮球学校。
I'm a basketball bitch. Alex.
我是个篮球婊子。 亚历克斯。
Here you go.
干得好。
Still playing with him. To.
还在跟他玩。 到。
So this is home now?
所以现在这里是家？
I had. I leave. Give me out of here.
我有。 我走了。 让我离开这里。
I have to walk into this Mysta. I'm stuck.
我必须走进这个Mysta。 我被困住了。
I get moving.
我动起来。
You stay with my son.
你留在我儿子身边。
How we get me out.
我们如何让我出去。
I'm going to go you for sex.
我要去找你做爱。
See x oh, my god.
见 x 哦，我的上帝。
Just dunks.
只是扣篮。
I trust
我相信
you dunk my balls into my wife.
你把我的球灌入我的妻子。
That's why you dunked. Shows.
这就是你扣篮的原因。 节目。
Leo. Fucking loser. Let's just deal.
狮子座。 他妈的失败者。 让我们交易吧。
I'm stuck, i'm stuck. I can't get out of here.
我被困住了，我被困住了。 我不能离开这里。
I really have to entertain the child.
我真的要让孩子开心。
No, knock me out.
不，把我赶出去。
Kick me out
赶我出去
you guys are going to have sex.
你们要发生性关系。
Ray, can I join that ass? No.
雷，我可以加入那个混蛋吗？ 不。
I'm sure he knows where Harvey's hiding.
我相信他知道哈维藏在哪里。
Paula, let me check her out, and then you can join.
宝拉，让我看看她，然后你就可以加入了。
He's working at the construction site downtown.
他在市中心的建筑工地工作。
Yeah.
是的。
I need you to be ready to leave the country soon.
我需要你准备好尽快离开这个国家。
Don't worry about that.
不用担心那个。
I'll take care of it.
我会照顾它。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
My wife is so nice.
我老婆真好
Yeah. Now, don't just scare me.
是的。 现在，不要只是吓唬我。
Get back safe or I'll kick your ass.
安全回来，否则我会踢你的屁股。
Oh, Jesus. Ow!
哦，耶稣。 哦！
Ow! Ow!
哦！ 哦！
OK. I do.
好的。 我愿意。
White Jesus.
白耶稣。
Well, she's really nice.
嗯，她真的很好。
I thought she'd be angry at you.
我以为她会生你的气。
She's a top.
她是一个顶尖的。
That's where I get my top energy from my wife.
这就是我从妻子那里获得最大能量的地方。
Really? I don't think that's how it works.
真的吗？ 我不认为它是这样工作的。
Here you go.
干得好。
Oh, she's just black.
哦，她只是黑。
I think you have a gun. Help us.
我想你有枪。 帮助我们。
Oh, I'm going to kiss her.
哦，我要吻她。
Don't look.
不要看。
I'm looking at you.
我在看着你。
You're literally staring right now. The fuck is wrong with you?
你现在真的在盯着看。 你他妈有毛病？
You were. Really good. Yeah.
你之前是。 真的很好。 是的。
Like I said, you're a real pro.
就像我说的，你是一个真正的专业人士。
You think.
您认为。
Yeah. You played with my kids.
是的。 你和我的孩子们一起玩。
High five.
举手击掌。
I was subjected to torments while you fucking had
当你他妈的在过去 3 个小时里发生性关系时，我受到了折磨。
But you take care of your mom now.
但是你现在照顾你妈妈。
All right? Can we be.
好的？ 我们可以吗。
Relaxed? I was up. 3 hours is like, 2 minutes.
轻松？ 我起来了。  3小时等于2分钟。
Oh, come on, give me a hug.
哦，来吧，给我一个拥抱。
Oh. Look at that.
哦。 看那个。
You are my son.
你是我的儿子。
Go to your mom now. OK?
现在去找你妈妈。 好的？
You said you are my son.
你说你是我的儿子。
Oh, oh. Is he adopted?
哦，哦。 他被收养了吗？
Thank you.
谢谢你。
By the way, son, you're adopted.
顺便说一句，儿子，你被收养了。
Goodbye.
再见。
Well, I was just reminding him you are nice
好吧，我只是提醒他你很好
that you said you aren't my son.
你说你不是我的儿子。
No, you are. You are.
不，你是。 你是。
Oh. Oh, look, it's. GTA.
哦。 哦，看，是的。 侠盗猎车手。
You said that.
你之前这么说。
Room five.
五号房。
I want to play GTA. I don't play.
我想玩GTA。 我不玩。
I didn't say it was GTA.
我没说这是GTA。
Oh, yeah, it is.
哦，是的，是的。
Yes, you did. You better.
是的，你做到了。 你更好。
What if he doesn't.
如果他没有怎么办。
I'm recycling consent.
我正在回收同意。
OK, it's been like an hour since then.
好吧，从那以后已经过去了一个小时。
Most people have like funnelled out and you people are in. OK.
大多数人都喜欢漏斗，而你们也加入了。好的。
Is that how it works?
它是这样工作的吗？
Yes, yes.
是的是的。
When we had to talk to someone.
当我们不得不和某人交谈时。
What's the problem?
问题是什么？
What's the problem is a coffee shop, which is a construction site.
问题是咖啡店，这是一个建筑工地。
You can't just waltz in here.
你不能在这里跳华尔兹。
You know, put out hot hot.
你知道的，把热的热的。
Love threats bluff I want to bluff.
爱威胁虚张声势 我想虚张声势。
OK, fine.
好的。
It's bluff and you're going to stop me.
这是虚张声势，你要阻止我。
You'll have to excuse my colleague.
你将不得不原谅我的同事。
He hasn't had his morning coffee yet, but he's right, though.
他还没有喝早茶，但他是对的。
We're here to check if this site is up to code.
我们在这里检查该站点是否符合代码要求。
Jesus Christ.
耶稣基督。
Another inspection.
另一个检查。
What is with you guys back? Me?
你们回来怎么了？ 我？
I actually believe that Dominic comment.
我实际上相信多米尼克的评论。
Yeah, I'm coming in. Come in and come in.
是的，我进来了。进来进来。
Come in and come in.
进来进来进来。
Come endless. Come calm. Me.
来无止境。 冷静下来。 我。
Oh, my God. There you go. Whole
我的天啊。 你去吧。 所有的
art house.
艺术之家。
I hope you're building code, man.
我希望你正在构建代码，伙计。
You hard hats even work?
你的安全帽甚至工作？
How many?
多少？
I'm pretty sure they do.
我很确定他们会这样做。
Imagine, like, that big block of wood just fell on your head.
想象一下，那块大木头刚刚落在你的头上。
OK, I think. I get squashed.
好吧，我想。 我被压扁了。
No, it would just it would slide off.
不，它只会滑落。
I wish I could say the same.
我希望我能说同样的话。
We just said the heart. It.
我们只说心。 它。
What the hell? Well, about safety.
我勒个去？ 嗯，关于安全。
Always cock.
总是鸡巴。
What is that? To be afraid of it.
那是什么？ 害怕它。
Nothing's going to happen, kid.
什么都不会发生，孩子。
Nothing's going to happen. OK, all right.
什么都不会发生。 好的没问题。
I'm pretty sure I do.
我很确定我知道。
Construction sites have, like, a high fatality rate guy.
建筑工地有一个高死亡率的家伙。
OK, so are you being sarcastic? What?
好吧，那你是在讽刺吗？ 什么？
Me? No. Oh, you just went into the toilets.
我？ 不，哦，你刚进了厕所。
Honest people. Me, honestly, knock me over.
诚实的人。 我，老实说，把我打倒。
Please don't knock him. Is that possible? Hey.
请不要敲他。 那可能吗？ 嘿。
Oh, hey, man.
哦，嘿，伙计。
Why is I
为什么我是哦，嘿。
What is he doing?
他在做什么？
What?
什么？
I can't hear you for your book.
我听不见你的书。
It's my what?
这是我的什么？
You're I don't think you're talking to the right guy.
你是我不认为你在和合适的人说话。
He's probably.
他大概是。
You know where he is.
你知道他在哪里。
What? Mysta.
什么？ 米斯塔。
Your boss, miss?
你的老板，小姐？
You're talking to the wrong dude.
你说错人了。
What do you mean? He's just stupid.
你什么意思？ 他只是愚蠢。
He can't hear you.
他听不见你的声音。
He can't hear you. He's jacking it.
他听不见你的声音。 他在顶它。
Why does he turn it off?
他为什么关掉它？
He talks to him no. Oh, my god.
他跟他说没有。 我的天啊。
Fine, fine. Let's go get us nowhere.
很好，很好。 让我们无处可去。
No watch.
没有手表。
Sorry.
对不起。
All right, you guys you're
好吧，你们很忙。
I know you got all week.
我知道你整整一个星期。
I fucking knew.
我他妈的知道。
You'd take a break.
你会休息一下。
And I did I can't take a break now.
我做到了，我现在不能休息。
I will find my.
我会找到我的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
That's Ashley Reagan's whereabouts.
那是阿什利·里根的下落。
Does is.
确实是。
Dude, the cow likes me.
伙计，牛喜欢我。
The fucking jock camera guy likes me or likes me in this game.
在这场比赛中，他妈的摄像师喜欢我或喜欢我。
Why is that, Leo?
为什么会这样，里奥？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Everyone hates me, even the animals.
每个人都讨厌我，甚至动物。
Sam Beck is killing me.
山姆贝克杀了我。
I have to quit this job before I end up a cripple. Ha.
我必须在我变成瘸子之前辞掉这份工作。 哈。
I found an elevator. Oh. Ooh, elevator use.
我找到了一部电梯。 哦。 哦，电梯使用。
Come on in, baby. Come on in. Hold on.
进来吧宝贝 进来。等一下。
I'm going to look around real quick.
我要快速环顾四周。
You really got to me. Hey, can we do this with each other?
你真的来找我了。 嘿，我们可以一起做吗？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
OK, fine.
好的。
No, Jeff.
不，杰夫。
Over there. Arm wrestling.
在那边。 手臂摔跤。
Wrestling. Hold on. Wait. Hold on a second.
摔角。 坚持，稍等。 等待。 稍等一下。
Yeah. Can't handle it.
是的。 处理不了。
All right, you want it?
好吧，你想要吗？
I'm going to arm wrestle all right.
我要去打架，好吧。
Well, no, no, I won't arm wrestle till you give me.
好吧，不，不，除非你给我，否则我不会摔跤。
All right, finally the thing.
好吧，终于有事了。
Oh, here we go.
哦，我们开始吧。
Here you go. Oh, Mysta. This. Here we go.
干得好。 哦，米斯塔。 这。 开始了。
We take him down one. Yeah,
我们把他拿下来一个。 是的，
not enough.
不够。
Man. Come on, come on.
男人。 好啦好啦。
What the fuck
什么鬼
mister? Nice
先生？ 好的
mister. Mysta.
先生。 米斯塔。
I'm top.
我是顶级的。
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起。 对不起。
I'm top dog.
我是顶级狗。
You have to give up eventually.
你最终必须放弃。
Your fuck you bitch.
你他妈的你这个婊子。
You bitch
你个婊子
oh, come on.
哦，来吧。
Give I give up, you know,
放弃我放弃，你知道，
fuck you
去你的
oh, my hand.
哦，我的手。
Oh, God, you. Oh.
哦，上帝，你。 哦。
Ow! Oh.
哦！ 哦。
Mysta. Mister, my arm hurts my arm worse.
米斯塔。 先生，我的胳膊疼得更厉害了。
Thank you, Bob.
谢谢你，鲍勃。
No, no, no more give up.
不，不，不要再放弃了。
No take.
不拿。
I'm going to go beyond
我要超越
gas coupons.
煤气券。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I missed my fingers.
我错过了我的手指。
Why not?
为什么不？
No. Fuck you.
不，操你。
You've not, right? No. Fuck you.
你没有，对吧？ 不，操你。
I'm trying to prove a point.
我试图证明一点。
He's got a point.
他有道理。
You make me laugh.
你让我发笑。
I got
我有
you got
你得到了
no, no, no, no. You
不不不不。 你
handle it.
处理它。
Oh, my God. You are so bad.
我的天啊。 你是如此糟糕。
You fuck my arm.
你操我的胳膊。
Oh, my God. Oh,
我的天啊。 哦，
all right.
好的。
The strongest boxing wins again.
最强的拳击再次获胜。
Oh, there's.
哦，有。
No rounds here.
这里没有轮回。
You go get get back and get back your best, too.
你也去找回自己，找回最好的自己。
I think that's true. I think that's two and three.
我认为这是真的。 我认为是二三。
That's two out of three of us. Two out of three.
那是我们三个人中的两个。 三分之二。
I refuse.
我拒绝。
Oh. Fine.
哦。 美好的。
How? Why not? How?
如何？ 为什么不？ 如何？
If I win this one, I win. OK, fine.
如果我赢了这一场，我就赢了。 好的。
If you want us younger, you win for real.
如果你想让我们更年轻，你就赢了。
You have to go find my friend. Let's do this.
你得去找我的朋友。 我们开工吧。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Two, one,
二，一，
come on, come on, come on.
来吧，来吧，来吧。
Jeff,
杰夫，
what the fuck?
什么鬼？
What do you mean, what the fuck, your love.
你是什​​么意思，他妈的，你的爱。
I slipped.
我滑倒了。
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
What the fuck all right, let's do it again.
什么他妈的好吧，让我们再做一次。
Let's do it again. Do again. I was going easy on me last time.
让我们再来一次。 再做一次。 我上次对我很轻松。
All winner wins, winner wins.
所有的赢家都赢了，赢家赢了。
All right, all right, all right.
好的，好的，好的。
Look, come a long way.
看，走得很远。
Ahmad, can you do a prediction?
艾哈迈德，你能预测一下吗？
Oh, my. God. I am so.
天啊。 上帝。 我就是这样。
My hands are so fucked.
我的手太烂了
Holy shit. Oh, yeah.
天啊。 哦耶。
All right.
好的。
Dudes.
伙计们。
When you started laughing, I started, like, flipping you.
当你开始笑时，我开始，就像，翻转你。
I don't know why you did that. Jesus Christ.
我不知道你为什么那样做。 耶稣基督。
OK, you ready?
好的，你准备好了吗？
Do this the week two.
第二周做这个。
What? Nice
什么？ 好的
hey. Come down.
嘿。 坠落。
Down. Yes.
向下。 是的。
Nice.
好的。
Come on, come on, come on.
来吧，来吧，来吧。
Yeah,
是的，
yeah. OK.
是的。 好的。
You can't.
你不能。
Handle it.
处理它。
Yeah,
是的，
can't handle it.
无法处理。
All right, mysta no, no.
好吧，mysta 不，不。
Stop, mysta!
别了，米斯塔！
up don't say anything.
起来不说什么。
Mysta.
米斯塔。
stop making me laugh.
别逗我笑了。
Mysta. Mysta.
米斯塔。 米斯塔。
Mysta. Mysta. Cock balls, cock and balls.
米斯塔。 米斯塔。 公鸡球，公鸡和球。
Cock, eyeballs. These, these, these, these. And it's massive.
公鸡，眼球。 这些，这些，这些，这些。 它是巨大的。
Dusty, dusty.
尘土飞扬，尘土飞扬。
Dusty that's suggesting that dusty and it in it and in it.
尘土飞扬的意思是尘土飞扬，它在里面和里面。
Oh, god, no. God.
哦，天哪，不。 上帝。
Why is this so hard?
为什么这么难？
Why is it so hard? How did you do this? How?
为什么这么难？ 你是怎么做的？ 如何？
Come on, come on.
好啦好啦。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
How? Hi,
如何？ 你好，
yeah.
是的。
Belly laugh.
肚皮笑。
You make me laugh
你让我笑
me back.
我回来了。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Fucking I mess ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
他妈的我乱了哈哈哈哈哈哈。
Just go on now. Go.
现在就继续吧。 去。
Oh. What?
哦。 什么？
No, no. No, no, no,
不，不。 不不不，
Accept it.no, man.
接受它。不，伙计。
Just fucking accept it! no good. Give up, boys.
就他妈的接受吧！ 不好。 放弃吧，孩子们。
I can't.
我不能。
I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. Oh, shit.
我不能。 我不能。 我不能。 我不能。 妈的。
Johnny, I got it.
强尼，我明白了。
I got it. Let's go.
我得到了它。 我们走吧。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Come on.
来吧。
Come on,
来吧，
guys.
伙计们。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
My fingers hurt.
我的手指受伤了。
My fingers hurt. Mysta, just give up. Just give up.
我的手指受伤了。 米斯塔，放弃吧。 放弃吧。
What's up?
怎么了？
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
哦，哦，哦，哦。
You can't handle the
你不能处理整个神圣的狗屎头。
You are so fucking stupid.
你真他妈傻。
Every time I went down, I lost you.
每次我跌倒，我都失去了你。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Take him down. Oh, my God.
把他拿下来。 我的天啊。
And now I need to.
现在我需要。
Not enough.
不够。
I need to fucking spray myself.
我他妈要喷我自己。
I'm sweating. So you're sweating.
我在出汗。 所以你出汗了。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
I got oh.
我得到哦。
Let's go, let's go.
走吧，走吧。
Ha ha ha.
哈哈哈。
Take them down. Take them down. Yeah.
把它们拿下来。 把它们拿下来。 是的。
Holy shit.
天啊。
That was that's more.
那就是更多。
That was more epic than the fucking fucking Christ.
那比他妈的基督还要史诗。
The Recog and Tsunade. His arm wrestling.
Recog 和 Tsunade。 他的手臂摔跤。
Come on, come on. Hello.
好啦好啦。 你好。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
My arm. Hurts. Hold on. Give me a second.
我的手臂。 疼。 坚持，稍等。 你稍等一会儿。
Yeah, same to I actually side's sweating hot from that.
是的，和我一样，实际上我一边汗流浃背。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Shoto, shotop?
肖特，肖特？
OK, whatever.
好吧，随你便。
Chat or whatever.
聊天什么的。
I want the first one.
我要第一个。
Yeah, but you want you lost the next two.
是的，但你希望你失去接下来的两个。
The first one is. Oh, the first one is always.
第一个是。 哦，第一个总是。
The first one is always a warm up.
第一个总是热身。
Sorry. No, the second one was so bullshit. Did
对不起。 不，第二个太废话了。 做过
you got caught off guard?
你措手不及？
Know what to say?
知道该说什么吗？
Yeah, I. Did. Yeah. You are.
是啊，我做了。 是的。 你是。
You're underestimating.
你低估了。
You underestimated me.
你低估了我。
That's your.
那是你的。
Fault. Oh, my God.
过错。 我的天啊。
Can you explain this shit?
你能解释一下这个狗屎吗？
Yeah. It looks like you just spit it out.
是的。 看起来你只是把它吐出来。
It's two here.
这里是两个。
I told you it should be four.
我告诉过你应该是四个。
Well, no, no, no.
嗯，不，不，不。
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
You misunderstood, you fucking idiot.
你误会了，你这该死的白痴。
Making fun of him too much.
太取笑他了。
I'm sure we do.
我相信我们会的。
OK, you chat you go home.
OK，你聊聊你回家吧。
But, sir, sign them.
但是，先生，请签字。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
You get away.
你滚开。
Oh, shit. Yeah, I'll go this way. All Do we know him?
妈的。 是的，我会走这条路。 我们认识他吗？
Do we know him? OK, I'm chasing.
我们认识他吗？ 好的，我在追。
He's all ok.
他一切都好。
Shit. The elevator.
拉屎。 电梯。
Go. Fuck, yeah.
去。 他妈的，是的。
I'm still on his ass and still on his ass.
我仍然在他的屁股上，仍然在他的屁股上。
Never eat shit. That
永远不要吃屎。 那
chess, that dada.
国际象棋，那个达达。
That that that that that that that that that.
那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个
What are you doing? OK.
你在做什么？ 好的。
How is that the elevator what are you doing?
那个电梯你在干什么？
Come on.
来吧。
I'm breaking my ass over here while you're enjoying a fucking joyride.
当你在享受他妈的兜风时，我正在这里打破我的屁股。
No, I'm chasing him right now.
不，我现在正在追他。
What are you doing? asshole?
你在做什么？ 混蛋？
I'm trusting him to bang
我相信他会爆炸
on this guy's face. Oh.
在这家伙的脸上。 哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I hope. I thought I had to help him for second.
我希望。 我想我必须第二次帮助他。
I can't believe he's asking me to tap more shit.
我不敢相信他要我敲更多的狗屎。
My fingers are so dead.
我的手指已经死了。
OK. OK, ok, ok. OK, ok, ok.
好的。 好好好。 好好好。
OK. You went into the orange room oh.
好的。 你进了橙色房间哦。
What? Just go in.
什么？ 进去吧。
But wait.
可是等等。
We have to redo it.
我们必须重做。
It was.
它是。
Oh, I think we do that.
哦，我想我们是这样做的。
Some people did lose. Yeah, we lost
有些人确实输了。 是的，我们输了
weight.
重量。
I blame you. Oh.
我怪你。 哦。
Yes, you slow did.
是的，你慢了。
You were way too slow.
你太慢了。
What do you mean, i'm too slow?
什么意思，我太慢了？
You cut me off. It's all your time.
你打断了我。 这是你所有的时间。
Sorry.
对不起。
I see you. You're fine.
我看见你。 你很好。
Cohen. You got him. You got him.
科恩。 你得到了他。 你得到了他。
Go, go, go on.
走，走，继续。
You're going to let a.
你要让一个。
Little fingering shit get in the way of.
小指法狗屎得到的方式。
This stuff.
这玩意。
What's up?
怎么了？
Come on. Come on. Oh, my God. I'm so close.
来吧。 来吧。 我的天啊。 我是如此接近。
I'm so. Close.
我就是这样。 关闭。
Why do you jump to what?
你为什么跳到什么？
It went down and stuff is underneath.
它掉下来了，下面有东西。
He's inside.
他在里面。
I'm going to go into the other elevator.
我要去另一部电梯。
I'll meet him down there.
我会在那里见到他。
You have to go up. Yeah.
你必须上去。 是的。
Upwards. Upwards.
向上。 向上。
Oh, my fucking God.
哦，我的他妈的上帝。
My fingers are shaking.
我的手指在颤抖。
They're quivering.
他们在颤抖。
Sorry. My
对不起。 我的
my wrist feel like my wrist feels overused.
我的手腕感觉手腕被过度使用了。
That's what the muscles in my forearms are shaking because of that.
这就是我前臂的肌肉因此而颤抖的原因。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I can't lift my hand up in the air.
我无法在空中举起手。
It's just start shaking.
它只是开始摇晃。
All right, where is he?
好吧，他在哪里？
I shoot him.
我射他。
Hard.
难的。
Hot arena.
热火朝天的竞技场。
Area,
区域，
aerialists, aerial.
空中飞人，空中飞人。
What is it?
它是什么？
Not like the finger on your nipples.
不像你乳头上的手指。
Yes, it is down.
是的，它下降了。
And yet you don't know what a a body is.
然而你不知道身体是什么。
Well, Arriola, it's a tag.
好吧，阿里奥拉，这是一个标签。
It's a tag.
它是一个标签。
What's really
什么是真的
the more you know
你懂得越多
where why am I moving so slow?
为什么我走得这么慢？
Where is this fucker?
这个混蛋在哪里？
Show yourself.
展示你自己。
Let's look around. OK, this. Is probably hiding in here.
让我们环顾四周。 好的，这个。 大概是躲在这里吧。
Oh, look.
哦，看。
It's like a reference to that one image.
这就像对那个图像的引用。
Can we push them?
我们可以推他们吗？
What's all?
什么是全部？
What is that?
那是什么？
Ah, alcohol.
啊，酒精。
It's alcohol. Hey.
是酒精。 嘿。
This looks so. Dangerous, by the way.
这看起来是这样。 顺便说一句，很危险。
Like, I can't imagine doing this enough. Yeah.
就像，我无法想象这样做不够。 是的。
Oh, my God, he's. No. Oh, no.
哦，我的上帝，他是。 不，哦，不。
He's here.
他在这里。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Help me bust it open. OK, ok.
帮我打开它。 好的好的。
I'm here.
我在这里。
You ready? Yeah.
你准备好了吗？ 是的。
Yeah, I'm ready.
是的，我准备好了。
Go. Nice, nice.
去。 好好。
Easy gig. Set me out.
轻松的演出。 让我出去。
You got that piece of shit.
你得到了那块狗屎。
I'm going to kill you.
我要杀了你。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Don't you have a gun? Why can't we just shoot him?
你没有枪吗？ 为什么我们不能直接射杀他？
He's not in line.
他不排队。
Of sight, is he? OK,
看得见，是吗？ 好的，
ok. OK.
行。 好的。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. OK.
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。 好的。
I'm extending.
我在扩展。
I'm extending ok.
我扩展好了。
And I grab nice.
我抓得很好。
Then you go up.
那你就上去。
I'll bring you over.
我带你过去。
Wow, this is so majestic.
哇，这太壮观了。
Holy shit. Hurry up.
天啊。 赶快。
Wait, the.
等等，
All right, we're timed. We're timed.
好吧，我们的时间到了。 我们是定时的。
Hold up. Go.
耽误。 去。
OK. OK, ok.
好的。 好的好的。
So, you know, I don't see him anywhere.
所以，你知道，我在任何地方都看不到他。
I don't know where you went.
我不知道你去了哪里。
Keep. Look, he's got to be up there. Somewhere.
保持。 看，他必须在上面。 某处。
He's going to jump me right now by you.
他现在要从你身边跳我。
Oh, my God. Holy shit.
我的天啊。 天啊。
Why is there an axe? What?
为什么会有斧头？ 什么？
I just had to watch yeah.
我只需要看看是的。
Yeah.
是的。
All right, I'll chase.
好吧，我去追。
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
我去，我去，我去。
I'm on his ass.
我在他的屁股上。
I see him. I see him.
我看见他了。 我看见他了。
Stop. Crane,
停止。 起重机，
can I move the crane?
我可以移动起重机吗？
I got to shake him off.
我得把他甩掉。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, my God. This is dangerous.
我的天啊。 这是危险的。
This is really bad, dude.
这真的很糟糕，伙计。
I don't know.
我不知道。
You know, afraid of heights.
你知道，恐高症。
Oh, my God. He's, like, down on this.
我的天啊。 他，就像，在这件事上。
Move all the way. On the thing.
一路移动。 事情上。
What the hell?
我勒个去？
This guy's crazy.
这家伙疯了。
I can't do that.
我不能那样做。
I don't
我不
I want you to slip.
我要你滑倒。
Oh. Oh. We're going to get him.
哦。 哦。 我们要得到他。
I'm going to get. I'm going to get him.
我要得到。 我要去接他。
I'm going to get him. Get him, get him, get you. Get him bitch.
我要去接他。 得到他，得到他，得到你。 给他个婊子
I'm on my way.
我在路上。
I'm almost there.
我快到了。
I'll jump down from top.
我会从上面跳下来。
Oh, my God. Oh, I slapped him.
我的天啊。 哦，我打了他一巴掌。
Oh, my God. Get him something.
我的天啊。 给他拿东西。
Get off.
下车。
Yeah,
是的，
literally. Oh, hang on.
字面上地。 哦，等一下。
I'm almost down. What was that?
我快要倒下了。 那是什么？
Oh, my God. Oh, no.
我的天啊。 不好了。
No way.
没门。
No way, no way.
没办法，没办法。
You got this.
你得到了这个。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
No, I got his like.
不，我得到了他的喜欢。
I got his like. It's OK. It's ok.
我得到了他的喜欢。 没关系。 没关系。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I can't move forward.
我无法前进。
OK, there we go.
好的，我们开始吧。
How does he get this?
他怎么得到这个？
Dude keeps getting away this fucking right.
伙计一直在逃避这该死的权利。
I'm dropping down. I got him.
我正在下降。 我找到他了。
I got him. I got him.
我找到他了。 我找到他了。
I got that.
我明白了。
I'm jumping. I'm jumping.
我在跳。 我在跳。
Dude, he's choking me. He's choking me. He's choking.
伙计，他在呛我。 他让我窒息。 他正在窒息。
I'm going to die.
我要死了。
I'm going to die. I'm going to die.
我要死了。 我要死了。
Oh, no, Mysta.
哦，不，米斯塔。
Fancy talking Dungeons Dragons.
花式说话的地牢龙。
I think I messed up. I got you.
我想我搞砸了。 我接到你了。
Go. What?
去。 什么？
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, my. God.
天啊。 上帝。
Oh, my God. I'm so tired of him.
我的天啊。 我厌倦了他。
I'm so tired of him.
我厌倦了他。
This fucking guy.
这该死的家伙。
This guy is the fastest man alive.
这家伙是活得最快的人。
Our perspectives.
我们的观点。
Yeah. This perspective.
是的。 这种观点。
OK, I'm up here.
好的，我在上面。
Where are you going next?
你接下来要去哪里？
Oh, we got him.
哦，我们得到了他。
Yeah, that's nice.
是的，这很好。
Holly Foxx gets her hands off me.
Holly Foxx 把手从我身上拿开。
Hands all the way too long then.
那就手太长了。
Oh, my God. Dude is. Slippery.
我的天啊。 伙计是。 滑。
It's like GTA I got it.
这就像 GTA 我明白了。
Hasn't even been an hour.
还不到一个小时。
What the fuck are you talking about?
你他妈在说什么？
Recycling glass.
回收玻璃。
So tell me where Harvey. Is.
所以告诉我哈维在哪里。 是。
Fuck you. I ain't telling you shit.
去你的。 我不是跟你说屁话。
Fuck me.
操我。
Oh. Fuck me. Fuck me.
哦。 操我。 操我。
Oh, whoa. Look at this.
哦，哇。 看这个。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, I wonder what you could do with this shoe.
哦，我想知道你能用这双鞋做什么。
Each one of. His kneecaps and a shoe his feet.
每一个。 他的膝盖骨和鞋子他的脚。
For now.
目前。
Making him talk.
让他说话。
You know.
你知道。
I don't know about you,
我不了解你，但我在这里看到很多不同的东西可以让这个人说话。
What do you say?
你说什么？
Feet I've got feet, and then they can shove.
脚 我有脚，然后他们可以推。
Yeah, just.
是的，只是。
Just put his feet to fill in this face.
只是把他的脚来填补这张脸。
Oh, we had to torture him.
哦，我们不得不折磨他。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
Oh, this is fun.
哦，这很有趣。
Way crowbar now.
现在是撬棍。
Oh, nail gun.
哦，钉枪。
Oh, I got a lamp. To get a real shock.
哦，我有一盏灯。 获得真正的震撼。
Oh, I'm going to.
哦，我要去。
I could shock. Him.
我可能会震惊。 他。
You're going to talk a lot I say shit. Yeah.
你会说很多我说狗屎。 是的。
How about this?
这个怎么样？
Oh. Oh, yeah.
哦。 哦耶。
You like that bitch? Oh. OK. That was good.
你喜欢那个婊子？ 哦。 好的。 那很好。
I'm going to shock you.
我要让你震惊。
Oh, I am you can put the light in my eye.
哦，我是你可以把光放在我的眼睛里。
Is that your bright idea?
这是你的好主意吗？
Is that my bright idea? Smart ass.
这是我的好主意吗？ 自作聪明。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔噢
You think he likes it? I think he likes it.
你觉得他喜欢吗？ 我觉得他喜欢。
Wait a second now.
现在等一下。
Oh, yeah, I think he like that.
哦，是的，我觉得他喜欢这样。
I'll try to blow top.
我会尝试吹顶。
Damn it.
该死的。
Oh, that's. Huh?
哦，那是。 嗯？
Your face.
你的脸。
His won't start talking.
他不会开始说话。
Fuck you. Fuck me, huh?
去你的。 操我吧？
How about the dick? Whoa.
鸡巴呢？ 哇。
No, no, not the dick. Oh.
不，不，不是鸡巴。 哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, dude, why are we doing this stock?
哦，伙计，我们为什么要做这只股票？
I don't think this is right.
我认为这是不对的。
Ha ha ha ha.
哈哈哈哈。
What the fuck is.
他妈的是什么。
I'm showing him his wallet. Leave my family out of this.
我给他看他的钱包。 让我的家人远离这一切。
All entirely up to you.
完全取决于你。
Don't you fucking touch them.
你他妈的不要碰他们。
They have nothing to do with this.
他们与此无关。
Oh. Then start talking.
哦。 然后开始说话。
He's still not talking.
他还是不说话。
All right, guys.
好吧，伙计们。
All right, I think the family did it.
好吧，我认为是家人做到了。
I'll tell you what. You what?
我会告诉你什么。 你什么？
I know I wanted to shoot him.
我知道我想射杀他。
Yeah, start talking then.
是的，那就开始说话吧。
All right, all right, calm down. Calm down.
好了好了，冷静下来。 冷静下来。
Somewhere we don't get the shooter.
某处我们没有得到射手。
I don't know where exactly, but he's in Mexico.
我不知道具体在哪里，但他在墨西哥。
I think you do.
我想你会的。
Maybe want to get info in there. Hmm?
也许想在那里获取信息。 唔？
I swear.
我发誓。
So that's where the rat is hiding. Oh, yeah.
这就是老鼠藏身的地方。 哦耶。
That's where he is.
那就是他所在的地方。
Don't tell him I told you. You don't tell me what to do.
不要告诉他我告诉过你。 你不告诉我该怎么做。
All right.
好的。
I'll see you later. Damn right.
以后我会来看你。 太他妈正确了。
Let's go, guys. Yeah.
伙计们出发。 是的。
What's I'm going to shoot him.
我要射他什么。
You're crazy. Untie me.
你疯了。 放开我。
No, come back.
不，回来。
You know.
你知道。
The whole electric shock and him moaning.
整个人触电而他呻吟着。
They're really just.
他们真的很公正。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔噢
Mexico.
墨西哥。
Then we got an electric shock too far.
然后我们触电太远了。
That's probably a good idea.
这可能是个好主意。
I'm telling you, the nipple idea is like this.
我告诉你，乳头的想法是这样的。
Incredible. Wait.
极好的。 等待。
Step aside.
靠边。
Are you speaking from experience? Or.
你说的是经验吗？ 或者。
No, I'm not speaking from experience.
不，我不是根据经验说话。
I'm just.
我只是。
You like, if there's a way to, like, experience it
你喜欢，如果有办法，喜欢，第一次体验它，它可能就是那个。
Hmm. My only concept of it.
唔。 我唯一的概念。
All right, there you go.
好吧，给你。
Come on, record it.
来，记录一下。
Yeah.
是的。
Like the nipple.
和乳头一样。
Contact that might like.
可能喜欢的联系方式。
If I electrocute your nipples.
如果我触电你的乳头。
Can we record. It?
可以录音吗。 它？
That's good.
那很好。
I got a record. Why get those gone, then?
我有记录。 那为什么要让那些人消失呢？
The nipple gang shocks you.
乳头帮让你震惊。
Yeah.
是的。
I mean, you can't risk robbing it like. No.
我的意思是，你不能冒险去抢劫它。 不。
There are ways other places to rob the banks.
还有其他地方可以抢劫银行。
You know. I just want to see you go. Like what?
你知道。 我只是想看你走。 像什么？
Oh, yeah, I guess maybe.
哦，是的，我想也许吧。
You know, I'm sure you don't.
你知道，我相信你不知道。
Like the whole class.
和全班一样。
As long as.
只要。
As long as you do the same.
只要你做同样的事情。
OK, right? Yeah, I'll use it. This Clemson.
好的，对吧？ 是的，我会用它。 这个克莱姆森。
Pinky promise. Promise, promise. School.
小指的承诺。 答应，答应。 学校。
I pinky promise.
我小指保证。
Good boy.
好孩子。
Roy and Rogers.
罗伊和罗杰斯。
Rogers Hogg, his.
罗杰斯·霍格，他的。
Voice is stronger.
声音更强。
You think they'll have enough money?
你认为他们会有足够的钱吗？
They better have.
他们最好有。
I'm not going after Harvey with just a handgun.
我不会只用手枪追捕哈维。
Well, yes.
嗯，是。
There's only one way to find.
只有一种方法可以找到。
OK, then.
好吧。
You ready? Yeah.
你准备好了吗？ 是的。
Why don't you give me the gun?
你为什么不把枪给我？
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
Look, we need to keep a low profile.
看，我们需要保持低调。
That's not really your thing.
那真的不是你的事。
I say we do this the best way, man. Just in and. Out.
我说我们这样做是最好的方式，伙计。 就在和。 出去。
Why is Leo always, like, default to the most chaotic option possible?
为什么 Leo 总是默认选择最混乱的选项？
Well, I don't like easy.
好吧，我不喜欢轻松。
Look at that.
看那个。
Oh, it's like you should. Keep the gun.
哦，这就像你应该的。 把枪留着。
Vincent.
文森特。
You don't like it? Fine. You can keep the gun. I'm OK with that.
你不喜欢它？ 美好的。 你可以留着枪。 我同意。
Just make sure nobody gets hurt.
只要确保没有人受伤。
Kiki.
琪琪。
Don't you think I'd do anything part of it?
你不觉得我会做其中的一部分吗？
I mean, I think. Trust me.
我的意思是，我认为。 相信我。
I think your fingers are still a little shaky, so I don't know.
我觉得你的手指还有点颤抖，所以我不知道。
It's all yours.
这都是你的。
Yeah, but.
好但是。
But. Hey,
但。 嘿，
hey, listen, listen.
嘿，听，听。
I'm good. I'm good with my fingers.
我很好。 我的手指很好。
That's a lie.
那是谎言。
I mean, obviously.
我的意思是，很明显。
Are you kidding me?
你在跟我开玩笑吗？
What did I tell you?
我跟你说了什么？
What did I tell you, little man?
我跟你说什么了，小家伙？
A guy's got to do what a guy's got to do to the register.
一个人必须做一个人必须对登记册做的事情。
So fucking open. It.
太他妈的开放了。 它。
Oh, my God. I can take you anywhere.
我的天啊。 我可以带你去任何地方。
Any cash in the register open. Hey.
收银机中的任何现金都已打开。 嘿。
I'm going to cash.
我要去兑现。
One more. Word from you. Sit down. Shit.
多一个。 你的话。 坐下。 拉屎。
Now stay there.
现在呆在那里。
What? Shut up. All right. All right.
什么？ 住口。 好的。 好的。
OK. Hey, Benson.
好的。 嘿，本森。
There should be safe around here somewhere.
这附近的某个地方应该是安全的。
I'm only. I'm just making safe.
我只是。 我只是在保证安全。
I'm making sure that people can't get away and making sure people don't get away.
我确保人们无法逃脱并确保人们不会逃脱。
Stop it. Mysta. Mysta.
停下来。 米斯塔。 米斯塔。
Mysta. I'm just.
米斯塔。 我只是。
Scaring them. OK. OK, i'm going back.
吓唬他们。 好的。 好的，我要回去了。
I'm going back.
我要回去了。
Oh, let me go.
哦，放开我。
Benson, let him go.
班森，放开他。
The safe. Is that your fucking piece of shit?
保险箱。 那是你他妈的狗屎吗？
What the fuck was that?
那是什么鬼？
What? Let's go. Wait.
什么？ 我们走吧。 等待。
The lady. The lady.
这位女士。 这位女士。
The lady, Mysta..
这位女士，米斯塔..
The lady Mysta. Lady,
米斯塔女士。 女士，不要开枪。
Give me the gun. Don't move.
把枪给我。 不许动。
Oh. Oh, shit.
哦。 妈的。
All right, I'll go and stay here.
好吧，我会去留在这里。
All right.
好的。
It's locked. We need the combination.
它被锁定。 我们需要这种组合。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。
You know, a lady got out, by the way, she came out of the store.
你知道，一位女士出来了，顺便说一下，她从商店里出来了。
Really? Yeah. She got out.
真的吗？ 是的。 她出去了。
I don't know if that's important or not.
我不知道这是否重要。
No, I'm fine. Nobody move.
不，我很好。 没人动。
Damn it.
该死的。
Why do we find that? Why would we find that?
为什么我们会发现？ 为什么我们会找到那个？
Fuck.
他妈的。
Maybe there's something here in the room.
也许房间里有什么东西。
Is this guy dead?
这家伙死了吗？
Oh, I think so. But it's fine.
哦，我想是的。 但没关系。
He didn't have a family.
他没有家庭。
We need to have a code.
我们需要一个代码。
Yeah, we have to find the code somewhere. What's the code?
是的，我们必须在某个地方找到代码。 代码是什么？
Where's the code?
代码在哪里？
Maybe it's written down.
也许它被写下来了。
Lady, what's the code?
小姐姐，密码是多少？
We need the combination.
我们需要这种组合。
I don't have it. Oh.
我没有它。 哦。
What's going on?
到底是怎么回事？
Calm down. Calm down.
冷静下来。 冷静下来。
I'm going to.
我要去。
Just give me the combination.
只要给我组合。
Oh, no. They know.
不好了。 他们知道。
They know yet.
他们还知道。
Are they OK? Yes. Yes, OK. OK.
他们还好吗？ 是的。 好的。 好的。
13713713721 is all we know.
13713713721 是我们所知道的。
Oh, my God. He's coming.
我的天啊。 他来了。
He's coming. He's coming. He's coming.
他来了。 他来了。 他来了。
Seven open grab bag.
七开抓包。
Grab gun was like $5.
抢枪就像5美元。
We do that for five bucks.
我们只花五块钱。
Are you kidding me? Get out of here.
你在跟我开玩笑吗？ 离开这里。
Whose idea was this?
这是谁的主意？
Nobody move.
没人动。
It was your idea.
这是你的主意。
You walked in with your toe on your knees.
你走进来，脚趾放在膝盖上。
Oh, my God. We fucked off.
我的天啊。 我们搞砸了。
Rebecca.
丽贝卡。
Oh, well, do we actually lose?
哦，好吧，我们真的输了吗？
Yeah, we lost.
是的，我们输了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
That wasn't even part of it. OK, did.
那甚至不是其中的一部分。 好的，做到了。
You watch the class? You might make a move.
你看课吗？ 你可能会有所行动。
Sure. Watch the clerks.
当然。 观察文员。
Yeah, I'm watching her.
是的，我在看着她。
I'm going to watch her. Hey.
我要看着她。 嘿。
Don't move.
不许动。
You get the gun, ok?
你拿枪，好吗？
It's 137.
是 137。
It's one through seven.
从一到七。
Marquesa, right?
马克萨，对吧？
OK, this guy, we just got to be fast.
好吧，这家伙，我们得快点。
This lock, we need a combination. I got it. I got it.
这把锁，我们需要一个密码。 我得到了它。 我得到了它。
I got. Three.
我有。 三。
I don't.
我不。
Seven. Got it open.
七。 打开了
OK, I grabbing.
好的，我抢了。
Got it.
知道了。
Let's go get him. I get him. I get away.
我们去找他吧。 我得到他。 我走开。
Why do we do.
我们为什么这样做。
That for just like, such a small amount of cash.
这就像，这么少的现金。
But broke, man, we're broke.
但是破产了，伙计，我们破产了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
This is so drama.
这太戏剧化了。
Get in the car. Get in the car.
上车。 上车。
I could do it.
我能行。
You're driving now.
你现在在开车。
OK? I'm an excellent driver.
好的？ 我是一个优秀的司机。
OK? Oh, that was easy.
好的？ 哦，那很容易。
So fucking dumb.
太他妈傻了
All that's. The are.
仅此而已。 是。
Make sure to bring the goods, ok?
一定要带货，好吗？
Yeah, I know where that is.
是的，我知道那在哪里。
Got it.
知道了。
He just walked into the stores are shooting everywhere.
他刚走进店里到处都是枪声。
Yeah. As to make a statement.
是的。 至于发表声明。
We got the guns.
我们拿到了枪。
So they don't do anything stupid.
所以他们不会做任何愚蠢的事情。
I do.
我愿意。
Stop worrying, Vincent. It's not good for your heart.
别担心，文森特。 这对你的心脏不好。
Yeah. Stop worrying, bitch.
是的。 别担心了，婊子。
I just want to know what we're dealing with.
我只是想知道我们在处理什么。
Relax, Mysta. Paranoia.
放松，米斯塔。 妄想症。
I trust her, OK?
我相信她，好吗？
Besides, she owes me one OK.
再说了，她还欠我一个好。
Let's talk about. Your gun. Celia.
让我们来谈谈。 你的枪。 西莉亚。
Yeah. Relax, Mom. All right?
是的。 放松，妈妈。 好的？
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You relax. Yeah.
耶耶耶。 你放松。 是的。
You're either alive.
你要么还活着。
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
是的，是的，随便。
Thomas Oh. StarWars.
托马斯哦。 星球大战。
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
I've never watched starwars. Same what?
我从来没有看过星球大战。 一样什么？
You think
您认为
that.
那。
Oh, that's a cool car.
哦，那是一辆很酷的车。
Hot lady.
辣妹。
OK, hello.
好的，你好。
See, she got floral pattern.
看，她有花卉图案。
Still, she knows where.
不过，她知道在哪里。
She owns. It, and she she works on it.
她拥有。 它，她正在努力。
You don't.
你没有。
I'm going to shoot your. But she. Left.
我要拍你的。 但是她。 左。
But she's my beloved jacket. No.
但她是我心爱的夹克。 不。
What is that?
那是什么？
You have no drip.
你没有滴水。
Don't want you. OK, that's.
不想你。 好的，就是这样。
You're your hands.
你是你的手。
Look, I'm Vincent.
看，我是文森特。
Oh, hello.
哦你好。
OK, that's too far to meet you. What the fuck, man?
好吧，那太远了，不能见你。 什么鬼，伙计？
Oh, you're a fucking idiot.
哦，你他妈是个白痴。
What?
什么？
Why don't you bring your whole family next time I'm out?
下次我出去的时候，你为什么不带上你的全家？
What's wrong?
怎么了？
What's wrong with me?
我是怎么了？
What the fuck is wrong with you? Yeah.
你他妈怎么了？ 是的。
You tell him what the fuck is wrong, you hear?
你告诉他他妈的出了什么问题，你听到了吗？
I want ice cream.
我想要冰激淋。
I told you, I don't do business with strangers.
我告诉过你，我不和陌生人做生意。
And this guy, he looks like a stranger to me.
而这家伙，对我来说，就像个陌生人。
You don't know me.
你不认识我。
Do you have a problem with me? Yeah.
你有我的问题吗？ 是的。
Yeah.
是的。
I got no wrong with me.
我没有错。
You have big earrings, Vince.
你有大耳环，文斯。
I can handle it. I can handle it. Don't worry.
我能应付。 我能应付。 不用担心。
I got this I want to see.
我得到了这个我想看的。
I'm just going to look at these birds over here.
我只是要看看这些鸟在这里。
Wow. Look at these birds flying around.
哇。 看看这些飞来飞去的鸟。
Star, look at him. Huh?
星星，看着他。 嗯？
Oh, is that OK?
哦，这样可以吗？
There's a lot of sexual tension here.
这里有很多性紧张。
I don't know. Oh,
我不知道。 哦，
I like the clouds.
我喜欢云。
Why is nothing.
为什么什么都没有。
Oh, my g something. Yes. You have to do something.
哦，我的东西。 是的。 你必须做点什么。
You OK.
你还好吗。
Here you go.
干得好。
OK, this is this is acting it.
OK，这就是这在演戏吧。
Disarms the gun, so you can't. She can't use it.
解除枪械，所以你不能。 她不能使用它。
Let's just go, then we'll be out of here.
我们走吧，然后我们就离开这里。
Yeah, time. OK.
是的，时间。 好的。
OK, Jasmine.
好的，茉莉花。
It's five bucks.
这是五块钱。
Are those.
是那些。
Those are benjamins.
那些是本杰明。
Where are you talking about? Five bucks?
你在说什么？ 五块钱？
Well, what's up? Benjamin?
嗯，怎么了？ 本杰明?
Those are hundred dollar bills each dime.
那些是一百美元的钞票，一角钱。
That's actually a lot of guns.
这实际上是很多枪。
OK, I want them.
好的，我想要它们。
I want one till.
我想要一个直到。
You get the.
你得到了。
Gun. Fuck off.
枪。 滚蛋。
Ellen. The assault rifle.
艾伦。 突击步枪。
OK? I don't want that. Anyways,
好的？ 我不要那个。 无论如何，让我看看。
Which one do I want?
我想要哪一个？
What is that?
那是什么？
Back there is a hunting rifle.
后面有一把猎枪。
Is a shotgun.
是霰弹枪。
Shotguns are always great after hunting N14.
猎杀 N14 后，霰弹枪总是很棒。
All right.
好的。
Packs quite a proboscis.
包装相当长鼻。
And a good place for target.
和目标的好地方。
Practise around here.
在这里练习。
Try shooting at those empty houses.
试着在那些空荡荡的房子里射击。
That should do the trick. Good idea.
这应该够了吧。 好主意。
Oh, are you? Shoot this bad boy.
哦，你是？ 射杀这个坏孩子。
Fuck,
他妈的，
fuck, fuck.
操，操。
Oh, no. OK, ok. I got it.
不好了。 好的好的。 我得到了它。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Oh, you crazy friends.
哦，你们这些疯狂的朋友。
This is the valley drinking from the wash.
这是从洗漱中饮用的山谷。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Impressive. Vincent, you're cheating.
感人的。 文森特，你在作弊。
What do you mean, I'm cheating?
什么意思，我在作弊？
You're hacking.
你在窃听。
You're locking on.
你正在锁定。
No, I'm not.
不我不是。
It's called good aim, motherfucker.
这被称为好目标，混蛋。
What is this? OK, get. It next time.
这是什么？ 好的，得到。 下次再来。
You ever heard of lobs?
你听说过 lob 吗？
No, no, no.
不不不。
No. Okay, well, thank you.
不，好的，谢谢。
That's bullshit.
那是胡说八道。
Did the sample schedule just match?
样品时间表是否匹配？
Who? You're just talking
谁？ 你只是在说
to. Just do our role.
到。 只做我们的角色。
We answer those. Call
我们回答这些。 称呼
this is a. Bus assault rifle.
这是一个。 巴士突击步枪。
I hate this shit.
我讨厌这个狗屎。
Yeah, I like this gun. I'm happy with it.
是的，我喜欢这把枪。 我很高兴。
I want.
我想。
I want a submachine gun.
我想要一把冲锋枪。
This is the perfect place for Target.
这是Target的理想之地。
This one.
这个。
This feels like.
这种感觉。
Yeah, it's looking.
是的，它正在寻找。
I was the lead
我是主角
oh, yeah?
哦耶？
Yeah. That's them all. My style.
是的。 这就是他们的全部。 我的风格。
Yeah. OK.
是的。 好的。
Some of them.
他们中有一些。
My mama
我的妈妈
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
blah, blah, blah. Blah, blah.
等等等等等等。 呸呸呸。
Oh, when was this?
哦，这是什么时候？
Give me a minute.
给我一点时间。
I want to make sure I have the right weapon.
我想确保我拥有正确的武器。
By this all.
靠这一切。
It's more target practise. OK.
这是更多的目标练习。 好的。
Cool.
凉爽的。
You. You mind?
你。 你介意？
Are you missing all of them?
你想念他们所有人吗？
I missed all of them.
我错过了他们所有人。
OK. I'm done.
好的。 我做完。
Yeah, let's go.
是的，我们走吧。
I think I'm. Gone.
我想我是。 走了。
I will figure it out.
我会弄清楚。
What? We wanted the fuck out.
什么？ 我们想他妈的出去。
I had those. I had those. OK, I that. You hit those.
我有那些。 我有那些。 好的，我那个。 你打那些。
Do you really hit those?
你真的打那些吗？
Yes, I hit those.
是的，我击中了那些。
OK, sir.
好的，先生。
I time to shoot people.
我是时候射人了。
I think
我认为
I buy
我买
my wife.
我的妻子。
She really does work it. Yeah.
她确实在工作。 是的。
She doesn't even say bye either.
她也没有说再见。
I like what she's.
我喜欢她的样子。
Girl bossing. Me.
女霸道。 我。
I think so.
我认同。
Why she looking at us like that?
为什么她这样看我们？
Like we're going to see her again.
就像我们要再见到她一样。
I'm taking off my hat.
我要脱帽子了。
Also, I want to ask when did you want to stop for today?
另外，我想问一下你今天想停在什么时候？
Because like, we haven't. Gone far off the reservation.
因为喜欢，我们没有。 远离预订。
OK? Yeah. One more mission. We shoot.
好的？ 是的。 又一个任务。 我们拍摄。
I'm naked now.
我现在赤身裸体。
Are you?
你是？
Yeah.
是的。
You're naked.
你赤身裸体。
Your heart is gone.
你的心没了。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
She goes. Yes, youSussy.
她去。 是的，你苏西。
You know, don't you dare, motherfucker.
你知道，你不敢，混蛋。
Don't you dare.
你敢。
Hey, it's me.
嘿，是我。
I got some information about lead. Oh, OK.
我得到了一些关于铅的信息。 哦好的。
You know where he is?
你知道他在哪里吗？
I just met him.
我刚认识他。
Give me his location, you son of a bitch.
给我他的位置，你这个狗娘养的。
Just tell me where he is.
告诉我他在哪里。
You got it.
你说对了。
Good job.
做得好。
Talk to you later.
我们回聊。
Wow. Wildfire, we got sold out.
哇。 野火，我们卖光了。
What the fuck
什么鬼
Harvey?
哈维？
What's up?
怎么了？
I found it.
我找到了。
Good.
好的。
Make sure we put up best guy on this.
确保我们在这方面设置了最好的人。
I want him dead. You got it.
我要他死。 你说对了。
What the fuck, man?
什么鬼，伙计？
I thought she was cool.
我觉得她很酷。
Yeah, same rich man.
是的，同样的有钱人。
Fuck rich.
他妈的有钱。
People.
人们。
It's I came out so in genuinely.
是我真的出来了。
I don't know, it was just like.
我不知道，它就像。
Yeah, fuck rich people. Yeah.
是的，去他妈的有钱人。 是的。
Well, now my wife is pissed. Oh.
好吧，现在我的妻子很生气。 哦。
Oh, fuck, no.
哦，他妈的，不。
Oh, my God. She's hatching.
我的天啊。 她正在孵化。
Hatching?
孵化？
Oh, no.
不好了。
This is happening right now.
这正在发生。
Oh. Oh, no.
哦。 不好了。
Oh, no.
不好了。
My name is Caramel Moretti.
我的名字是焦糖莫雷蒂。
I'm pregnant, and I think I'm going into labour.
我怀孕了，我想我要临产了。
Oh, no,
不好了，
please send an ambulance.
请派救护车。
OK, does she even say hatching?
好吧，她甚至说孵化吗？
I think yeah.
我想是的。
You said she's hatching
你说她在孵化
oh, that's.
哦，那是。
Look, man, focus on the game, OK?
看，伙计，专注于比赛，好吗？
Focus on driving. It. Can you stop it?
专注于驾驶。 它。 你能阻止它吗？
You're the one that's driving it.
你是驱动它的人。
You're the one that's driving, mother fucker.
你是那个在开车的人，妈的。
Excuse me. I sure hope so.
打扰一下。 我当然希望如此。
I mean, I'm focussing on driving.
我的意思是，我专注于驾驶。
You focus on sitting there.
你专注于坐在那里。
Oh, we're going to see a movie together.
哦，我们要一起看电影。
Oh, you're going to have a little date night.
哦，你会有一个小小的约会之夜。
We're going to see a miniature beer.
我们将看到一种微型啤酒。
And Douglas Johnson,
还有道格拉斯约翰逊，
it's just a name that's the.
那只是一个名字而已。
Names of the actors.
演员的名字。
They're going to see East River.
他们要去东河看看。
Yep. Oh, fuck.
是的。 哦，操。
OK, let's go.
好的，我们走吧。
Oh, sure. To get us that play, like.
行，可以。 为了让我们玩，就像。
We solve our guns too. No, no guns.
我们也解决了我们的枪支问题。 不，没有枪。
I think they're shoved in our ass right now.
我认为他们现在被推到我们的屁股上了。
Can we just go around the city? Oh, man.
我们可以绕着城市转一圈吗？ 天啊。
Hold on. Wait. I think we can.
坚持，稍等。 等待。 我认为我们可以。
Got to make that phone call first.
得先打那个电话。
Oh, man.
天啊。
Phone call.
电话。
That's the name of.
那是的名字。
The movie theatre. The phone booth last year.
电影院。 去年的电话亭。
Oh, yeah, right.
哦，是的，对。
And you got to make a phone call.
你必须打个电话。
I'll snoop for the call.
我会偷听电话。
I don't have any change. What?
我没有任何变化。 什么？
How we get money.
我们如何赚钱。
On the other side of the square.
在广场的另一边。
Maybe I could get some change there. Here.
也许我可以在那里得到一些改变。 这里。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I can't believe do.
我不敢相信做。
Well, how about we ask these people?
那么，我们问这些人怎么样？
Hey, you have any money?
嘿，你有钱吗？
I'm just gonna sit down what about that guy?
我只是要坐下 那家伙呢？
I don't want to be with you anymore. Oh, fuck. Me.
我不想再和你在一起了。 哦，操。 我。
Tell her she's making a big mistake breaking.
告诉她她犯了一个大错误。
I didn't want to get involved in this. I just want a free change.
我不想卷入这件事。 我只想要免费的零钱。
Oh, could I get some money?
哦，我能弄点钱吗？
Jesus, spin off. She make him.
耶稣，滚开。 她让他。
This is not my business.
这不关我的事。
If you make him, you know, I'll.
如果你让他，你知道，我会的。
Five bucks making a big mistake.
五块钱犯了一个大错误。
Yes, of course.
是的当然。
She is.
她是。
No, you slept with her best friend. Oh.
不，你和她最好的朋友睡了。 哦。
What are you doing over that?
你在做什么？
Yes, but it was a long time ago.
是的，但那是很久以前的事了。
It was terrible.
太可怕了。
I mean, she was frigid sorry.
我的意思是，她冷冰冰的对不起。
You're on your own. Oh, thanks a lot.
你只能靠自己。 哦，非常感谢。
They're having a couples dispute or something.
他们有夫妻争执什么的。
I saw you flirting with her.
我看到你在和她调情。
Oh, God.
天啊。
I'll sort this out, OK?
我会解决这个问题的，好吗？
Yeah, you got this fucking right. We're talking.
是的，你说得对。 我们正在交谈。
He was arrested.
他被捕了。
My I do mind.
我确实介意。
Just like a girlfriend here did when you were flirting with another girl.
就像这里的女朋友在你和另一个女孩调情时所做的那样。
At least someone understands me.
至少有人理解我。
Damn, damn.
该死，该死。
Sorry. I'm a that's how you handle it.
对不起。 我就是你的处理方式。
Fine. All right. I'm sorry.
美好的。 好的。 对不起。
Say it like you mean it.
像你的意思一样说出来。
I'm really, really sorry.
我真的，真的很抱歉。
I don't believe you. Damn
我不相信你。 该死的，你听起来并不很抱歉，伙计。
Whoa.
哇。
What the fuck, dude? I'm a magician. Man.
什么鬼，伙计？ 我是魔术师。 男人。
That's what you mean. Slender man.
这就是你的意思。 修长的人。
Hey, do you have any change? Hello?
嘿，你有零钱吗？ 你好？
Can I help you with something?
我能帮你什么吗？
Oh, he looks like something.
哦，他看起来像什么东西。
I need to buy some porn. Make a phone call.
我需要买一些色情片。 打个电话。
Sorry.
对不起。
But you have to buy something first. SC.
但是你必须先买点东西。  SC。
Any recommendations?
有什么建议吗？
All right, what do you recommend?
好吧，你有什么推荐的？
We're literally on the pay phone right here.
我们就在这儿的公用电话上。
Oh, magazines.
哦，杂志。
I'll pass.
我会通过的。
Literally right here.
字面上就在这里。
Give me some.
给我一些。
So I'm sure.
所以我很确定。
This guy kind of OK.
这人还行
You're welcome, Jim. All right.
不客气，吉姆。 好的。
How does he not see that?
他怎么看不出来？
Literally right there. Damn it.
从字面上看就在那里。 该死的。
This is these guys my see?
这是我看到的这些家伙？
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
Can we just like.
我们可以喜欢吗。
I. Think we finally we just bought off those newspapers
I. 想想我们终于买下了那些报纸
someone up there till you see them up there.
有人在那里，直到你在那里看到他们。
Oh, yeah. He's watching, right?
哦耶。 他在看，对吧？
You make the phone call.
你打个电话。
Oh, look at this guy.
哦，看看这个人。
Hey, man, what you look at up?
嘿，伙计，你在看什么？
Spell me.
拼写我。
Go on. Pussy.
继续。 猫。
I'm coming up
我来了
what if I can ruin this catfish moment.
如果我能毁掉这个鲶鱼时刻呢？
Can you?
你可以吗？
Oh, no, I don't think so. Hey.
哦，不，我不这么认为。 嘿。
Yeah, I don't appear it's.
是的，我没有出现它。
Not like in. Free rendered cut scene.
不像在。免费渲染的过场动画。
Look, I need to fly somewhere.
听着，我需要飞到某个地方。
This bullshit. Tomorrow.
这胡说八道。 明天。
For your end of the cut scene that. Work.
为你结束过场动画。 工作。
OK, great.
好的，不错。
We're going to Mexico, right?
我们要去墨西哥，对吧？
Is that what they said?
他们是这么说的吗？
No idea.
不知道。
What what
什么什么，什么时候，
what's when, where.
什么时候，什么地方。
Where? She.
在哪里？ 她。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Really? OK,
真的吗？ 好吧，你走了。
I think so.
我认同。
When I go, I got to be swarmed.
当我去的时候，我必须被蜂拥而至。
Yeah,
是的，
I think they're talking about life and labour play.
我认为他们在谈论生活和劳动游戏。
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, I did.
是啊，我做了。
But I need to go all right.
但我必须没事。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
You OK?
你还好吗？
I'm fine, but I need to be somewhere else right now.
我很好，但我现在需要去别的地方。
Hey, you can't just walk away.
嘿，你不能就这么走开。
I'm not walking away, but something happened and I need to be there.
我没有走开，但发生了一些事情，我需要在那里。
All right.
好的。
Vincent,
文森特，
we come too far to back down.
我们走得太远了，不能退缩。
No, you need to talk to me.
不，你需要和我谈谈。
Tell me what's going on in your head.
告诉我你脑子里在想什么。
Uh, wife.
嗯，老婆。
Preggers. Preggers. Pregnant.
怀孕者。 怀孕者。 孕。
Greg.
格雷格。
Greg. Norman?
格雷格。 诺曼？
What was that?
那是什么？
Oh. Oh, no.
哦。 不好了。
Oh, shit. Who is this dude?
妈的。 这哥们是谁？
It's his best friend, but he said he's going to hire his best to kill us.
这是他最好的朋友，但他说他会雇佣他最好的人来杀了我们。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, no. Oh, my God. It's a hit, man.
不好了。 我的天啊。 这是一个打击，伙计。
He has a silencer. And everything.
他有一个消音器。 和所有。
OK, fine.
好的。
It's my wife.
是我的妻子。
She's hot. Oh.
她很漂亮。 哦。
That's your best.
那是你最好的。
That's your best list.
那是你最好的清单。
Oh, my God. This is. Dude, this game's easy.
我的天啊。 这是。 兄弟，这游戏很简单。
I think we were standing still.
我想我们是站着不动的。
He missed his shot.
他投失了。
Come on.
来吧。
Yeah, and he's shooting nothing.
是的，他什么也没拍。
OK, I'm running around.
好吧，我跑来跑去。
He's still looking at us. Oh, shit.
他还在看着我们。 妈的。
What is this perspective? Quick.
这个观点是什么？ 快的。
I'm on the top right now.
我现在在上面。
It says a lot, doesn't it?
它说了很多，不是吗？
Just help me put our point.
只是帮助我提出我们的观点。
Point, play Cover the door. Cover the door.
点，打 盖门。 盖上门。
I'm holding it.
我拿着它。
OK. OK.
好的。 好的。
This should buy some diamonds like this one.
这应该买一些像这样的钻石。
I actually got lost.
我真的迷路了。
I was up there.
我在上面。
Yeah. Oh, shit.
是的。 妈的。
They didn't close like lockers and shit. OK.
他们没有像储物柜和狗屎一样关闭。 好的。
Push.
推。
You get up there and I'll push across.
你上去，我推过去。
Oh, yeah. We'll get out.
哦耶。 我们会出去的。
Get up. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
起床。 走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走。
I'll pull. A boom.
我会拉。 一声巨响。
Move you over. Move you over. Ow, ow, ow.
把你挪过去。 把你挪过去。 呜呜呜
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
走，走，走，走，走，走，走，走。
Jump, jump, jump, jump.
跳，跳，跳，跳。
Ahead.
先。
OK, I'll give you a quick, quick, quick, quick.
好的，我给你一个快，快，快，快。
Get up, get up, get out. I'm on my way. I'm on my way, baby.
起来，起来，出去。 我在路上。 我在路上，宝贝。
I'm on my way.
我在路上。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Not panicking.
不惊慌。
We're fine. These are going to get through.
我们都很好。 这些都会过去的。
He is going to get first.
他将获得第一名。
No, look at him. He's taking forever.
不，看着他。 他是永远的。
Oh, my God. He got through
我的天啊。 他通过了
up. Oh, my God, he got through.
向上。 哦，我的上帝，他通过了。
Holy shit.
天啊。
My God, we've entered.
天哪，我们进去了。
We've entered softly, softly, softly, softly, softly.
我们轻柔地、轻柔地、轻柔地、轻柔地、轻柔地进入。
He's still here.
他还在这里。
My God. Shit.
我的上帝。 拉屎。
What happened to our guns?
我们的枪怎么了？
It's fine.
没事。
Silence gives it last penetration.
沉默给了它最后的穿透力。
OK, hold on.
好的，稍等。
Hey, hold it, hold it. Nice.
嘿，等一下，等一下。 好的。
Nice. Oh, I.
好的。 哦，我。
Got move with me.
跟我一起动
Huh? Suck, suck, suck, suck, suck.
嗯？ 吸，吸，吸，吸，吸，吸。
Dude.
老兄。
How many bullets is this going to have?
这会有多少子弹？
He's really so bad.
他真的太坏了。
He's wasting so many.
他浪费了这么多。
Out of control.
失控。
The next one me here.
下一个我在这里。
Get behind you.
跟在你后面。
Me? Oh, you got mine.
我？ 哦，你得到了我的。
Oh, Isaiah behind.
哦，以赛亚在后面。
Oh, I'm on the bottom now. OK, ok.
哦，我现在在底部。 好的好的。
This is so weird. OK,
这太奇怪了。 好的，
stop it.
停下来。
Move along. Move it.
向前走。 移动它。
Yes, I am. I am, i am.
我是。 我是，我是。
I'm moving. I'm moving right now. Your head's covering it.
我正在移动。 我现在正在搬家。 你的头盖住了它。
Might have.
可能有。
Yeah, your head's covering it. Oh, shit.
是的，你的头盖住了它。 妈的。
You're on the top.
你在上面。
Oh, I am on the top.
哦，我在上面。
Oh, I'm on the top of my body soaking about.
哦，我在我的身体上浸泡。
I thought I was on the bottom. I wasn't at the bottom.
我以为我在底部。 我不在最底层。
Jumped out of them.
从他们身上跳了出来。
Help me. What are you doing down there?
帮我。 你在下面做什么？
Help! Help!
帮助！ 帮助！
Oh, oh, crap.
哦，哦，废话。
How the hell does the worst help ever. Huh?
最糟糕的帮助到底如何。 嗯？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Yeah.
是的。
So you just grabbed his gun?
所以你只是抓住了他的枪？
Oh, you're so. Oh,
哦，你就是这样。 哦，
yeah, yeah, I'm tough.
是的，是的，我很坚强。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
My fingers push. Shit.
我的手指在推。 拉屎。
Yes. Send your best bitch.
是的。 发送你最好的婊子。
Send your best.
发送你最好的。
That was way too easy.
那太容易了。
I like his other jacket.
我喜欢他的另一件夹克。
I want to take the jacket.
我想拿外套。
You got to listen.
你要听。
Yeah.
是的。
Trips close.
行程关闭。
Take it. Take as close.
拿着。 尽量靠近。
Look, I'll take his underwear.
看，我去拿他的内衣。
I don't know what's going on with you, but we need to finish what we started
我不知道你怎么了，但我们需要完成我们开始的事情
Harvey's going to keep sending guys like this.
哈维会继续派出这样的人。
Yeah, true.
是啊，没错。
I know, but. Wifey, you.
我知道但是。 老婆，你
Yeah. If you went to your wife, though, he'd send someone to.
是的。 但是，如果你去找你的妻子，他会派人去。
Oh, my wife is pomegranate.
哦，我的妻子是石榴。
It's my wife.
是我的妻子。
She's in the what?
她在什么？
What's the problem?
问题是什么？
Pomegranate?
石榴？
Yeah. Oh, my God. Is great. News. What does that. Mean?
是的。 我的天啊。 是很棒的。 消息。 那是做什么的。 意思是？
That's, man, you know?
那就是，伙计，你知道吗？
I mean, she's.
我的意思是，她是。
She's great.
她很棒。
Pregnant.
孕。
When when does.
什么时候什么时候。
The pomegranate become a thing?
石榴变成东西了？
To fragment
分片
her Papa, papa, papa, papa.
她的爸爸，爸爸，爸爸，爸爸。
It's just a. Bigger cheese pomegranate.
它只是一个。 更大的奶酪石榴。
Really cool.
真的很酷。
Look,
看，不管复杂与否，你得去看一个孩子。
Whatever's going on between you two.
不管你们两个之间发生了什么。
Oh, man.
天啊。
Your kid. Oh, he gets it.
你的孩子。 哦，他明白了。
You're right.
你说的对。
Of course I am.
我当然是。
You know I am.
你知道我是。
Yeah, I am.
对我是。
You got to that playing, didn't you?
你去玩了，不是吗？
I did. Here's what we're going to do.
我做到了。 这就是我们要做的。
We're going to go to the hospital, see your kid, then we go get that plane.
我们要去医院，看你的孩子，然后我们去拿那架飞机。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
It was me. Mm hmm. Yeah.
那是我。 嗯嗯。 是的。
Oh, with you,
哦，和你一起，
Vincent. I need to trust you on this one.
文森特。 我需要在这件事上相信你。
You can trust me.
你可以相信我。
All right.
好的。
How do we jerk each other off in the cell?
我们如何在牢房里互相抽搐？
I don't think he gets more trusting than not.
我不认为他比没有得到更多的信任。
Yeah, you literally ate my ass
是的，你真的吃了我的屁股
I only trust.
我只相信。
I only let people who I trust eat my ass.
我只让我信任的人吃我的屁股。
Oh, you know,
哦，你知道，
I could tell it was your first kid.
我可以说这是你的第一个孩子。
You could?
你可以？
Yeah. What the fuck?
是的。 什么鬼？
You having flashbacks again?
你又闪回了？
The way you were holding your baby and shit.
你抱着孩子的方式和狗屎。
I mean, sorry about the shit part, I.
我的意思是，我对狗屎部分感到抱歉。
I don't mean in a bad way, you know, but.
我不是说不好，你知道，但是。
Yeah, anyway, it's a great.
是的，无论如何，它是一个伟大的。
OK, you a kid. Cool. OK.
好吧，你是个孩子。 凉爽的。 好的。
Yeah, that was awkward. I was.
是的，那很尴尬。 我曾是。
Very hell.
非常地狱。
You know what?
你知道吗？
That was a weird life.
那是一种奇怪的生活。
Look,
看，
Carol is the love of my life.
卡罗尔是我一生的挚爱。
Oh, man.
天啊。
Always wanted to have a child
一直想要个孩子
we tried for years.
我们尝试了多年。
All we did every time we failed
每次失败时我们所做的一切
was like a part of his died.
就像是他死去的一部分。
Oh, did he let someone else fuck his wife finally happened?
哦，他让别人操他的妻子终于发生了吗？
Oh, that day when we found out,
哦，那天我们发现，
I never been so happy.
我从来没有这么开心过。
Why did you default to like somebody else?
为什么你默认喜欢别人？
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Because maybe his sperm doesn't match of hers, you know?
因为也许他的精子和她的不匹配，你知道吗？
So they need someone else's sperm.
所以他们需要别人的精子。
What if it was your sperm, huh?
如果是你的精子呢，嗯？
What if it's your child?
如果是你的孩子呢？
Like we're family now.
就像我们现在是一家人一样。
That would make us related.
那会让我们有联系。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, well,
那好吧，
ok. I think this is a good place to stop them.
行。 我认为这是阻止他们的好地方。
Yeah, it is. It pulled it off here, and.
是啊，就是。 它在这里成功了，而且。
Yeah, because the game is still like, what?
是啊，因为游戏还是一样的，什么？
How what?
怎么什么？
How far are we into the game? Like, halfway.
我们离游戏有多远？ 比如，半途而废。
I think it's halfway.
我认为是一半。
I think I got told it was like a nine hour game.
我想我被告知这就像一场九小时的比赛。
Yeah. So this is nothing. So we're, like, halfway.
是的。 所以这没什么。 所以我们，就像，一半。
So I think we could finish it next time.
所以我认为我们下次可以完成它。
This thing.
这东西。
Yeah. All right, let's end the here chat.
是的。 好吧，让我们结束这里的聊天。
Okeydokey, it.
Okeydokey，它。
Should not go. Oh, that was really fun.
不应该去。 哦，那真的很有趣。
I enjoyed that.
我喜欢那个。
I enjoy that. It's on like this is.
我喜欢那个。 它是这样的。
I've never played a game like this.
我从来没有玩过这样的游戏。
Besides, it takes two, and I can see why I won this one game of the year.
此外，它需要两个，我可以理解为什么我赢得了今年的这一场比赛。
It's something I don't know or.
这是我不知道或不知道的事情。
Like I wanted a word.
就像我想要一个词。
Something like that is still really fucking awesome.
像这样的东西仍然非常他妈的棒。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Like, don't kiss.
就像，不要亲吻。
Me. Oh, oh, oh. Ok.
我。 哦哦哦。 行。
But thank you for collabing today with me.
但是感谢您今天与我合作。
Because you were here.
因为你在这里。
It was really fun.
这真的很有趣。
There's a lot of good moments in this, I think.
我想，这里面有很多美好的时刻。
OK, all right, so just do the next one sometime in the future.
好的，好的，所以请在以后的某个时间做下一个。
Yeah, I could do.
是的，我可以。
I we have talked about, I don't know, either next year,
我我们已经谈过了，我不知道，要么明年，得到你的，你的打扰。
get your, your interrupting. You're interrupting.
你在打断。
Sorry. Sorry.
对不起。 对不起。
I thought you're needy and fucking bitch.
我以为你是有需要的，他妈的婊子。
Anyways.
无论如何。
We're getting we can do.
我们正在做我们能做的。
It either.
它要么。
We could either.
我们也可以。
Redone.
重做。
Are you done? Huh?
你好了吗？ 嗯？
Are you done?
你好了吗？
What? What?
什么？ 什么？
So we can probably do this either next week
因此，我们可能可以在下周或在接下来的几周内或其他任何时间进行此操作。
You whatever you wanted to we can talk about.
你想谈什么我们都可以谈。
Yeah. I don't know
是的。 我不知道
why my schedule my schedule is pretty free.
为什么我的日程安排我的日程安排很自由。
So then talk about that.
那么就谈谈这个吧。
I do want to finish this game, though. It's really fucking amazing.
不过，我确实想完成这场比赛。 真是太他妈了不起了。
Yeah, of. Course.
是的，的。 课程。
Yay. All right, I'll just talk to my chat for a bit then, OK?
耶。 好吧，那我就和我的聊天聊一聊，好吗？
All right.
好的。
I will log off here.
我将在这里注销。
Did take care and have a good day, dude.
确实照顾好并度过了愉快的一天，伙计。
All right?
好的？
Yeah, you too. Bye.
对，你也是。 再见。
Bye. Bye.
再见。 再见。
Thank you, Dude.
谢谢老兄。
Fucking kiss me.
他妈的吻我。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Give me a second.
你稍等一会儿。
I'm going to exit.
我要退出了。
Mm mm
嗯嗯
mm mm mm mm mm mm mm.
emmmm。
Okeydokey.
Okeydokey。
Let's go back to the bedroom.
我们回卧室吧。
Gimme a second, y'all.
给我一秒钟，你们大家。
I just got to figure out how to get back to the bedroom.
我只是想弄清楚如何回到卧室。
Here we go. All right,
开始了。 好的，
Hello?
你好？
Where am I?
我在哪里？
Oh,there am I, very cool. Okay.
哦，我来了，很酷。 好的。
All right, I'll turn on some music, and then we can talk for a little bit
好吧，我会打开一些音乐，然后我们可以聊一聊，然后我们就结束了。
before we end things off. Okay.
好的。
Thank you guys so much for coming by today, though.
不过，非常感谢你们今天光临。
It means a lot that everyone here really enjoyed the game.
这意味着这里的每个人都非常喜欢这场比赛。
I had such a fun time with this.
我玩得很开心。
This is fucking amazing, dude.
这他妈的太神奇了，伙计。
Like, honestly,
就像，老实说，
I didn't think it was
与需要两个相比，我认为它不会经得起任何考验，但该死的家伙，我是。
I'm really enjoying myself so far, and, like.
到目前为止，我真的很享受自己，而且，喜欢。
Like, it keeps changing, right?
就像，它一直在变化，对吧？
You never really you never really get bored of anything
你永远不会真的 你永远不会对任何事情感到厌烦
because the like, everything is like, really?
因为喜欢，一切都喜欢，真的吗？
What's it you just it flips between, like, what you got to do from one part to
你是什​​么，它只是在你必须做的事情之间翻转，从一个部分到另一个部分。
the next. And the minigame games are also really pottery still.
而且小游戏也确实是陶器。
We be the arm wrestling dude.
我们是摔跤的家伙。
What do I get for winning the arm wrestling?
赢得摔跤比赛我能得到什么？
Holy shit.
天啊。
Oh, gosh, I lower down the music.
哦，天哪，我降低了音乐。
Ah, yeah.
啊，是的。
Give me a second.
你稍等一会儿。
I'm going to read through all the donations and stuff
我将通读直播期间发生的所有捐赠和事情，因为我没有通读
all of them while all the fucking chaos is happening.
所有这些都在发生，而所有他妈的混乱都在发生。
So ah, what's the thank you for the gift it's all but just thank you
所以啊，感谢你的礼物是什么，只是感谢你的浆果。
Mazzara Thank you for the 10,000 bits, dude.
Mazzara 谢谢你的 10,000 位，伙计。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Bivins I love you.
比文斯我爱你。
Thank you for the resolve Ray.
谢谢你解决雷。
Thank you for that sense.
谢谢你的感觉。
Everyone gives us
每个人都给了我们你所做的爱和对你的爱，我也感谢你的真诚。
And thank you, thank you for the donation.
谢谢你，谢谢你的捐赠。
To Churchill
致丘吉尔
SEAL and Sara.
海豹突击队和萨拉。
Thank you for the bits
谢谢你的比特
and that's it.
就是这样。
I thank you for 5000 more videos anon.
我感谢您提供了 5000 多个视频。
Thank you for all the bits as well. And the dona.
也感谢您提供的所有信息。 还有多纳。
I'm hon. Thank you for the cell monster and Yagi.
我很荣幸。 谢谢你的细胞怪物和八木。
Thank you for the cell. No, you've been trying your best to hold back.
谢谢你的细胞。 不，你一直在尽力阻止。
LAUGHTER During your night study time.
LAUGHTER 在你的夜间学习时间。
I'm so sorry we've been distracting you during your studies
很抱歉我们在你学习期间分散了你的注意力希望你喜欢这个直播吗
and I think you brought more 5000 bits and another 10,000 bits.
我认为你带来了更多的 5000 位和另外 10,000 位。
Holy shit. And hypnosis. Thank you for the 12 hours.
天啊。 还有催眠。 谢谢你的12小时。
You're on gift subs, bro.
你是礼物潜艇，兄弟。
Thank you so much. Of course.
非常感谢。 当然。
And Aurora, thank you for all the bits as well.
还有 Aurora，也感谢您提供的所有信息。
And Zen.
还有禅。
Thank you for the sub.
谢谢你的子。
And Nadia, thank you for the raid.
还有 Nadia，谢谢你的突袭。
I'm sorry I didn't get to say thank you for the read the audio earlier
很抱歉，我没能对您之前阅读音频和记录表示感谢。
Thank you for that send and give subs.Akari.
感谢您发送并给予 subs.Akari。
Thank you for the five gifts of small.
谢谢小五的礼物。
Thanks for all the gifts I'll say and thanks for all the support everybody.
感谢我要说的所有礼物，感谢大家的支持。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
It means a ton that, you know,
这意味着一吨，你知道，
you guys give so much support all the time.
你们一直给予这么多的支持。
OK, I brought our sound alerts and everything back on Nuncio
好的，我把我们的声音警报和一切都带回了
so I think it should pop up and velia.
Nuncio，所以我认为它应该弹出并 velia。
Thank you for the donation.
感谢您的捐赠。
And Zach.
还有扎克。
Yeah, thank you for the babies are not.
是的，谢谢你的婴儿不是。
Thank you for the donations. I didn't get a chance to say hi ussery.
感谢您的捐款。 我没有机会打招呼。
Love you. Have a nice day you all and good night.
爱你。 祝大家有美好的一天，晚安。
It's you did it and saying thank for the donation.
是你做到了，并感谢捐赠。
Thank you, babe.
谢谢你宝贝。
This thing was so funny. I love to help him. My roommate bullied me.
这件事太搞笑了。 我喜欢帮助他。 我的室友欺负我。
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉。
You guys are.
你们真的是。
I'd still like you to answer your phone and if you miss
我仍然希望你接听你的电话，如果你错过了
like other people, probably like you're like you do.
像其他人一样，可能就像你一样。
Shut up.
住口。
You're being too loud.
你声音太大了。
My mom even texted me saying, like, shop, I'll be quiet.
我妈妈甚至给我发短信说，比如，购物，我会安静的。
I'm on.
我在。
I have a phone call right now,
我现在有一个电话，在直播期间，我不得不在某些地方安静下来
and sound. Thank you for the $20.
和声音。 谢谢你的 20 美元。
Good morning shop.
早安店。
Please treat yourself to a wonderful lunch today. You deserve it.
今天请犒劳自己一顿丰盛的午餐。 你应得的。
That's what exactly what good you are.
这就是你到底有多好。
I want to go over now is get myself some lunch because I'm hungry.
我现在想过去给自己吃点午饭，因为我饿了。
Oh, Dana, thank you for the five T ones.
哦，Dana，谢谢你的五个 T。
And Brian, thank you for the suits your ones as well
还有布赖恩，谢谢你的西装
is your first time
是您第一次观看赔率或感谢您第一次过来观看。
It means a lot that you guys
这意味着很多你们认识的人，不仅支持我，也支持我的朋友。
So everybody that's here on the stream, if you haven't saw checked out Mysta.
因此，如果您还没有看到，请查看直播中的每个人。
Yap, be sure to go to his channel and show him some support.
是的，一定要去他的频道，给他一些支持。
He wants to hit 500 case in on YouTube to do a outlast stream
他想在 YouTube 上打 500
and I really want to watch that stream so bad dude
个案例来进行最后一次直播，我真的很想看那个直播，真是太糟糕了，伙计
like outlaws is all my favourite games of all time and I think I'd be
就像亡命之徒是我一直以来最喜欢的游戏，我想我会很清楚这是手表，所以是的，他也可以支持他的那些频道
not only just me OK Simmons lunch it's full day I'm here.
不仅是我，还好席梦思午餐，我在这里是一整天。
Well it's 12 p.m.
嗯，现在是晚上 12 点。
for me OK so I don't live in in Asia or Europe or anything like that.
对我来说好吧，所以我不住在亚洲或欧洲或类似的地方。
I live in you know the US
我住在你知道美国
ok. Mm mm mm mm
行。 emmmm
mm mm mm mm mm mm mm.
emmmm。
Yeah.
是的。
We're going to end it off here and I will catch you guys next time.
我们将在这里结束它，下次我会抓住你们。
All right.
好的。
Thank you very for coming by I love you guys so much.
非常感谢你们的光临，我非常爱你们。
Mm. Is really fun.
emm。 真的很有趣。
I hope we get to play again. National Farmers stuff.
我希望我们能再玩一次。 国家农民的东西。
I think I'll probably try to plan something for next week.
我想我可能会尝试为下周计划一些事情。
And if not next week, the following week. OK,
如果不是下周，下周。 好的，
be sure to join the discord if you haven't.
如果您还没有，请务必加入不和谐。
It's our discord dogs.
这是我们的不和谐狗。
I shop all of usually hang out there and you guys get up to date
我购物时通常都在那里闲逛，当我们上线时，你们会及时了解公告和公告
on, you know, some events and plenty of other things that we got going on.
关于，你知道的，我们正在进行一些活动和许多其他事情。
OK, and also subscribe to YouTube.
好的，还订阅 YouTube。
I do have a YouTube channel, by the way.
顺便说一句，我确实有一个 YouTube 频道。
If people didn't know about that, I do try to upload their whenever
如果人们不知道这一点，我会尝试随时上传他们的
I can, but some not all the time.Follow me on Twitter as well.
我可以，但有些不是一直都可以。也可以在 Twitter 上关注我。
We're almost up for manslaughter as well, so that's really insane.
我们也差点被误杀，所以这真的很疯狂。
I feel like we hit 400 K on YouTube, on Twitter.
我觉得我们在 YouTube 和 Twitter 上达到了 400 K。
I'll do something special for you guys.
我会为你们做一些特别的事情。
God plan on the celebration.
上帝计划庆祝。
Yeah,
是的，
OK, I'm going to apply an ad break.
好的，我将应用广告插播时间。
So if you guys want to stick around and support
所以如果你们想留下来支持
my plan outbreak, that would be very much appreciated.
我的计划爆发，那将不胜感激。
All right.
好的。
And I'll look for somebody to rate in the meantime.
同时我会找人来评价。
So  BRB.
所以BRB。
OK.
好的。
Who is live right now if you go read.
如果你去阅读，现在谁在直播。
Sergeant Joshua Thorne about bum
约书亚·索恩中士关于流浪汉
bum ba ba ba dum dum bum and.
bum ba ba ba dum dum bum and。
I think, uh, let's see it all
我想，呃，让我们看看这一切
on the green is also live
on the green 也是活的
I think we all radar.
我想我们都雷达。
I think Eddie
我觉得埃迪
let's go read them
让我们去阅读它们，看看它们在做什么。
They're just chatting right now.
他们现在只是在聊天。
Usher let's go see what they're all still.
亚瑟让我们去看看他们都还在。
I don't think we read them before either. So I be kind of nice.
我认为我们以前也没有读过它们。 所以我会很好。
Oh God. See?
天啊。 看？
And I said, oh, go see it. Oh.
我说，哦，去看看。 哦。
I'm giddy and.
我头晕目眩。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I know. Damn, God
我知道。 该死的，上帝
thank god
感谢上帝，它已经消失了。
Now, I think they're just shouting right now, so.
现在，我认为他们现在只是在大喊大叫，所以。
Yeah, let's go over there and see what's up.
是的，让我们去那里看看发生了什么事。
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
我明天见。
Be sure to come by tomorrow at 8 p.m.
明天晚上 8 点一定要来。
EDT or 9 a.m. JST.
EDT 或 JST 上午 9 点。
We're going to be playing to the moon and it's going to be
我们将要玩到月球，这将是另一个故事时间，因为我发现我真的很想看到。
So I wanted to play the game again to have like a proper story
所以我想再次玩这个游戏来有一个适当的故事会议，喜欢在
session and like do some full narration in VA.
VA 做一些完整的叙述。
And I'm also going to try and play the sequel
下周我还将尝试玩名为《寻找天堂》的游戏的续集。
So yeah, if you guys really enjoyed our string for paranoia, and other RPG
所以，是的，如果你们真的很喜欢我们的偏执狂和其他有很多故事、大量内容和对话的
maker games where there's a lot of story and heavy content and dialogue
RPG 制作游戏
you'll enjoy tomorrow string.
你会喜欢明天的字符串。
All right. So I'll be sure come by for that.
好的。 所以我一定会为此而来。
All right.
好的。
Well, make me happy because I love I love stories
好吧，让我开心，因为我爱我喜欢故事，我仍然喜欢为你们朗读故事。
It's really fun.
这真的很有趣。
OK, good night, guys.
好的，晚安，伙计们。
Have a good night.
祝你晚安。
Have a good day.
祝你有美好的一天。
Take care
小心
Mm mm mm mm mm
mm
we are gonna see that
我们会看到的
Bye.
再见。
Gone.
走了。
Thank god.
感谢上帝。